<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 08:08:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 10:08:18 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tabletop RPG Resources by Dicegeeks</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/tabletop-rpg-resources-dicegeeks-books</link>
      <description>Let the dice decide!</description>
      <content:encoded>Embrace the will of the dice gods with this bundle of gamemaster resources from Dicegeeks, designed to help you improvise fun and imaginative scenarios at the table! You’ll get more than 30 books to help quickly randomly generate content for your tabletop RPGs, including the &lt;em&gt;The Great Book of Random Tables&lt;/em&gt; and a vast library of spin-offs, covering genres from fantasy to cyberpunk, and a multitude of scenarios, like adventure hooks, dungeons, inns and taverns, and more. Also included are titles packed with GMing guidance, like &lt;em&gt;The No-Prep Gamemaster&lt;/em&gt;, full of practical advice for running spontaneous RPG sessions. Pay what you want for this bundle of handy GM tools, and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c7879b211b41ce27606f208d330181d01a969510.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=6c6b9e63ea229cb562ad2a44bc5bb0e0" length="78030" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Tales by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-tales-paizo-books</link>
      <description>Novels &amp; stories from the realms of Pathfinder</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover tales of heroism, espionage, love, blood, and betrayal in this bundle of fiction set in the award-winning world of the Pathfinder Roleplaying Game! This library of 40+ ebooks from Paizo is filled with epic adventures from across the world of Golarion. Uncover the secrets of the elves in the fantastical &lt;em&gt;Queen of Thorns&lt;/em&gt;. Explore the impact of strange wonders from the sky in &lt;em&gt;Reign of Stars&lt;/em&gt;. Sail the Inner Sea with the crew of &lt;em&gt;Pirate’s Promise&lt;/em&gt;, and much more—and help support ComicBooks for Kids!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/75d7283f511e5ea8795601cca1c7f36553632e8f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9dd23bc4863464a7ffaf3d324e46e96d" length="80088" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math for Programmers 2023 by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-for-programmers-2023-manning-books</link>
      <description>Level up your programming fundamentals</description>
      <content:encoded>Dive into math, machine learning, and other crucial disciplines and take your programming skills to the next level! Our latest bundle from Manning Publications will help you harness math to write better code, utilize deep learning across various languages and applications, and get up to speed on foundational concepts like functional programming, cryptography, and data structures. Pay what you want and help support Trees, Water &amp; People with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/57d2d615aaa7ad50eb6e73e93927622ef3a75a8e.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9db31843017ff44b6751de1dfd460893" length="56055" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Cooking</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mexican-cooking-books</link>
      <description>A vast culinary library of Mexico</description>
      <content:encoded>Deepen your understanding of Mexican cuisine with this expansive collection of cookbooks, designed to help you harness and master the flavors you love! Start your journey with &lt;em&gt;Oaxaca: Home Cooking from the Heart of Mexico&lt;/em&gt; for a collection of authentic recipes from the region’s rich culinary tradition. Step into &lt;em&gt;Claudia’s Cocina&lt;/em&gt; for &lt;em&gt;MasterChef&lt;/em&gt; winner Claudia Sandoval’s personal take on traditional Mexican cuisine. Tuck into &lt;em&gt;Vegan Mexico&lt;/em&gt; for delicious plant-based recipes that will help you hit your macros. Pay what you want for these books and more than 20 others, spanning Mexico’s multifaceted cuisine, and support the Global FoodBanking Network with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d4f951bd7747a4194a93751c20e50dd4af951e29.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e0a4403ce4e60fcddab2ca7ce5e31b13" length="172801" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traveller by Mongoose Publishing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/traveller-mongoose-publishing-books</link>
      <description>The universe awaits</description>
      <content:encoded>Set out on a journey into the unknown in &lt;em&gt;Traveller&lt;/em&gt;, the science fiction role-playing game of the far future! This starfarers’ bundle features over a dozen digital rulebooks, sourcebooks, and character &amp; campaign resources for the latest edition of the iconic tabletop RPG. Plunder the galaxy in the &lt;em&gt;Pirates of Drinax&lt;/em&gt; campaign and &lt;em&gt;Drinaxian Companion&lt;/em&gt;, expanding the setting with new possibilities for adventure. Gear up with weapons and equipment using the &lt;em&gt;Central Supply Catalogue&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Field Catalogue&lt;/em&gt;. Get everything you need to craft and play your own sci-fi saga, and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/32efdae968eb895834c3e8d5c75b5e4de6e197d3.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e0e8eeb76dc8772b2419f6f69d8c67e7" length="96564" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA and Cisco Cert Prep by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/comptia-and-cisco-cert-prep-packt-books</link>
      <description>Certification training for IT pros</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn the knowledge you need to get certified in CompTIA and Cisco with this bundle of ebooks from Packt. Featuring exam guides and practice tests for cert in CyberOps, implementing and administering Cisco solutions, CompTIA Security+, and much more, this bundle will help IT professionals take the next step in their career. Study up, and help support charity: water with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/b5bcd5b52c33628bf3af915fe39a680ac4c2a5df.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=199e46258ce61fa3719c7422b555279b" length="79230" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tad Williams: Osten Ard, Otherland, and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/tad-williams-osten-ard-otherland-and-beyond-books</link>
      <description>Experience the vast world of Tad Williams</description>
      <content:encoded>Get lost in the boundless imagination of best-selling science fiction and fantasy author Tad Williams with this vast collection of novels. Techno-thriller &lt;em&gt;City of Golden Shadow&lt;/em&gt; is your intro to the harrowing &lt;em&gt;Otherland&lt;/em&gt; series, where vast conspiracies harness wondrous VR worlds for wicked ends. Journey into Williams’ beloved fantasy world of Osten Ard—praised by the likes of George R. R. Martin and Patrick Rothfuss—with the &lt;em&gt;The Witchwood Crown&lt;/em&gt;. Dive into these and other series from Williams (including &lt;em&gt;Shadowmarch&lt;em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Bobby Dollar&lt;em&gt;), and support National Coalition Against Censorship with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a47d80bcc3b6ee5d663ee0a4f94d065349ea7449.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0935a66260f4f040c15876a062425951" length="97120" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bethesda 3D Printables and TTRPGs Feat. Elder Scrolls</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/bethesda-3d-printables-and-ttrpgs-feat-elder-scrolls-books</link>
      <description>The Elder Scrolls, Dishonored, and Fallout tabletop adventures</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore the realms of Tamriel, the Empire of the Isles, and the wastelands of America with this bundle of tabletop role-playing &amp; war-gaming ebooks and 3D printables! This bundle featuring Bethesda’s popular fantasy and sci-fi universes features rulebooks and more resources for &lt;em&gt;Fallout: The Roleplaying Game&lt;/em&gt; &amp; &lt;em&gt;Wasteland Warfare&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Elder Scrolls: Call to Arms&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Dishonored&lt;/em&gt;, plus a cache of 3D print-at-home files to bring your wastelands and tombs to life. Experience your favorite universes in a whole new dimension, and help support International Rescue Committee with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/707f5c0a75a85e669be3066359bfb4c8102133d5.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3635d4d81e211d0b349fb2db510c9b0c" length="81004" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps 2023 by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/devops-2023-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Your software development &amp; operations reference library</description>
      <content:encoded>Expand your DevOps skills and solve a range of engineering &amp; IT issues with this bundle of books from O’Reilly. Learn how to harness service mesh technology in &lt;em&gt;Consul: Up and Running&lt;/em&gt;. Discover best practices for managing reliable and sustainable systems in &lt;em&gt;Modern System Administration&lt;/em&gt;. Tap into the collected wisdom of &lt;em&gt;97 Things Every IT Professional Should Know&lt;/em&gt; and more, and help support Code for America.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/275a241dd3a33970317790a2b48c681dbfb7585f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ffbf3143bc438a542940f0a9359ffb10" length="53643" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
