<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 09:10:24 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Microservices by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/microservices-packt-books</link>
      <description>Integrate, deploy, and scale seamlessly</description>
      <content:encoded>Elevate your command of microservices and learn to craft scalable, modular, and resilient applications with some of the most prevalent and powerful tools available! This bundle from the leaders at Packt is full of books that’ll get you up to speed on building and maintaining microservice applications with a variety of frameworks. You’ll learn to craft cloud-native microservices with Spring, how to leverage your Python skills to create performant applications with FastAPI, keep your services communicating efficiently with gRPC, and much more! Pay what you want for 16 books that’ll help you master these in-demand skills and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c901772eb1ac4851e149e48d7b6c4c7d06d8b878.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=cd90b5f1eb47ebb791109306ceb7a91b" length="86048" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Age and Mass Effect Comics by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dragon-age-and-mass-effect-comics-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Explore worlds of Mass Effect &amp; Dragon Age comics</description>
      <content:encoded>The masterfully realized universes of famed game maker BioWare come alive on the page in this collection of &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age&lt;/em&gt; comics from Dark Horse! Get into Commander Shepard’s offscreen adventures in &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect Volume 1: Redemption&lt;/em&gt;, which takes place after the events of the revered &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect 2&lt;/em&gt;. Prime yourself for high adventure with &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age: The Missing&lt;/em&gt;, the comic story that leads into &lt;em&gt;Dreadwolf&lt;/em&gt;, the upcoming fourth installment in the beloved RPG series. Get more than 15 exciting &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age&lt;/em&gt; volumes in this bundle, and support Child’s Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/10336583fd715a21b1be9aa3385175d1aa126225.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8436da0235c577e6901be93e62e5ed1f" length="123459" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rick and Morty Comic Collection by Oni Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/rick-and-morty-comic-collection-oni-press-books</link>
      <description>Time-traveling, multiverse-hopping comic adventures</description>
      <content:encoded>Join the universe’s most notorious superscientist Rick Sanchez and his hapless grandson Morty on adventures across time and space—and beyond all reason—in this bundle of &lt;em&gt;Rick and Morty&lt;/em&gt; comics from Oni Press! Based on the hit [adult swim] animated series, this collection features 60 issues from the acclaimed original run, taking readers from dimension C-132 to C-137 and a host of alternate realities in between. Lose yourself in the &lt;em&gt;Rick &amp; Morty&lt;/em&gt; comics multiverse, and help support  BINC and The Hero Initiative with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/67e9ecd07a1e8a015b40c29d9551d0a834da4624.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=cbb2c9500bc7792cb5761ba94f9976d5" length="105985" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking &amp; Security Cert Prep with EXAM CRAM and More By Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/networking-security-cert-prep-with-exam-cram-and-more-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Study guides to help you get certified</description>
      <content:encoded>Preparing for a tech certification exam to advance your career? Get ready—and don’t sweat it—with the help of these practical study resources from Pearson! The guides in this bundle cover a range of the most popular certifications, including Cisco CCNA, CompTIA Network+, CISSP, AWS Solutions Architect, and more networking, security, and IT disciplines. Get the resources you need to prepare for test day success, and help support Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f071b536f78c314a45d2fb0fdb8f8b4140613d9f.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=6e787f1c662fc04e1b939184ac6d4baa" length="68559" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Incal to Twilight Man by Humanoids</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/incal-to-twilight-man-humanoids-books</link>
      <description>A treasury of groundbreaking comics</description>
      <content:encoded>Lose yourself in celebrated fantasy, sci-fi, and biographical comic fiction in this massive collection from Humanoids! Journey to a surreal dystopia of Metabarons and Technopriests in Alejandro Jodorowsky’s influential &lt;em&gt;The Incal&lt;/em&gt;, featuring art by the legendary Mœbius. Step into the dimension of TV legend Rod Serling’s mind in Koren Shadmi’s &lt;em&gt;The Twilight Man&lt;/em&gt;. Discover tales of time-traveling photographers (&lt;em&gt;Luisa: Now &amp; Then&lt;/em&gt;), unstoppable forces (&lt;em&gt;Armies&lt;/em&gt;), and much, much more across 100+ volumes—and help support the Freedom to Read Foundation.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/91a5add14f9b48b627a9fa0cc1473b6ea5a916ca.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=45f1509edbaaf9fe18fb1b55db772901" length="84599" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who Megabundle 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/doctor-who-megabundle-2023-books</link>
      <description>A TARDIS full of audio dramas, comic collections, and role-playing</description>
      <content:encoded>The wonders of the Whoniverse are at your fingertips with this massive bundle of Doctor Who comic collections, tabletop role-playing games, and audio dramas! Take your gaming group on a trip to Gallifrey and beyond with the &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who Roleplaying Game Rulebook&lt;/em&gt; and a TARDIS-full of adventures and supplements. Travel to the swinging 60s with two different incarnations of the Doctor in the comic collection &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who: A Tale of Two Time Lords&lt;/em&gt;. Return to one of the most captivating settings from the TV show in the audio drama anthology &lt;em&gt;Tales from New Earth&lt;/em&gt;. Get all this and more than 30 other Whovian treats, and help BBC Children in Need with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/668832e9f84cb36ab604c36f7debe1fb47a88174.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=301bc9e6e809ec66a2639cc4b45d33c7" length="106614" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Science by No Starch Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-science-no-starch-press-books</link>
      <description>Welcome to the age of data</description>
      <content:encoded>Elevate your career with mission-critical skills essential across business, research, and academia with this data science book bundle by No Starch Press. &lt;em&gt;Dive Into Data Science&lt;/em&gt; will teach you how to harness the approachable Python programming language to solve common business challenges. If you’re a researcher, &lt;em&gt;Python Tools for Scientists&lt;/em&gt; will equip you with a powerful arsenal for creating data visualizations, running simulations, and more. And regardless of your discipline, &lt;em&gt;The Book of Dash&lt;/em&gt; will empower you to create dashboards that elegantly and effectively present your data. Pay what you want for these and 15 more books, and support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/b2974af9fc2f75b3707c06c330eb0a2cfd65b04b.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9bfb96e3245cc118daedd5e1fb69dfa9" length="111514" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ready for NaNoWriMo 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/get-ready-for-nanowrimo-2023-books</link>
      <description>NaNoWriMo inspiration, tools, and advice</description>
      <content:encoded>Getting creative for National Novel Writing Month this year? Discover inspiration. advice, and tools to help achieve your goals in our NaNoWriMo 2023 bundle! Get guides to building compelling science fiction and fantasy worlds. Pick up habits to keep you focused and help break blocks. Learn how to effectively outline, structure your plot, or craft a screenplay. Plus, unlock timely access to the creative writing software tools Novlr and Plottr, along with courses from Writing Mastery Academy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Your purchase helps support National Novel Writing Month, the nonprofit organization behind the movement, helping provide the structure, community, and encouragement to help people find their voices, achieve creative goals, and build new worlds—on and off the page.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c7e248b6694abe12ac03d73c214fddc0b4f60b55.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=4fe74b1a9481d66e30ea7f8dc3a3e1b6" length="68405" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best of Warhammer by Cubicle 7</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/best-warhammer-cubicle-7-books</link>
      <description>RPGs spanning the worlds of Warhammer</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re partial to Space Marines, Stormcast Eternals, or good ol’ greenskins and high elves, this bundle of &lt;em&gt;Warhammer&lt;/em&gt; pen-and-paper RPGs from Cubicle 7 will bring eternities of adventure to your table! If you seek adventure in the 41st century, &lt;em&gt;Warhammer 40,000: Wrath &amp; Glory&lt;/em&gt; will immerse your RPG group in the galaxy’s grimdark battles and heretical nightmares. If your tastes run classic, &lt;em&gt;Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay&lt;/em&gt; puts the entirety of the beloved Old World at your fingertips. And if you want to explore a realm of high fantasy, magitech, and post-apocalyptic horror, &lt;em&gt;Warhammer Age of Sigmar: Soulbound&lt;/em&gt; invites you to forge your group’s destiny in a gods-shattered realm. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Pay what you want for over 20 books, supplements, game aids, and more resources for these three thrilling Warhammer RPG systems, and help support Children's Health Ireland with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7b0173350913ab4a762cdeb2b79b41e4856f21b2.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e95d0cab903e50aa2bd765cfecd48f8e" length="120144" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming MEGA Bundle 2023 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/programming-mega-bundle-2023-packt-books</link>
      <description>Your practical all-purpose programming library</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn principles, best practices, and advanced concepts for myriad programming disciplines with this massive bundle from Packt. This 30-book library covers a wide range of topics today’s coders and tech professionals need to know, including cloud computing, systems engineering, quantum machine learning, and more. It also includes development resources for popular platforms and languages like Java, Go, Delphi, and more. Level up your programming knowledge, and help support Child’s Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/28422fb8226c8da694837145c660eab65bb85f49.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=54067ed57a81d6b50daff84c4c6b5ca9" length="79593" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
