<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 08:09:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:09:48 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud Development by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/aws-azure-and-google-cloud-development-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Cloud skills for data, IoT &amp; more!</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn how to leverage leading cloud platforms for mission critical tasks—from data science to smart device control—with this book bundle from O’Reilly! &lt;em&gt;Architecting IoT Solutions on Azure&lt;/em&gt; will teach you about device management at scale and get you up to speed on Azure’s tools for building globally distributed systems. &lt;em&gt;Data Science on the Google Cloud Platform&lt;/em&gt; shows you how to implement end-to-end data pipelines with cloud native tools through a series of hands-on projects. Pay what you want for these and more—a total of 15 books valued at almost $1,000—and helps support Code for America with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7046227edfbc07bd818855c4eba298236cd64d23.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e47ae3b724264be74edb016645b0b60b" length="74634" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Your Finances For Dummies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/better-your-finances-for-dummies-books</link>
      <description>Dummy-proof guidance on personal finance</description>
      <content:encoded>Need help getting your finances in order, building wealth, and setting yourself up for a secure future? These books in the popular &lt;em&gt;For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; series are ready to come to the rescue! &lt;em&gt;Investing in your 20s &amp; 30s For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; is full of targeted investment advice for people early in their careers, designed to set you up for future success. &lt;em&gt;Budgeting For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; takes the pain out of day-to-day finance, sharing the tools you’ll need to manage debt, improve your credit, and live your best life within your means. &lt;em&gt;Investing in Stocks For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; demystifies this complex world, covering everything you need to to know invest wisely and grow your wealth. Pay what you want for this bundle full of expert-backed financial guidance and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7f0ab3e89aaaefc0d37b94118e5ad87916f5ce44.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=736dcfbe6d109d5055206bf15903b7aa" length="71676" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-packt-books</link>
      <description>Comprehensive instruction on software architecture</description>
      <content:encoded>Developers of all disciplines, it’s time to take the lead and start creating software that’s cleaner, highly scalable, and more performant with this bundle of books on software architecture from Packt. &lt;em&gt;The Software Architect's Handbook&lt;/em&gt; covers the design patterns, best practices, and paradigms for efficient software development, with an eye on performance, security, and big-picture decision making. &lt;em&gt;Modern Computer Architecture and Organization&lt;/em&gt; will give you a thorough understanding of hardware down to the circuit level, covering modern architectures like 86, x64, ARM, and RISC-V. Pay what you want for over 20 books on this essential topic and help support Hello World with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9aa4013a6da72c087242395132da4d85be3fa33c.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f52b1891bb928f819e606f4afd98d3c9" length="77691" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All I Need to Know I Learned from Star Trek</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/all-i-need-to-know-i-learned-from-star-trek-books</link>
      <description>Go boldly behind the scenes…</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore strange new worlds, seek out new life and civilizations, and deepen your connection with all things Star Trek with this bundle full of galactic wonder! Join the crew of the Federation’s mighty flagship in a mission to prevent all-out war in the Alpha Quadrant in the novel &lt;em&gt;Star Trek Prometheus: Fire With Fire&lt;/em&gt;. Get a behind-the-scenes look at the hit show, including interviews with Sir Patrick Stewart and other Trek luminaries in &lt;em&gt;Star Trek: Picard - The Collector's Edition&lt;/em&gt;. You’ll get 18 books in total, including novels and intimate, behind the scenes coverage of your favorite Star Trek Shows and movies, and your purchase will support the EveryLibrary Institute and The Trevor Project!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/059a5d5678114634780e991c9f875ab58e7937e9.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=b257aee755c488d5681d2faa59c0118e" length="116939" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry Pratchett's Discworld by HarperCollins</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/terry-pratchetts-discworld-harpercollins-books</link>
      <description>Mighty and mundane magic</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover Sir Terry Pratchett's &lt;em&gt;Discworld&lt;/em&gt;, the beloved comic fantasy universe that’s brimming with wit, wisdom, and wonder. Start where it all began in the seminal novel &lt;em&gt;The Color of Magic&lt;/em&gt;, which follows the misadventures of the inept wizard Rincewind as he serves as tour guide to Twoflower, Discworld's first-ever sightseer. The hapless duo’s journeys continue in &lt;em&gt;The Light Fantastic&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Sourcery&lt;/em&gt;, where the scale of world-threatening hazards (and accompanying absurdities) increase exponentially. You’ll get over 35 &lt;em&gt;Discworld&lt;/em&gt; novels in all, touching all corners of this whimsical realm and all manner of its denizens, and you’ll help Room to Read with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This bundle is only available to those in the US.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2efaa22f4a33caf847c8e10d74b4b78e7963a5aa.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2009e1cb2faa32443a9e0a59bbc6ad10" length="94850" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Master 2024 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/python-master-2024-packt-books</link>
      <description>10X your Python skills</description>
      <content:encoded>Deepen your knowledge of one of the world’s most widely used and in-demand programming languages with this bundle of Python books from Packt. &lt;em&gt;Mastering Python&lt;/em&gt; will teach you the advanced skills and techniques necessary to produce clean, readable, and production-ready code. &lt;em&gt;Python Real-World Projects&lt;/em&gt; will walk you through building a project portfolio that will wow potential employers using libraries and resources like Pydantic, JupyterLab, and more. &lt;em&gt;Open Source Projects - Beyond Code&lt;/em&gt; walks you through the steps to open source success, covering licensing, ecosystem management, and other critical dimensions. Pay what you want for over 20 books that’ll take your Python skills to the next level and help support One Tree Planted!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f2eda5fc2fef24a2ad591763c1fc9857817b0f85.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c69cf5b1a1ee7528f11a1aa07043670a" length="109047" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Cthulhu by Chaosium, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/call-cthulhu-chaosium-inc-books</link>
      <description>Invite eldritch terror to your table</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring a taste of terror to your game nights with this bundle from Chaosium, complete with everything you need to run the dreaded (yet beloved) &lt;em&gt;Call of Cthulhu&lt;/em&gt; RPG system! On top of the &lt;em&gt;Call of Cthulhu Starter Set&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll get the &lt;em&gt;Investigator Handbook&lt;/em&gt;, replete with expanded rules for creating player characters, as well as the &lt;em&gt;Keeper Rulebook&lt;/em&gt;, brimming with all the information you need to keep things orderly as your table descends into madness. You’ll also get tons of adventures, including some aimed at first-time game masters, as well as entire campaigns! Pay what you want for over 25 books and game aids for this seminal RPG and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/45ea0735233838d6a510817956b91331ea76d44c.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9d20fb2fdbee0009e2cec4f30d5b97ff" length="79912" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
