<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 10:10:10 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Books That Will Radically Improve Your Sleep</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/books-that-will-radically-improve-your-sleep-books</link>
      <description>Rest, recharge, and rejuvenate</description>
      <content:encoded>Snooze your way to a healthy body and sound mind with this collection of 20 books covering the topic of sleep in all its dreamy dimensions. &lt;em&gt;The Book of Sleep&lt;/em&gt; provides 75 strategies to alleviate insomnia, based in cognitive behavioral therapy. In &lt;em&gt;The Complete Book of Dreams&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll learn techniques that will allow you to harness the healing potential of your nocturnal journeys. And if the sandman needs a nudge, &lt;em&gt;This Book Will Put You to Sleep&lt;/em&gt; is full of stories written to make your eyelids heavy. Don’t compromise on the immeasurable benefits of sound sleep! Pick up this dream-inducing bundle, and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ba2bf9db80ff44824ac1f1d766f8f4ae7544254d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8568515cb015b034bc4c4008d821b796" length="45083" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization by Taylor &amp; Francis</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-visualization-taylor-francis-books</link>
      <description>Turn raw data into tangible insights</description>
      <content:encoded>Transform your data into visual models that spark new insights for your project or organization with the help of the experts at Taylor &amp; Francis. The library of 20 ebooks explores multiple facets of data visualization. Learn to tell stories with your data, and uncover graphics techniques to aid in analysis. Explore the world of modern input devices, and derive meaning from your data using R visualizations. Translate your data into more human terms, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f6d4ec5e74f7083323c43faae0dcd87b81104f0a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7c38376a54eed82bf94a9faaf888b41e" length="126319" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assassin's Creed Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/assassins-creed-mega-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Take the leap from screen to page</description>
      <content:encoded>Peek into the chronicles of the ages-old battle between the Assassin Brotherhood and the Templar Order in this massive bundle of books and comics set in the &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed&lt;/em&gt; universe! Get a gritty account of the life of the mighty Eivor before the events of the game in the comic series &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed Valhalla: Song of Glory&lt;/em&gt;. Witness the clash between the Brotherhood and Templars in Tang Dynasty–era China in the stunning manga &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed: Dynasty&lt;/em&gt;. Join a crew of young Assassins on a journey that spans early 20th Century Spain and the modern day in the comic &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed: Uprising&lt;/em&gt;. Get all these and more—a total over 20 books and comics—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/e426c85adbb9409a9f009fe8f0ef52bd6afb7193.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=95cce1ce0336b67bab1bd494657229aa" length="130748" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Manga by Saturday AM</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/diverse-manga-saturday-am-books</link>
      <description>Awesome manga from diverse creators</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover your new favorite series with this collection of diverse manga from diverse creators across the globe, in partnership with publisher Saturday AM! In &lt;em&gt;Apple Black&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll meet Sano, a young sorcerer with an epic destiny who must battle sinister temptations. Join &lt;em&gt;Clock Striker&lt;/em&gt;’s aspiring warrior-engineer Cast as she pursues her dreams amidst hidebound tradition and discrimination. Explore the &lt;em&gt;Massively Multiplayer World of Ghosts&lt;/em&gt; alongside Nil, an average kid who must do extraordinary things to survive its mysteries and hazards. Lose yourself in these great manga and more, and support BINC with your purchase</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/152f8f2d1e8e1645f8bbe5706b1070b196ee7d7f.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=74fef6a4eeda1e0a3474d7d03ae53582" length="137750" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Month MEGA Bundle by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-month-mega-bundle-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Unlock a library of cybersecurity knowledge</description>
      <content:encoded>October marks Cybersecurity Awareness Month, and the tech experts at O’Reilly are here to help programmers, engineers, and IT pros keep systems safe all year round. Learn about identity-native access management and intelligence-driven incident response. Wrap your head around the principles of security chaos engineering and security-as-code methodology. Build the know-how you need to create systems that can withstand today’s ever-evolving cybersecurity threats, and help support Code for America with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d040a836d78b4140afaae4d4b975dbda83435c93.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3c263f0ad34833210076dd7dfece3cd4" length="100588" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eerie Comics Collection by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/eerie-comics-collection-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>A groundbreakingly gruesome horror comic library</description>
      <content:encoded>Looking for some macabre reading for the spookiest season of the year? Fix your gaze upon this massive &lt;em&gt;Eerie&lt;/em&gt; archive from Dark Horse, collecting over 130 issues of the long-running horror comics magazine! Featuring terrifying tales and astonishing artwork from legends like Gray Morrow, Frank Frazetta, Alex Toth, Neal Adams, and Joe Orlando, this &lt;em&gt;Eerie&lt;/em&gt; library is for everyone who loves strange and twisted tales of terror, fantasy, and science fiction. Lose yourself in the &lt;em&gt;Eerie Archives&lt;/em&gt;, and help support the Hero Initiative with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1625e695ec6054c8a5ec1cf40ec25d6958ea9ea0.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=85bce213a6db2ea07d65992763ee4c53" length="126627" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.E. Modesitt Collection by Tor Publishing Group</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/le-modesitt-collection-tor-publishing-group-books</link>
      <description>Order, chaos, magic, and technology</description>
      <content:encoded>Lose yourself in the contemporary epic fantasy and science fiction of bestselling author L. E. Modesitt, Jr.! Journey to a realm where chaos and order clash in all 22 current volumes of Modesitt’s iconic Saga of Recluce series, from &lt;em&gt;The Magic of Recluce&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;em&gt;Fairhaven Rising&lt;/em&gt;, plus the short story collection &lt;em&gt;Recluce Tales&lt;/em&gt;. Discover the history and fate of a lost civilization in all eight novels of the Corean Chronicles. Travel to the far future in standalone science-fiction works including &lt;em&gt;The Hammer of Darkness&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Quantum Shadows&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support World Wildlife Fund with your purchase. </content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ee21ec0edd81dfb805306ba2d3aebd491dd7a1d7.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=635d5cbde9bdcb3833d95cf84b45a19b" length="96320" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a Python Expert by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/become-python-expert-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Sage Python advice from the pros</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re a seasoned pro or a budding coder looking to cut your teeth in web dev, data science, or AI engineering, this bundle of Python books from Pearson will bolster your command of this indispensable programming language! &lt;em&gt;Effective Python&lt;/em&gt; will teach you tips and tricks, straight from Google Python guru Brett Slakin, to help you get the most out of your code. Aimed at experienced developers, &lt;em&gt;Deitel: Python for Programmers&lt;/em&gt; provides hands-on exercises focusing on deep learning, big data, and other exciting applications. &lt;em&gt;Learn Python 3 the Hard Way&lt;/em&gt; gives you a rigorous crash course where you’ll create working code regardless of your level. Get all these and more, and help support Npower with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7770c5472abc4b83125f59214a3dac13548debba.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=faca5e782c6f47f569ebeaccd951ade7" length="101945" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowrun Legends Fiction Collection by Catalyst Game Labs</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shadowrun-legends-catalyst-game-labs-books</link>
      <description>Elves &amp; cyberdecks, Orks &amp; megacorps</description>
      <content:encoded>Dive deep into a world where sorcery and cybernetics collide with this collection of &lt;em&gt;Shadowrun&lt;/em&gt; novels! Included in this collection of over 40 books are the stories that set the foundation and flesh out the world of this iconic RPG setting. In &lt;em&gt;Never Deal with a Dragon&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll get a thrilling look at the frightening powers that drive &lt;em&gt;Shadowrun&lt;/em&gt;’s megacorps. In &lt;em&gt;2XS&lt;/em&gt;, a deadly cyberdrug is infesting the streets, and its origins point to something ancient and wicked. Get these and more classic novels that defined this beloved cyberpunk fantasy world, and help support the Legal Defense Fund!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7c9affe16c33ee0730f50440c879159611919eba.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0d110915c26a104652bbc2698b4297f5" length="104476" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Build your software architecture knowledge</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you want to create a solid foundation for a career or expand your existing software architecture skills, this bundle of books from O’Reilly can help you achieve your goals! Explore architectural patterns, component determination, evolutionary architecture, and more. Dig into the facets that distinguish architecture from engineering and other development disciplines. Learn the skills you need to succeed in this in-demand field, and help support Code for America with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/3e20830836740faa73279165e851dcfad5b50066.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3109c162d73b89f2ac23559c6959780f" length="61434" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
