<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:09:28 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate RPG Guides by Adams Media Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-rpg-guides-adams-media-holiday-encore-books</link>
      <description>Level up your role-playing</description>
      <content:encoded>Back for a Very Humble Holiday encore…Make your campaigns more epic, your heroes more mythic, and your game sessions more fun for the whole party with these books from Adams Media! This TTRPG treasure trove features 20+ digital guides to worldbuilding, coming up with great characters, concocting compelling challenges, being a legendary host, and lots more. Explore a library for players, DMs, and anyone who loves the art and craft of role-playing, and help support Worldreader with your purchase. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quantities for our Very Humble Holiday encore bundles are highly limited, and this bundle will no longer be available for purchase after supplies run out.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; If you purchase the bundle, please be aware that keys may not be immediately available for certain items; we appreciate your patience while we work to restock them.&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/888e954f078152e48a979edb0d6787eb8e854664.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=62622b4851a21f7cf9ccd472a545f805" length="56832" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition Legacy Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-legacy-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>Everything you need for Pathfinder 2E</description>
      <content:encoded>Endless adventure awaits your RPG group with this &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition&lt;/em&gt; bundle from Paizo! Included are the &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition Core Rulebook&lt;/em&gt; and digital &lt;em&gt;Beginner’s Box&lt;/em&gt;, as well as a bounty of sourcebooks, supplements, and adventure modules to keep your table busy for multiple campaigns’ worth of play. You’ll get three volumes of the &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder Bestiary&lt;/em&gt; to keep the challenges fresh, numerous adventures like the beloved &lt;em&gt;Crown of the Kobold King&lt;/em&gt;, and much more! Pay what you want for a lifetime of fuel for your RPG sessions and help support Comic Books for Kids with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/806612c23f6b64cca4e1604090183cb6d1bc9c9d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f2b6badace615885f0c7ec8a81d717e3" length="109089" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning, AI, and Bots by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-ai-and-bots-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>All about artificial intelligence</description>
      <content:encoded>Delve deep into the realms of machine learning, AI, and bots with this bundle of books from O’Reilly! Inside this 14-book library, you’ll get expert insights on the tools and technology behind these cutting-edge fields. Learn about coding in Python or TensorFlow. Dig into designing deep learning systems. Level up your skills &amp; knowledge whether you’re a novice or a seasoned prof, and help support Code for America with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/694e8b932100cc4fbc92cc46b1a9ac1ff23cdcaf.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ef51cc515e462f31190cd627001d8bc2" length="95330" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directors, Filmmaking, and Hollywood Movies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/directors-filmmaking-and-hollywood-movies-books</link>
      <description>Books on film</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore the work of the world’s most celebrated movies and moviemakers with this library of books! This 25-book collection puts the spotlight on visionary creators like Wes Anderson, Tim Burton, Bong Joon-ho, and Quentin Tarantino; delves into popular genres and Hollywood myths; and much more. Get lost in a library curated for cinephiles everywhere, and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2699841dd05864a4a5de7a07d8d931227be1ac64.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=578e63b3e084c60e533a61502b8f388d" length="137253" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mignola's Hellboy by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mike-mignolas-hellboy-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>A modern (and hellish) comics classic</description>
      <content:encoded>Follow &lt;em&gt;Hellboy&lt;/em&gt;, the beloved sardonic antihero, into the vilest infernal depths and beyond in this jam-packed bundle of comics from Dark Horse! Witness the occult madness that brought the Right Hand of Doom to our world in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy Volume 1: Seeds of Destruction&lt;/em&gt;. Go to the very depths of Hell alongside him in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy in Hell Volume 1: The Descent&lt;/em&gt;. Feast your eyes on his dark allure in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy: 25 Years of Covers&lt;/em&gt;. And more! Get your hands on over 30 books of &lt;em&gt;Hellboy&lt;/em&gt; and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9f270f1710b4d2992a6df2f19ed1fb3585653f0f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a5533571ee7a373c1721423b97a18a6f" length="56773" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking 2023 by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hacking-2023-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Explore the art &amp; science of hacking</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to think like a hacker with this bundle of books from No Starch Press! Inside this 18-book library, you’ll get expert insights on how to be an ethical hacker, the ins and outs of cybersecurity, how malicious actors engage in social engineering, and a lot more. Learn to defend systems, anticipate attacks, and more—and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/38b110f4b2ec62fba59357883ecd52e845cd41ed.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=b518720893642370847da7bddead7616" length="104045" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Solo RPG Library by Parts Per Million</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/solo-rpg-library-parts-per-million-books</link>
      <description>Adventure for a party of one</description>
      <content:encoded>Looking to take an RPG ruleset for a spin, but can’t manage to convince your friends to try a new system? This bundle of solo adventure modules by the specialists at Parts Per Million is exactly what you’ve been looking for! Included in the bundle are dozens of adventures written specifically for a variety of RPGs, from well-known indies like &lt;em&gt;Blades in the Dark&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dungeon Crawl Classics&lt;/em&gt;, to cult favorites like &lt;em&gt;Stars Without Number&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Lancer&lt;/em&gt;. And if your tastes run to the old school, you’ll also find plenty of solo adventures tailored for good old fashioned OSR-style play. Pay what you want for this bundle of endless adventure, and help support buildOn with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d619f174f1b64115ff260ff154b5af4819570b93.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0f0039d791488a5dd4bb2fdf6af0bd07" length="109310" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The John Scalzi Collection: Old Man's War, The Interdependency, and More, by Tor</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/john-scalzis-interdependency-old-mans-war-and-more-tor-books</link>
      <description>Discover the worlds of John Scalzi</description>
      <content:encoded>Immerse yourself in the rich sci-fi worlds of multiple Hugo Award–winning author John Scalzi! Explore themes of life extension, mortality, and humanity amidst the backdrop of alien war in the groundbreaking &lt;em&gt;Old Man's War&lt;/em&gt; series, from first novel to its thrilling conclusion in &lt;em&gt;The End of All Things&lt;/em&gt;. Also included are the mind-bending &lt;em&gt;Lock In&lt;/em&gt; series, the sprawling &lt;em&gt;Interdependency&lt;/em&gt; series, and beloved standalone novels like &lt;em&gt;Redshirts&lt;/em&gt;—and much more! Pay what you want for this library of stellar sci-fi from one of the contemporary masters, and help support the work of First Book with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a38738c8abf338d94ec3a6804956d701d2e397ae.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3e74fdf06f21f7cf28f90b8fa861f165" length="97382" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity 2023 by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-2023-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Tips &amp; tricks from white hat hackers</description>
      <content:encoded>Take your OpSec into your own hands with this bundle of books on cybersecurity from Wiley. In addition to comprehensive how-tos covering a variety of topics in the security space, you’ll get thrilling real-world accounts from renowned figures in the hacking world. In &lt;em&gt;How I Rob Banks: And Other Such Places&lt;/em&gt;, ethical hacker FC shares his adventures in testing the limits of physical bank security without breaking any laws. &lt;em&gt;Threats: What Every Engineer Should Learn From Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; combines the excitement of the galaxy far, far away with the author’s unique perspective on security threats and secure system development. Pay what you want for these and more–a total of 18 books–and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0fdfd93aec60520d885c806d21467f095b36adac.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=670279d6d023ac832d786cbe85553615" length="28370" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Start Drawing with Walter Foster</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/how-to-start-drawing-with-walter-foster-books</link>
      <description>Capture the world in your sketchbook</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to capture the world around you and let your creativity bloom with this collection of books on drawing and painting! Whether you’re a budding talent or a seasoned artist looking to dabble in a new medium, &lt;em&gt;100 Things Every Artist Should Know&lt;/em&gt; will inspire you fresh perspectives. &lt;em&gt;Urban Sketching Handbook Sketch Now, Think Later&lt;/em&gt; will get you out in the world and examining your surroundings with new eyes. With &lt;em&gt;Draw Every Little Thing&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll discover the potential for artistic growth in the mundane objects all around you. Get all these and more–over 35 books in all–and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/e2f44044431de0c00fc7f8ded97d04d00eb10189.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d35d201db24509abb6dc7ff2a4275249" length="81764" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5th Edition Mega Bundle: Gygax + Kobold and Friends + More!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/5th-edition-mega-bundle-gygax-kobold-and-friends-more-books</link>
      <description>Elevate your 5e game</description>
      <content:encoded>Searching for ways to spice up your 5e game? Look no further than this bundle, packed with a treasure hoard of 5e-compatible sourcebooks, adventures, and indispensable game aids from some of the finest publishers in the game! Sic some new threats on your seen-it-all players with the &lt;em&gt;Tome of Beasts 3&lt;/em&gt;. Send them a journey they’ll never forget with &lt;em&gt;Necropolis&lt;/em&gt;, a grand adventure based on the work of none other than Gary Gygax, the Father of RPGs! Broaden their horizons with a smorgasbord of new player options with the &lt;em&gt;Tome of Heroes&lt;/em&gt;. Pay what you want for this vast library of over 70 books—valued at more than $1,000—and help support International Medical Corps!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4e7bce0aed044b38237943a1f94e0c622c0a7c36.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f50a239ed39855b65bcb542f8f39a8f2" length="57666" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Age and Mass Effect Comics by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dragon-age-and-mass-effect-comics-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Explore worlds of Mass Effect &amp; Dragon Age comics</description>
      <content:encoded>The masterfully realized universes of famed game maker BioWare come alive on the page in this collection of &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age&lt;/em&gt; comics from Dark Horse! Get into Commander Shepard’s offscreen adventures in &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect Volume 1: Redemption&lt;/em&gt;, which takes place after the events of the revered &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect 2&lt;/em&gt;. Prime yourself for high adventure with &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age: The Missing&lt;/em&gt;, the comic story that leads into &lt;em&gt;Dreadwolf&lt;/em&gt;, the upcoming fourth installment in the beloved RPG series. Get more than 15 exciting &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age&lt;/em&gt; volumes in this bundle, and support Child’s Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/10336583fd715a21b1be9aa3385175d1aa126225.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8436da0235c577e6901be93e62e5ed1f" length="123459" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
