<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 08:08:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 10:08:46 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who Megabundle 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/doctor-who-megabundle-2023-books</link>
      <description>A TARDIS full of audio dramas, comic collections, and role-playing</description>
      <content:encoded>The wonders of the Whoniverse are at your fingertips with this massive bundle of Doctor Who comic collections, tabletop role-playing games, and audio dramas! Take your gaming group on a trip to Gallifrey and beyond with the &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who Roleplaying Game Rulebook&lt;/em&gt; and a TARDIS-full of adventures and supplements. Travel to the swinging 60s with two different incarnations of the Doctor in the comic collection &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who: A Tale of Two Time Lords&lt;/em&gt;. Return to one of the most captivating settings from the TV show in the audio drama anthology &lt;em&gt;Tales from New Earth&lt;/em&gt;. Get all this and more than 30 other Whovian treats, and help BBC Children in Need with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/668832e9f84cb36ab604c36f7debe1fb47a88174.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=301bc9e6e809ec66a2639cc4b45d33c7" length="106614" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Science by No Starch Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-science-no-starch-press-books</link>
      <description>Welcome to the age of data</description>
      <content:encoded>Elevate your career with mission-critical skills essential across business, research, and academia with this data science book bundle by No Starch Press. &lt;em&gt;Dive Into Data Science&lt;/em&gt; will teach you how to harness the approachable Python programming language to solve common business challenges. If you’re a researcher, &lt;em&gt;Python Tools for Scientists&lt;/em&gt; will equip you with a powerful arsenal for creating data visualizations, running simulations, and more. And regardless of your discipline, &lt;em&gt;The Book of Dash&lt;/em&gt; will empower you to create dashboards that elegantly and effectively present your data. Pay what you want for these and 15 more books, and support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/b2974af9fc2f75b3707c06c330eb0a2cfd65b04b.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9bfb96e3245cc118daedd5e1fb69dfa9" length="111514" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ready for NaNoWriMo 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/get-ready-for-nanowrimo-2023-books</link>
      <description>NaNoWriMo inspiration, tools, and advice</description>
      <content:encoded>Getting creative for National Novel Writing Month this year? Discover inspiration. advice, and tools to help achieve your goals in our NaNoWriMo 2023 bundle! Get guides to building compelling science fiction and fantasy worlds. Pick up habits to keep you focused and help break blocks. Learn how to effectively outline, structure your plot, or craft a screenplay. Plus, unlock timely access to the creative writing software tools Novlr and Plottr, along with courses from Writing Mastery Academy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Your purchase helps support National Novel Writing Month, the nonprofit organization behind the movement, helping provide the structure, community, and encouragement to help people find their voices, achieve creative goals, and build new worlds—on and off the page.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c7e248b6694abe12ac03d73c214fddc0b4f60b55.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=4fe74b1a9481d66e30ea7f8dc3a3e1b6" length="68405" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best of Warhammer by Cubicle 7</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/best-warhammer-cubicle-7-books</link>
      <description>RPGs spanning the worlds of Warhammer</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re partial to Space Marines, Stormcast Eternals, or good ol’ greenskins and high elves, this bundle of &lt;em&gt;Warhammer&lt;/em&gt; pen-and-paper RPGs from Cubicle 7 will bring eternities of adventure to your table! If you seek adventure in the 41st century, &lt;em&gt;Warhammer 40,000: Wrath &amp; Glory&lt;/em&gt; will immerse your RPG group in the galaxy’s grimdark battles and heretical nightmares. If your tastes run classic, &lt;em&gt;Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay&lt;/em&gt; puts the entirety of the beloved Old World at your fingertips. And if you want to explore a realm of high fantasy, magitech, and post-apocalyptic horror, &lt;em&gt;Warhammer Age of Sigmar: Soulbound&lt;/em&gt; invites you to forge your group’s destiny in a gods-shattered realm. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Pay what you want for over 20 books, supplements, game aids, and more resources for these three thrilling Warhammer RPG systems, and help support Children's Health Ireland with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7b0173350913ab4a762cdeb2b79b41e4856f21b2.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e95d0cab903e50aa2bd765cfecd48f8e" length="120144" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming MEGA Bundle 2023 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/programming-mega-bundle-2023-packt-books</link>
      <description>Your practical all-purpose programming library</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn principles, best practices, and advanced concepts for myriad programming disciplines with this massive bundle from Packt. This 30-book library covers a wide range of topics today’s coders and tech professionals need to know, including cloud computing, systems engineering, quantum machine learning, and more. It also includes development resources for popular platforms and languages like Java, Go, Delphi, and more. Level up your programming knowledge, and help support Child’s Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/28422fb8226c8da694837145c660eab65bb85f49.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=54067ed57a81d6b50daff84c4c6b5ca9" length="79593" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creepy Comics Collection by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/creepy-comics-collection-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>A seminal collection of horror tales</description>
      <content:encoded>Ring in the season of fright with this massive collection of terrifying tales from Dark Horse! Within this monstrous bundle you’ll find the entire 145-issue run of the seminal horror comics magazine &lt;em&gt;Creepy&lt;/em&gt;, established in 1964, collected here in 29 chilling &lt;em&gt;Creepy Archives&lt;/em&gt; volumes. Featuring the work of revered creators like Gray Morrow, Frank Frazetta, Alex Toth, and Steve Ditko, this collection will take you on a twisted journey through an unforgettable era of horror storytelling. Also included is a collection of volumes from Dark Horse’s new &lt;em&gt;Creepy&lt;/em&gt; magazine, featuring horrific tales from names like Ray Fawkes, Michael Woods, and others. Get all this and more, and help support the Hero Initiative with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0f6a82e12a225c9f5b6730374f00a8c6e8edf795.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=492dd6048d140d1c989d12dd1c4f1f2a" length="144958" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookbooks and Cocktails by Chronicle Books</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cookbooks-cocktails-chronicle-books</link>
      <description>Cuisines and cocktails from far and wide</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover tastes you’ll want to return to again and again in this collection of cookbooks and cocktail guides from Chronicle Books! Step into the kitchens of celebrity chefs with Snoop Dogg’s &lt;em&gt;From Crook to Cook&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Top Chef&lt;/em&gt; winner Kelsey Barnard Clark’s &lt;em&gt;Southern Grit&lt;/em&gt;. Make simple, delicious Indian meals with &lt;em&gt;6 Spices, 60 Dishes&lt;/em&gt;. Explore recipes and stories sourced from the renowned San Francisco incubator kitchen La Cocina. Complement your meals with mixed spirits, craft beers, and more—and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f089e0204fead7e2b30c0e867ccc0deb0e69b921.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c67cdc9c81931d3fd91fe6abca1d46c9" length="74220" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Design and Development from Smashing Magazine</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/web-design-and-development-from-smashing-magazine-books</link>
      <description>Build your web design and dev skills</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn everything you need to start creating well-designed and well-built websites with this bundle of ebooks from Smashing Magazine! For over a decade, the experts at Smashing have been helping designers and developers learn about design trends and advanced coding techniques. Whether you’re interested in smart design patterns, mobile interfaces, privacy, image optimization, or ethical and inclusive design, you’ll find something in this bundle for you. Build your web skills, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ee9b150f6f7245a0967e01e2a849526a0d4fdfa7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a6121e5652f49afe8485c0b0924fe62e" length="54373" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire: The Masquerade Month of Darkness by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/vampire-masquerade-month-darkness-renegade-game-studios-books</link>
      <description>Enter the World of Darkness</description>
      <content:encoded>Take your first step into the eternal night of &lt;em&gt;Vampire: The Masquerade&lt;/em&gt; with this bundle of digital RPG rulebooks &amp; supplements—plus the physical &lt;em&gt;Rivals&lt;/em&gt; card game! Get everything you need to start running RPGs in the storied World of Darkness, including digital rulebooks for both &lt;em&gt;Vampire: The Masquerade&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Hunter: The Reckoning&lt;/em&gt;, a host of sourcebooks covering the setting’s darkest mysteries, and a selection of adventures to get your campaign up and running. &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ef9741;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Note: Due to limited quantities, the $40 physical tier is no longer available.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/dc2a57e4b28e603888b4c4ae44018d59faafe404.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2eb33822d0274a9838be5ab30e454f14" length="71886" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
