<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:10:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 09:10:31 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity 2023 by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-2023-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Tips &amp; tricks from white hat hackers</description>
      <content:encoded>Take your OpSec into your own hands with this bundle of books on cybersecurity from Wiley. In addition to comprehensive how-tos covering a variety of topics in the security space, you’ll get thrilling real-world accounts from renowned figures in the hacking world. In &lt;em&gt;How I Rob Banks: And Other Such Places&lt;/em&gt;, ethical hacker FC shares his adventures in testing the limits of physical bank security without breaking any laws. &lt;em&gt;Threats: What Every Engineer Should Learn From Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; combines the excitement of the galaxy far, far away with the author’s unique perspective on security threats and secure system development. Pay what you want for these and more–a total of 18 books–and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0fdfd93aec60520d885c806d21467f095b36adac.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=670279d6d023ac832d786cbe85553615" length="28370" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Start Drawing with Walter Foster</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/how-to-start-drawing-with-walter-foster-books</link>
      <description>Capture the world in your sketchbook</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to capture the world around you and let your creativity bloom with this collection of books on drawing and painting! Whether you’re a budding talent or a seasoned artist looking to dabble in a new medium, &lt;em&gt;100 Things Every Artist Should Know&lt;/em&gt; will inspire you fresh perspectives. &lt;em&gt;Urban Sketching Handbook Sketch Now, Think Later&lt;/em&gt; will get you out in the world and examining your surroundings with new eyes. With &lt;em&gt;Draw Every Little Thing&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll discover the potential for artistic growth in the mundane objects all around you. Get all these and more–over 35 books in all–and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/e2f44044431de0c00fc7f8ded97d04d00eb10189.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d35d201db24509abb6dc7ff2a4275249" length="81764" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Steven Universe, Adventure Time, and Many More!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/art-steven-universe-adventure-time-and-many-more-books</link>
      <description>A treasury of fantastic, fantastical art</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore the awesome visual artistry of your favorite shows and films with this collection of digital books from Abrams! Get a vibrant look at the colorful cartoon universe of the Crystal Gems in &lt;em&gt;Steven Universe: Art &amp; Origins&lt;/em&gt;. Learn more about the land of Ooo and its inhabitants in the playful &lt;em&gt;Adventure Time Encyclopaedia&lt;/em&gt;. Feast your eyes on the unmistakable images of Wes Anderson, the iconic fantasy art of Samwise, and more—and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0cbd1f68f0d24d67cf9e75883e1c1b6a5377c94c.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d2da079f5227be2a5fd4042321b34a41" length="45722" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruby on Rails by Pragmatic Programmer</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ruby-rails-pragmatic-programmer-books</link>
      <description>Learn development with Ruby &amp; Rails</description>
      <content:encoded>Want to write powerful, easy-to-maintain code with the Ruby programming language? Looking to create great web apps quickly with Rails? This bundle of books from the experts at Pragmatic Programmers will get you on track! Explore topics like metaprogramming, optimization, testing, sustainable development, and much more, and help support Active Minds with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/e118795fcf28b4c9c64f58bb8c2eae7e27373fbb.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ca94f6cf4cbb3979955730798792b76c" length="42172" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5th Edition Mega Bundle: Gygax + Kobold and Friends + More!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/5th-edition-mega-bundle-gygax-kobold-and-friends-more-books</link>
      <description>Elevate your 5e game</description>
      <content:encoded>Searching for ways to spice up your 5e game? Look no further than this bundle, packed with a treasure hoard of 5e-compatible sourcebooks, adventures, and indispensable game aids from some of the finest publishers in the game! Sic some new threats on your seen-it-all players with the &lt;em&gt;Tome of Beasts 3&lt;/em&gt;. Send them a journey they’ll never forget with &lt;em&gt;Necropolis&lt;/em&gt;, a grand adventure based on the work of none other than Gary Gygax, the Father of RPGs! Broaden their horizons with a smorgasbord of new player options with the &lt;em&gt;Tome of Heroes&lt;/em&gt;. Pay what you want for this vast library of over 70 books—valued at more than $1,000—and help support International Medical Corps!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4e7bce0aed044b38237943a1f94e0c622c0a7c36.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f50a239ed39855b65bcb542f8f39a8f2" length="57666" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oni Press Great Graphic Novel Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/oni-press-great-graphic-novel-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Scott Pilgrim, Courtney Crumrin, and more</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover awesome stories and unforgettable characters in this bundle of acclaimed graphic novels from Oni Press! Catch up with &lt;em&gt;Scott Pilgrim&lt;/em&gt; as he battles bands and evil ex-boyfriends in Bryan Lee O’Malley’s renowned series. Crawl under the covers with a creepy collection of Ted Naifeh’s &lt;em&gt;Courtney Crumrin&lt;/em&gt; tales. Get caught up in &lt;em&gt;The Tea Dragon Society&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Bad Machinery&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support BINC and The Hero Initiative with your purchase. </content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/8574bb3b1ebacc9547f8fdf4286605626d26c8b7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3f4d40cdc0b1ff457b6b88e2fd1594df" length="142899" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microservices by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/microservices-packt-books</link>
      <description>Integrate, deploy, and scale seamlessly</description>
      <content:encoded>Elevate your command of microservices and learn to craft scalable, modular, and resilient applications with some of the most prevalent and powerful tools available! This bundle from the leaders at Packt is full of books that’ll get you up to speed on building and maintaining microservice applications with a variety of frameworks. You’ll learn to craft cloud-native microservices with Spring, how to leverage your Python skills to create performant applications with FastAPI, keep your services communicating efficiently with gRPC, and much more! Pay what you want for 16 books that’ll help you master these in-demand skills and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c901772eb1ac4851e149e48d7b6c4c7d06d8b878.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=cd90b5f1eb47ebb791109306ceb7a91b" length="86048" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Age and Mass Effect Comics by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dragon-age-and-mass-effect-comics-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Explore worlds of Mass Effect &amp; Dragon Age comics</description>
      <content:encoded>The masterfully realized universes of famed game maker BioWare come alive on the page in this collection of &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age&lt;/em&gt; comics from Dark Horse! Get into Commander Shepard’s offscreen adventures in &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect Volume 1: Redemption&lt;/em&gt;, which takes place after the events of the revered &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect 2&lt;/em&gt;. Prime yourself for high adventure with &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age: The Missing&lt;/em&gt;, the comic story that leads into &lt;em&gt;Dreadwolf&lt;/em&gt;, the upcoming fourth installment in the beloved RPG series. Get more than 15 exciting &lt;em&gt;Mass Effect&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dragon Age&lt;/em&gt; volumes in this bundle, and support Child’s Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/10336583fd715a21b1be9aa3385175d1aa126225.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8436da0235c577e6901be93e62e5ed1f" length="123459" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rick and Morty Comic Collection by Oni Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/rick-and-morty-comic-collection-oni-press-books</link>
      <description>Time-traveling, multiverse-hopping comic adventures</description>
      <content:encoded>Join the universe’s most notorious superscientist Rick Sanchez and his hapless grandson Morty on adventures across time and space—and beyond all reason—in this bundle of &lt;em&gt;Rick and Morty&lt;/em&gt; comics from Oni Press! Based on the hit [adult swim] animated series, this collection features 60 issues from the acclaimed original run, taking readers from dimension C-132 to C-137 and a host of alternate realities in between. Lose yourself in the &lt;em&gt;Rick &amp; Morty&lt;/em&gt; comics multiverse, and help support  BINC and The Hero Initiative with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/67e9ecd07a1e8a015b40c29d9551d0a834da4624.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=cbb2c9500bc7792cb5761ba94f9976d5" length="105985" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who Megabundle 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/doctor-who-megabundle-2023-books</link>
      <description>A TARDIS full of audio dramas, comic collections, and role-playing</description>
      <content:encoded>The wonders of the Whoniverse are at your fingertips with this massive bundle of Doctor Who comic collections, tabletop role-playing games, and audio dramas! Take your gaming group on a trip to Gallifrey and beyond with the &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who Roleplaying Game Rulebook&lt;/em&gt; and a TARDIS-full of adventures and supplements. Travel to the swinging 60s with two different incarnations of the Doctor in the comic collection &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who: A Tale of Two Time Lords&lt;/em&gt;. Return to one of the most captivating settings from the TV show in the audio drama anthology &lt;em&gt;Tales from New Earth&lt;/em&gt;. Get all this and more than 30 other Whovian treats, and help BBC Children in Need with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/668832e9f84cb36ab604c36f7debe1fb47a88174.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=301bc9e6e809ec66a2639cc4b45d33c7" length="106614" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ready for NaNoWriMo 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/get-ready-for-nanowrimo-2023-books</link>
      <description>NaNoWriMo inspiration, tools, and advice</description>
      <content:encoded>Getting creative for National Novel Writing Month this year? Discover inspiration. advice, and tools to help achieve your goals in our NaNoWriMo 2023 bundle! Get guides to building compelling science fiction and fantasy worlds. Pick up habits to keep you focused and help break blocks. Learn how to effectively outline, structure your plot, or craft a screenplay. Plus, unlock timely access to the creative writing software tools Novlr and Plottr, along with courses from Writing Mastery Academy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Your purchase helps support National Novel Writing Month, the nonprofit organization behind the movement, helping provide the structure, community, and encouragement to help people find their voices, achieve creative goals, and build new worlds—on and off the page.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c7e248b6694abe12ac03d73c214fddc0b4f60b55.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=4fe74b1a9481d66e30ea7f8dc3a3e1b6" length="68405" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
