<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:10:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:10:36 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tabletop RPG Resources by Dicegeeks Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/tabletop-rpg-resources-dicegeeks-holiday-encore-books</link>
      <description>Let the dice decide!</description>
      <content:encoded>Back for a Very Humble Holiday encore…Embrace the will of the dice gods with this bundle of gamemaster resources from Dicegeeks, designed to help you improvise fun and imaginative scenarios at the table! You’ll get more than 30 books to help quickly randomly generate content for your tabletop RPGs, including the &lt;em&gt;The Great Book of Random Tables&lt;/em&gt; and a vast library of spin-offs, &lt;em&gt;The No-Prep Gamemaster&lt;/em&gt; full of practical advice for running spontaneous RPG sessions, and more. Help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quantities for our Very Humble Holiday encore bundles are highly limited, and this bundle will no longer be available for purchase after supplies run out.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; If you purchase the bundle, please be aware that keys may not be immediately available for certain items; we appreciate your patience while we work to restock them.&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c7879b211b41ce27606f208d330181d01a969510.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=6c6b9e63ea229cb562ad2a44bc5bb0e0" length="78030" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Development by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-development-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Harness new ideas in software development</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn all about the latest methodologies and technologies that are reshaping the world of software development with this book bundle from Pearson. In the &lt;em&gt;Async-First Playbook&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll glean invaluable insights on remote-native, asynchronous work styles to prime your globe-spanning teams for success. &lt;em&gt;Serverless as a Game Changer&lt;/em&gt; will teach you how to evolve your tech stack to	deliver software faster, better, and at lower cost, backed up by real-world case studies. The latest edition of &lt;em&gt;Software Architecture in Practice&lt;/em&gt; provides guidance on how to design, instantiate, analyze, manage, and evolve complex software projects, using the latest strategies and tech, like DevOps and quantum computing. Get all these books and more, and help support Women Who Code with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/303b81d81667f6b3a9f1b506542f95b644b7fd72.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2d069747ee372c718bb91ed752e705a7" length="35376" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cthulhu Casebooks of Sherlock Holmes</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cthulhu-casebooks-sherlock-holmes-books</link>
      <description>It’s elementary, Mr. Yog-Sothoth</description>
      <content:encoded>The adventures of the legendary sleuth Sherlock Holmes take a turn for the eldritch in this bundle of audiobooks from Blackstone Audio! You’ll get a host of novels and stories from New York Times best-selling author James Lovergrove featuring the world’s greatest detective, including the celebrated &lt;em&gt;Cthulhu Casebooks&lt;/em&gt; series. &lt;em&gt;Sherlock Holmes and the Shadwell Shadows&lt;/em&gt; invites you to delve into the heart of Victorian London's darkness, where Holmes and Watson confront a sinister force feeding on the city's despair. In &lt;em&gt;Sherlock Holmes and the Miskatonic Monstrosities&lt;/em&gt;,  the duo faces forgotten horrors from a scientist's past. Get all these stories and more, masterfully adapted as audiobooks, and help support FirstBook!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c069f1a550bf33a255a6ced4e9a734b989ca2d39.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e2fdeded03c56d4edd23dec55e21e237" length="77308" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition Legacy Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-legacy-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>Everything you need for Pathfinder 2E</description>
      <content:encoded>Endless adventure awaits your RPG group with this &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition&lt;/em&gt; bundle from Paizo! Included are the &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition Core Rulebook&lt;/em&gt; and digital &lt;em&gt;Beginner’s Box&lt;/em&gt;, as well as a bounty of sourcebooks, supplements, and adventure modules to keep your table busy for multiple campaigns’ worth of play. You’ll get three volumes of the &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder Bestiary&lt;/em&gt; to keep the challenges fresh, numerous adventures like the beloved &lt;em&gt;Crown of the Kobold King&lt;/em&gt;, and much more! Pay what you want for a lifetime of fuel for your RPG sessions and help support Comic Books for Kids with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/806612c23f6b64cca4e1604090183cb6d1bc9c9d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f2b6badace615885f0c7ec8a81d717e3" length="109089" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning, AI, and Bots by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-ai-and-bots-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>All about artificial intelligence</description>
      <content:encoded>Delve deep into the realms of machine learning, AI, and bots with this bundle of books from O’Reilly! Inside this 14-book library, you’ll get expert insights on the tools and technology behind these cutting-edge fields. Learn about coding in Python or TensorFlow. Dig into designing deep learning systems. Level up your skills &amp; knowledge whether you’re a novice or a seasoned prof, and help support Code for America with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/694e8b932100cc4fbc92cc46b1a9ac1ff23cdcaf.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ef51cc515e462f31190cd627001d8bc2" length="95330" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directors, Filmmaking, and Hollywood Movies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/directors-filmmaking-and-hollywood-movies-books</link>
      <description>Books on film</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore the work of the world’s most celebrated movies and moviemakers with this library of books! This 25-book collection puts the spotlight on visionary creators like Wes Anderson, Tim Burton, Bong Joon-ho, and Quentin Tarantino; delves into popular genres and Hollywood myths; and much more. Get lost in a library curated for cinephiles everywhere, and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2699841dd05864a4a5de7a07d8d931227be1ac64.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=578e63b3e084c60e533a61502b8f388d" length="137253" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mignola's Hellboy by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mike-mignolas-hellboy-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>A modern (and hellish) comics classic</description>
      <content:encoded>Follow &lt;em&gt;Hellboy&lt;/em&gt;, the beloved sardonic antihero, into the vilest infernal depths and beyond in this jam-packed bundle of comics from Dark Horse! Witness the occult madness that brought the Right Hand of Doom to our world in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy Volume 1: Seeds of Destruction&lt;/em&gt;. Go to the very depths of Hell alongside him in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy in Hell Volume 1: The Descent&lt;/em&gt;. Feast your eyes on his dark allure in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy: 25 Years of Covers&lt;/em&gt;. And more! Get your hands on over 30 books of &lt;em&gt;Hellboy&lt;/em&gt; and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9f270f1710b4d2992a6df2f19ed1fb3585653f0f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a5533571ee7a373c1721423b97a18a6f" length="56773" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking 2023 by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hacking-2023-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Explore the art &amp; science of hacking</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to think like a hacker with this bundle of books from No Starch Press! Inside this 18-book library, you’ll get expert insights on how to be an ethical hacker, the ins and outs of cybersecurity, how malicious actors engage in social engineering, and a lot more. Learn to defend systems, anticipate attacks, and more—and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/38b110f4b2ec62fba59357883ecd52e845cd41ed.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=b518720893642370847da7bddead7616" length="103670" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Solo RPG Library by Parts Per Million</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/solo-rpg-library-parts-per-million-books</link>
      <description>Adventure for a party of one</description>
      <content:encoded>Looking to take an RPG ruleset for a spin, but can’t manage to convince your friends to try a new system? This bundle of solo adventure modules by the specialists at Parts Per Million is exactly what you’ve been looking for! Included in the bundle are dozens of adventures written specifically for a variety of RPGs, from well-known indies like &lt;em&gt;Blades in the Dark&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dungeon Crawl Classics&lt;/em&gt;, to cult favorites like &lt;em&gt;Stars Without Number&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Lancer&lt;/em&gt;. And if your tastes run to the old school, you’ll also find plenty of solo adventures tailored for good old fashioned OSR-style play. Pay what you want for this bundle of endless adventure, and help support buildOn with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d619f174f1b64115ff260ff154b5af4819570b93.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0f0039d791488a5dd4bb2fdf6af0bd07" length="109310" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The John Scalzi Collection: Old Man's War, The Interdependency, and More, by Tor</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/john-scalzis-interdependency-old-mans-war-and-more-tor-books</link>
      <description>Discover the worlds of John Scalzi</description>
      <content:encoded>Immerse yourself in the rich sci-fi worlds of multiple Hugo Award–winning author John Scalzi! Explore themes of life extension, mortality, and humanity amidst the backdrop of alien war in the groundbreaking &lt;em&gt;Old Man's War&lt;/em&gt; series, from first novel to its thrilling conclusion in &lt;em&gt;The End of All Things&lt;/em&gt;. Also included are the mind-bending &lt;em&gt;Lock In&lt;/em&gt; series, the sprawling &lt;em&gt;Interdependency&lt;/em&gt; series, and beloved standalone novels like &lt;em&gt;Redshirts&lt;/em&gt;—and much more! Pay what you want for this library of stellar sci-fi from one of the contemporary masters, and help support the work of First Book with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a38738c8abf338d94ec3a6804956d701d2e397ae.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3e74fdf06f21f7cf28f90b8fa861f165" length="97382" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5th Edition Mega Bundle: Gygax + Kobold and Friends + More!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/5th-edition-mega-bundle-gygax-kobold-and-friends-more-books</link>
      <description>Elevate your 5e game</description>
      <content:encoded>Searching for ways to spice up your 5e game? Look no further than this bundle, packed with a treasure hoard of 5e-compatible sourcebooks, adventures, and indispensable game aids from some of the finest publishers in the game! Sic some new threats on your seen-it-all players with the &lt;em&gt;Tome of Beasts 3&lt;/em&gt;. Send them a journey they’ll never forget with &lt;em&gt;Necropolis&lt;/em&gt;, a grand adventure based on the work of none other than Gary Gygax, the Father of RPGs! Broaden their horizons with a smorgasbord of new player options with the &lt;em&gt;Tome of Heroes&lt;/em&gt;. Pay what you want for this vast library of over 70 books—valued at more than $1,000—and help support International Medical Corps!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4e7bce0aed044b38237943a1f94e0c622c0a7c36.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f50a239ed39855b65bcb542f8f39a8f2" length="57666" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
