<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 08:09:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:09:59 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Become an Access and Excel Expert by Mercury Learning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/become-an-access-and-excel-expert-mercury-learning-books</link>
      <description>Become a spreadsheet and database master</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to capture, organize, and leverage the data that drives your business or workplace with this book bundle focused on advanced topics in Microsoft Access and Excel. Master the tasks related to the creation, use, and management of Access databases. Unlock the secrets of Excel with techniques like task automation and advanced shortcuts, and learn how to harness its potential for data analytics. You’ll also get books on in-demand skills like data mining, programming languages like SQL, R, and Python, plus much more! Pay what you want for this career-boosting bundle and help support charities like Code.org and Whale and Dolphin Conservation.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1a6cc37f29f3ed6b253e35ebe458e45c8bb631e4.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f4f2fa1a8ac29896535029da011be406" length="90133" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 Cinematic Adventure RPGs by Evil Genius Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/2023-cinematic-adventure-rpgs-evil-genius-games-books</link>
      <description>Bring the movies to your game table</description>
      <content:encoded>Don’t forget to pack the popcorn for your next RPG night, because it’s time to bring the movies to your table! This bundle from Evil Genius is packed with games inspired by some of the silver screen's most exciting names. Get ready to walk in the shoes of elite special forces fighters and take on larger-than-life missions in &lt;em&gt;Rambo&lt;/em&gt;, based on the beloved films and fully compatible with 5e! Hop into your Jaeger and protect mankind from vicious kaiju in the 5e-compatible &lt;em&gt;Pacific Rim&lt;/em&gt;! And more! Get games based on &lt;em&gt;The Crow&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Kong Island&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Highlander&lt;/em&gt;, and other great films, and help support Gameheads with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/53f3c4c963f1541e520fd3e6d0263fd103a979c2.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=709b9725922acb2d414580d9cc13e8e0" length="101703" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Easy Cooking by Callisto Publishing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fast-and-easy-cooking-callisto-publishing-books</link>
      <description>Fast, east, and tasty meals</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re looking for fast and easy recipes to simplify your meal prep or need inspiration to mix up your weeknight menu, this bundle of cookbooks from Callisto is here to assist! Turn to the &lt;em&gt;30-Minute Mediterranean Diet Cookbook&lt;/em&gt; for quick, delicious, and healthy home-cooked meals you can throw together in a flash. &lt;em&gt;5-Ingredient Cooking for Two&lt;/em&gt; offers recipes for 100 delicious two-person meals as well as a wealth of tips for shopping, meal planning, and preparation. &lt;em&gt;Easy Charcuterie Boards&lt;/em&gt; will help you dazzle your guests with amazing spreads, including tips on pairing and presenting ingredients. Pay what you want for 30 books that’ll make meal prep a pleasure and help support the International Medical Corps with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/5d56ebb6c7461f5ecd2be3f54f01a2103e414eab.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0cb18cfece85e380b687450549496100" length="73321" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a Linux Master by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/become-linux-master-packt-books</link>
      <description>Get comfortable with the command line</description>
      <content:encoded>If you’re looking to advance your career in IT, security, and other thriving fields, a strong grasp of Linux is non-negotiable—this book bundle from Packt is here to help! Get a handle of the basics with &lt;em&gt;Linux for System Administrators&lt;/em&gt;, which provides a primer for aspiring pros, as well as skill-boosts for helpdesk staff, support engineers, and others. &lt;em&gt;The Linux DevOps Handbook&lt;/em&gt; will arm you with knowledge of essential tools like Docker and Git and upgrade your skills in command line and shell scripting. &lt;em&gt;Mastering Linux Security and Hardening&lt;/em&gt; will equip sysadmins with the knowledge to prevent and detect malware infections, detect unauthorized network access, and more! Pay what you want for more than 20 books to help you achieve Linux mastery and support charity:water with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9bebef656b7ee7c97bc4260322ff7871b6fe75e1.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=20a9fbb503c21a3dd3bea5a9788af2cc" length="75489" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Square Enix Manga Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/square-enix-manga-collection-books</link>
      <description>A manga mosaic of friendship, love &amp; life</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover tales of friendship, love, and the simple pleasures of life with this collection of manga from Square Enix. Witness the power of unexpected friendship in the heartwarming slice-of-life series &lt;em&gt;My Clueless First Friend&lt;/em&gt;. Dive into the world of cosplay with the sweet and spicy rom-com &lt;em&gt;My Dress-Up Darling&lt;/em&gt;. Savor the blend of delicious food and soulful comedy in the delectably touching &lt;em&gt;Beauty and the Feast&lt;/em&gt;. Explore all these series and many more, and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation with your purchase!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/35fc8ba4f8870ac798b5e6f1caceb34036e1e972.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f031f33fe97f6fc0ff02de1f5785e835" length="130992" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel the World by National Geographic</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/travel-world-national-geographic-books</link>
      <description>Travel inspiration from National Geographic</description>
      <content:encoded>Give in to your wanderlust and prepare for a lifetime of unforgettable journeys with this bundle of books from National Geographic. This library of over 20 books is brimming with travel tips covering a variety of locales and topics, as well as the transportive imagery you expect from National Geographic. &lt;em&gt;50 States, 5,000 Ideas&lt;/em&gt; highlights interesting travel experiences in every U.S. state, from the obvious to the unexpected. &lt;em&gt;Destinations of a Lifetime&lt;/em&gt; takes you on a photographic tour around some of the world’s most breathtaking locales, both natural and man-made. In &lt;em&gt;Gordon Ramsay's Uncharted&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll join the legendary chef across some of the world’s most remote locations in search of culinary inspiration and human connection. Get all these books and much more, and help support First Book with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/449c4975d31cb1df32388314800006b09acdd20b.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1869b748f960b2a5c7b846557bb9c167" length="129453" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Development by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-development-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Harness new ideas in software development</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn all about the latest methodologies and technologies that are reshaping the world of software development with this book bundle from Pearson. In the &lt;em&gt;Async-First Playbook&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll glean invaluable insights on remote-native, asynchronous work styles to prime your globe-spanning teams for success. &lt;em&gt;Serverless as a Game Changer&lt;/em&gt; will teach you how to evolve your tech stack to	deliver software faster, better, and at lower cost, backed up by real-world case studies. The latest edition of &lt;em&gt;Software Architecture in Practice&lt;/em&gt; provides guidance on how to design, instantiate, analyze, manage, and evolve complex software projects, using the latest strategies and tech, like DevOps and quantum computing. Get all these books and more, and help support Women Who Code with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/303b81d81667f6b3a9f1b506542f95b644b7fd72.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2d069747ee372c718bb91ed752e705a7" length="35376" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cthulhu Casebooks of Sherlock Holmes</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cthulhu-casebooks-sherlock-holmes-books</link>
      <description>It’s elementary, Mr. Yog-Sothoth</description>
      <content:encoded>The adventures of the legendary sleuth Sherlock Holmes take a turn for the eldritch in this bundle of audiobooks from Blackstone Audio! You’ll get a host of novels and stories from New York Times best-selling author James Lovergrove featuring the world’s greatest detective, including the celebrated &lt;em&gt;Cthulhu Casebooks&lt;/em&gt; series. &lt;em&gt;Sherlock Holmes and the Shadwell Shadows&lt;/em&gt; invites you to delve into the heart of Victorian London's darkness, where Holmes and Watson confront a sinister force feeding on the city's despair. In &lt;em&gt;Sherlock Holmes and the Miskatonic Monstrosities&lt;/em&gt;,  the duo faces forgotten horrors from a scientist's past. Get all these stories and more, masterfully adapted as audiobooks, and help support FirstBook!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c069f1a550bf33a255a6ced4e9a734b989ca2d39.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e2fdeded03c56d4edd23dec55e21e237" length="77308" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition Legacy Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-legacy-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>Everything you need for Pathfinder 2E</description>
      <content:encoded>Endless adventure awaits your RPG group with this &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition&lt;/em&gt; bundle from Paizo! Included are the &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition Core Rulebook&lt;/em&gt; and digital &lt;em&gt;Beginner’s Box&lt;/em&gt;, as well as a bounty of sourcebooks, supplements, and adventure modules to keep your table busy for multiple campaigns’ worth of play. You’ll get three volumes of the &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder Bestiary&lt;/em&gt; to keep the challenges fresh, numerous adventures like the beloved &lt;em&gt;Crown of the Kobold King&lt;/em&gt;, and much more! Pay what you want for a lifetime of fuel for your RPG sessions and help support Comic Books for Kids with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/806612c23f6b64cca4e1604090183cb6d1bc9c9d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f2b6badace615885f0c7ec8a81d717e3" length="109089" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mignola's Hellboy by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mike-mignolas-hellboy-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>A modern (and hellish) comics classic</description>
      <content:encoded>Follow &lt;em&gt;Hellboy&lt;/em&gt;, the beloved sardonic antihero, into the vilest infernal depths and beyond in this jam-packed bundle of comics from Dark Horse! Witness the occult madness that brought the Right Hand of Doom to our world in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy Volume 1: Seeds of Destruction&lt;/em&gt;. Go to the very depths of Hell alongside him in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy in Hell Volume 1: The Descent&lt;/em&gt;. Feast your eyes on his dark allure in &lt;em&gt;Hellboy: 25 Years of Covers&lt;/em&gt;. And more! Get your hands on over 30 books of &lt;em&gt;Hellboy&lt;/em&gt; and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9f270f1710b4d2992a6df2f19ed1fb3585653f0f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a5533571ee7a373c1721423b97a18a6f" length="56773" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
