<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 08:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:10:46 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Become a Python Expert by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/become-python-expert-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Sage Python advice from the pros</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re a seasoned pro or a budding coder looking to cut your teeth in web dev, data science, or AI engineering, this bundle of Python books from Pearson will bolster your command of this indispensable programming language! &lt;em&gt;Effective Python&lt;/em&gt; will teach you tips and tricks, straight from Google Python guru Brett Slakin, to help you get the most out of your code. Aimed at experienced developers, &lt;em&gt;Deitel: Python for Programmers&lt;/em&gt; provides hands-on exercises focusing on deep learning, big data, and other exciting applications. &lt;em&gt;Learn Python 3 the Hard Way&lt;/em&gt; gives you a rigorous crash course where you’ll create working code regardless of your level. Get all these and more, and help support Npower with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7770c5472abc4b83125f59214a3dac13548debba.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=faca5e782c6f47f569ebeaccd951ade7" length="101945" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowrun Legends by Catalyst Game Labs</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shadowrun-legends-catalyst-game-labs-books</link>
      <description>Elves &amp; cyberdecks, Orks &amp; megacorps</description>
      <content:encoded>Dive deep into a world where sorcery and cybernetics collide with this collection of &lt;em&gt;Shadowrun&lt;/em&gt; novels! Included in this collection of over 20 books are the stories that set the foundation and flesh out the world of this iconic RPG setting. In &lt;em&gt;Never Deal with a Dragon&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll get a thrilling look at the frightening powers that drive &lt;em&gt;Shadowrun&lt;/em&gt;’s megacorps. In &lt;em&gt;2XS&lt;/em&gt;, a deadly cyberdrug is infesting the streets, and its origins point to something ancient and wicked. Get these and more classic novels that defined this beloved cyberpunk fantasy world, and help support the Legal Defense Fund!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7c9affe16c33ee0730f50440c879159611919eba.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0d110915c26a104652bbc2698b4297f5" length="104476" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iconic Sci Fi Audiobooks by Blackstone Audio</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sci-fi-classic-audiobooks-feat-hell-divers-books</link>
      <description>Feast your ears on iconic sci-fi and fantasy</description>
      <content:encoded>In Nicholas Sansbury Smith’s bestselling Hell Divers series, you’ll explore the deadly skies of a blighted, war-ravaged Earth as humanity scavenges to survive. Close your eyes and tune into a selection of iconic sci-fi and fantasy series with this audiobook bundle from Blackstone Publishing! Discover the mysteries of an ancient cosmic artifact of mind-boggling scale in Larry Niven’s Hugo and Nebula award-winning &lt;em&gt;Ringworld&lt;/em&gt; series. In the &lt;em&gt;Runelords&lt;/em&gt; series by David Farland, you’re thrust into a fantasy world where great power can be transferred between beings—often at great cost. Immerse yourself in these beloved series and more—a total of 20 audiobooks—and help First Book’s mission to provide quality education for kids in need.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/43a5f987ca741aa350909606929565507eb2a4d7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=cc6b09ed9005356d561d0f9ef62d1916" length="58390" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Build your software architecture knowledge</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you want to create a solid foundation for a career or expand your existing software architecture skills, this bundle of books from O’Reilly can help you achieve your goals! Explore architectural patterns, component determination, evolutionary architecture, and more. Dig into the facets that distinguish architecture from engineering and other development disciplines. Learn the skills you need to succeed in this in-demand field, and help support Code for America with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/3e20830836740faa73279165e851dcfad5b50066.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3109c162d73b89f2ac23559c6959780f" length="61434" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halo Graphic Novels by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/halo-graphic-novels-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Join Master Chief’s fight</description>
      <content:encoded>Follow the Spartans’ fight against the Covenant, the Flood, the Banished, and other threats to humanity with this graphic novel collection from Dark Horse! Discover tales of legendary Brutes, plasma-scarred battlefields, slip-space travel, and off-the-books genetic engineering in titles like &lt;em&gt;Halo: Rise of Atriox&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Halo: Tales from Slipspace&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Halo: Lone Wolf&lt;/em&gt;—and those are just the tip of the energy sword. Buckle up for a galaxy-spanning bundle of more than a dozen graphic novels perfect for new and old Halo fans alike, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/538bd7b43c7743f457ba59e7b460a381145887ac.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f9fc6d5086a05893f8e61ab6ef7014e8" length="125213" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trail of Cthulhu by Pelgrane Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/trail-cthulhu-pelgrane-press-books</link>
      <description>The Cthulhu Mythos at your table</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore the sublime, horrifying worlds of H.P. Lovecraft at your gaming table with this &lt;em&gt;Trail of Cthulhu&lt;/em&gt; bundle from Pelgrane Press. Utilizing the GUMSHOE RPG system to foreground the investigative elements of the Cthulhu mythos stories, this award-winning RPG delivers an experience that makes clue-finding engrossing and interactive for players, while amplifying the cosmic dread. Get the &lt;em&gt;Trail of Cthulhu&lt;/em&gt; rulebook plus more than 20 other sourcebooks, adventures, and more to fuel uncountable campaigns’ worth of unfathomable eldritch horror, and support Cancer Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/879e6ff49ccaed818c59f599a3c6064060ef6e89.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=bcd2fd0ca7d0a6a09c4da2d441947afa" length="95030" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Programming with C++ &amp; Unreal by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/game-programming-with-c-unreal-packt-books</link>
      <description>Crack the code to game development</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn the secrets of scripting and best practices for programming with this bundle of books from Packt! This game developers’ library focuses on C++ and its coding applications in Unreal Engine and Blueprints visual scripting. Level up your skills through hands-on game dev projects, explore creating characters and animation, and much more, and help support Room to Read with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/33b7338c922472665c720018e1de25c79fafc73d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=dee4a7c9a64e1f5384e51ce644a5dee9" length="84963" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival and Readiness Essentials by Skyhorse Publishing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/survival-and-readiness-essentials-skyhorse-publishing-books</link>
      <description>Self-sufficient living is within reach</description>
      <content:encoded>Take the first steps to a life of self-sufficient abundance with this invaluable collection of books from Skyhorse Publishing. &lt;em&gt;The Homesteading Handbook&lt;/em&gt; features primers on canning, energy production, herbal medicine, and more. &lt;em&gt;Mini Farming&lt;/em&gt; will help you build a sustainable small-scale farm in your backyard, covering topics like seed-saving, sustainable soil fertility practices, and pest management. &lt;em&gt;Basic Fishing&lt;/em&gt; will turn you into an accomplished angler in no time, empowering you with the basics of equipment, bait and tackle, fishing safety, and other critical subjects. Get all these books and many more covering the full spectrum of survival and self-sufficiency, and help support Room to Read with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/65aa8c03b4b0598c822c13e79e3e8495464c93fe.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=595b8b60fb179fd70a16c3f5e043448c" length="108230" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheel of Time and More Dynamite Books!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/wheel-time-and-more-dynamite-books-books</link>
      <description>Legends and myths from across ages</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore worlds of fantasy in this treasury of digital comics—featuring Robert Jordan’s beloved epic &lt;em&gt;The Wheel of Time&lt;/em&gt; and more! Discover the saga of the Dragon Reborn in the adaptations of &lt;em&gt;The Eye of the World&lt;/em&gt; (#1–35) and &lt;em&gt;New Spring&lt;/em&gt; (#1–8). Leap into stories of swords and sorcery from a range of characters and creators in &lt;em&gt;Savage Tales&lt;/em&gt;, featuring Red Sonja, Vampirella, and more. Get &lt;em&gt;Damsels&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Warlords&lt;/em&gt;, and more digital comics &amp; graphic novels from Dynamite!, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase. </content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/669bf83e5177eef23efb29f29150fe0b7a3512b5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c995cce8a4f7fd6f53d6cd7a0e909362" length="90308" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Crawl Classics MEGA Bundle by Goodman Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dungeon-crawl-classics-mega-bundle-goodman-games-books</link>
      <description>Ages of role-playing adventure</description>
      <content:encoded>Get ready to put your players through the meat grinder with this gargantuan collection of modules and supplements for the &lt;em&gt;Dungeon Crawl Classics&lt;/em&gt; RPG system from Goodman Games! This bundle includes 70+ &lt;em&gt;DCC&lt;/em&gt; books, ranging from essential modules like &lt;em&gt;Idylls of the Rat King&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Lost Vault of Tsathzar Rho&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;The Mysterious Tower&lt;/em&gt;, to mammoth supplements like &lt;em&gt;Castle Whiterock&lt;/em&gt;, a veritable campaign-in-a-virtual-box. Pay what you want for enough material to keep your campaign going for ages—valued at over $1,000—and support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/57c1bf2e798c8d767685d217853bf241ed0d8a08.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=16533efa980046812405b8a9ce0c3f2d" length="177020" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
