<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 08:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 09:09:28 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>All I Need to Know I Learned from Star Trek</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/all-i-need-to-know-i-learned-from-star-trek-books</link>
      <description>Go boldly behind the scenes…</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore strange new worlds, seek out new life and civilizations, and deepen your connection with all things Star Trek with this bundle full of galactic wonder! Join the crew of the Federation’s mighty flagship in a mission to prevent all-out war in the Alpha Quadrant in the novel &lt;em&gt;Star Trek Prometheus: Fire With Fire&lt;/em&gt;. Get a behind-the-scenes look at the hit show, including interviews with Sir Patrick Stewart and other Trek luminaries in &lt;em&gt;Star Trek: Picard - The Collector's Edition&lt;/em&gt;. You’ll get 18 books in total, including novels and intimate, behind the scenes coverage of your favorite Star Trek Shows and movies, and your purchase will support the EveryLibrary Institute and The Trevor Project!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/059a5d5678114634780e991c9f875ab58e7937e9.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=b257aee755c488d5681d2faa59c0118e" length="116939" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry Pratchett's Discworld by HarperCollins</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/terry-pratchetts-discworld-harpercollins-books</link>
      <description>Mighty and mundane magic</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover Sir Terry Pratchett's &lt;em&gt;Discworld&lt;/em&gt;, the beloved comic fantasy universe that’s brimming with wit, wisdom, and wonder. Start where it all began in the seminal novel &lt;em&gt;The Color of Magic&lt;/em&gt;, which follows the misadventures of the inept wizard Rincewind as he serves as tour guide to Twoflower, Discworld's first-ever sightseer. The hapless duo’s journeys continue in &lt;em&gt;The Light Fantastic&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Sourcery&lt;/em&gt;, where the scale of world-threatening hazards (and accompanying absurdities) increase exponentially. You’ll get over 35 &lt;em&gt;Discworld&lt;/em&gt; novels in all, touching all corners of this whimsical realm and all manner of its denizens, and you’ll help Room to Read with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This bundle is only available to those in the US.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2efaa22f4a33caf847c8e10d74b4b78e7963a5aa.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2009e1cb2faa32443a9e0a59bbc6ad10" length="97340" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Master 2024 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/python-master-2024-packt-books</link>
      <description>10X your Python skills</description>
      <content:encoded>Deepen your knowledge of one of the world’s most widely used and in-demand programming languages with this bundle of Python books from Packt. &lt;em&gt;Mastering Python&lt;/em&gt; will teach you the advanced skills and techniques necessary to produce clean, readable, and production-ready code. &lt;em&gt;Python Real-World Projects&lt;/em&gt; will walk you through building a project portfolio that will wow potential employers using libraries and resources like Pydantic, JupyterLab, and more. &lt;em&gt;Open Source Projects - Beyond Code&lt;/em&gt; walks you through the steps to open source success, covering licensing, ecosystem management, and other critical dimensions. Pay what you want for over 20 books that’ll take your Python skills to the next level and help support One Tree Planted!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f2eda5fc2fef24a2ad591763c1fc9857817b0f85.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c69cf5b1a1ee7528f11a1aa07043670a" length="109047" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Cthulhu by Chaosium, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/call-cthulhu-chaosium-inc-books</link>
      <description>Invite eldritch terror to your table</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring a taste of terror to your game nights with this bundle from Chaosium, complete with everything you need to run the dreaded (yet beloved) &lt;em&gt;Call of Cthulhu&lt;/em&gt; RPG system! On top of the &lt;em&gt;Call of Cthulhu Starter Set&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll get the &lt;em&gt;Investigator Handbook&lt;/em&gt;, replete with expanded rules for creating player characters, as well as the &lt;em&gt;Keeper Rulebook&lt;/em&gt;, brimming with all the information you need to keep things orderly as your table descends into madness. You’ll also get tons of adventures, including some aimed at first-time game masters, as well as entire campaigns! Pay what you want for over 25 books and game aids for this seminal RPG and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/45ea0735233838d6a510817956b91331ea76d44c.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9d20fb2fdbee0009e2cec4f30d5b97ff" length="79912" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Fit, Lose Weight, and Better Your Mental Health</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/get-fit-lose-weight-and-better-your-mental-health-books</link>
      <description>New year, new you!</description>
      <content:encoded>Get the guidance and inspiration you need to start living your best life in the new year with this bundle of books full of essential knowledge on fitness, mental health, and self-improvement! In &lt;em&gt;Practicing Mindfulness&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll learn evidenced-based methods to deal with distorted thoughts, mental blocks, and other common challenges. &lt;em&gt;Stay Curious and Keep Exploring&lt;/em&gt; features 50 experiments to introduce the wonders of science to you and your family, complete with illustrations and detailed instructions. In the &lt;em&gt;Beginner's Guide to Weight Lifting&lt;/em&gt;,	you’ll explore beginner-friendly exercises with clear step-by-step illustrations to help you safely get stronger and healthier, whether at home or in the gym. And more! Pay what you want for 20+ books that’ll help reshape your health and perspective, and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/43ce20f298f06dcd42d643e190da5457c8302e4b.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7c51591020b7ae094108777e27f32533" length="97572" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT Management by Taylor &amp; Francis</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/it-management-taylor-francis-books</link>
      <description>Success and security in IT management</description>
      <content:encoded>IT pros, start the new year off right with this book bundle, packed with knowledge on a number of critical topics in IT management, security, and more. &lt;em&gt;Big Data for Big Decisions&lt;/em&gt; provides step-by-step methodologies, backed by expert experience, to successfully run a data-driven organization. &lt;em&gt;What To Do When You Get Hacked&lt;/em&gt; maps out in detail everything you need to know to prepare for a data breach. &lt;em&gt;Managing Business Projects: The Essentials&lt;/em&gt; breaks down the essential techniques and perspectives that ensure success for small to medium-sized business projects, covering estimates, scheduling, risk projection, and more. Pay what you want for this wealth of career-boosting knowledge and help support Every Child a Reader with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d523af7c52560d64666a209b5e572477e43b50a4.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c73e9e224775f3a46fddeddd1259e7c1" length="57821" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Palmiotti &amp; Friends Feat. Garth Ennis, Justin Gray &amp; Amanda Conner</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/jimmy-palmiotti-friends-feat-garth-ennis-justin-gray-amanda-conner-books</link>
      <description>Gritty stories from giants of comics</description>
      <content:encoded>Treat yourself to some top-notch storytelling with this bundle of comics, created by some of the most celebrated names in the medium! &lt;em&gt;Random Acts of Violence&lt;/em&gt; is a graphic horror novella too gruesome to be described, brought to you by the twisted minds of writers James Palmiotti and Justin Gray. Dive into &lt;em&gt;The Pro&lt;/em&gt;, a darkly comic sendup of the superhero genre from Garth Ennis, creator of revered titles like &lt;em&gt;Preacher&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Boys&lt;/em&gt;. Also from Ennis, you’ll get &lt;em&gt;Back to Brooklyn&lt;/em&gt;, a brutal, thrilling crime story about two brothers at war in New York’s gritty underworld. All these comics and more—a total of 20 books—and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9ecca22e2c0ce086043ce3304ffdc57e5d8b9de8.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=95d1db7518ff6bcfa41ba3e7786470e8" length="150726" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math and Physics for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-and-physics-for-dummies-books</link>
      <description>Math, physics &amp; more… For Dummies</description>
      <content:encoded>Need some help wrapping your head around complex subjects in math and physics? This bundle of books in the popular &lt;em&gt;For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; series is here to help with fun and approachable lessons across a number of tricky topics! &lt;em&gt;Statistics All-in-One For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; will teach you how to interpret graphs, determine probability, critique data and more! Bone up on the fundamentals and move onto the advanced stuff like graphing functions and approximating area with &lt;em&gt;Calculus For Dummies&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Thermodynamics For Dummies&lt;/em&gt; will help you wrap your head around complex concepts like entropy and the laws of thermodynamics in an easily digestible and approachable manner. Pay what you want for all these and more—a total of 16 books—and help support buildOn with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2ec34f4d0636ab3442fcd04d71bd68996b4937c6.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=17a19b95c81bf8e0c6c3438f0e8bdf86" length="118539" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become an Access and Excel Expert by Mercury Learning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/become-an-access-and-excel-expert-mercury-learning-books</link>
      <description>Become a spreadsheet and database master</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to capture, organize, and leverage the data that drives your business or workplace with this book bundle focused on advanced topics in Microsoft Access and Excel. Master the tasks related to the creation, use, and management of Access databases. Unlock the secrets of Excel with techniques like task automation and advanced shortcuts, and learn how to harness its potential for data analytics. You’ll also get books on in-demand skills like data mining, programming languages like SQL, R, and Python, plus much more! Pay what you want for this career-boosting bundle and help support charities like Code.org and Whale and Dolphin Conservation.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1a6cc37f29f3ed6b253e35ebe458e45c8bb631e4.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f4f2fa1a8ac29896535029da011be406" length="90133" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
