<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 08:08:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:08:53 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cookbooks and Cocktails by Chronicle Books</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cookbooks-cocktails-chronicle-books</link>
      <description>Cuisines and cocktails from far and wide</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover tastes you’ll want to return to again and again in this collection of cookbooks and cocktail guides from Chronicle Books! Step into the kitchens of celebrity chefs with Snoop Dogg’s &lt;em&gt;From Crook to Cook&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Top Chef&lt;/em&gt; winner Kelsey Barnard Clark’s &lt;em&gt;Southern Grit&lt;/em&gt;. Make simple, delicious Indian meals with &lt;em&gt;6 Spices, 60 Dishes&lt;/em&gt;. Explore recipes and stories sourced from the renowned San Francisco incubator kitchen La Cocina. Complement your meals with mixed spirits, craft beers, and more—and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f089e0204fead7e2b30c0e867ccc0deb0e69b921.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c67cdc9c81931d3fd91fe6abca1d46c9" length="74220" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Design and Development from Smashing Magazine</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/web-design-and-development-from-smashing-magazine-books</link>
      <description>Build your web design and dev skills</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn everything you need to start creating well-designed and well-built websites with this bundle of ebooks from Smashing Magazine! For over a decade, the experts at Smashing have been helping designers and developers learn about design trends and advanced coding techniques. Whether you’re interested in smart design patterns, mobile interfaces, privacy, image optimization, or ethical and inclusive design, you’ll find something in this bundle for you. Build your web skills, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ee9b150f6f7245a0967e01e2a849526a0d4fdfa7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a6121e5652f49afe8485c0b0924fe62e" length="54373" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire: The Masquerade Month of Darkness by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/vampire-masquerade-month-darkness-renegade-game-studios-books</link>
      <description>Enter the World of Darkness</description>
      <content:encoded>Take your first step into the eternal night of &lt;em&gt;Vampire: The Masquerade&lt;/em&gt; with this bundle of digital RPG rulebooks &amp; supplements—plus the physical &lt;em&gt;Rivals&lt;/em&gt; card game! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Get everything you need to start running RPGs in the storied World of Darkness, including digital rulebooks for both &lt;em&gt;Vampire: The Masquerade&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Hunter: The Reckoning&lt;/em&gt;, a host of sourcebooks covering the setting’s darkest mysteries, and a selection of adventures to get your campaign up and running.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; When you pay $40 or more, you’ll also get the boxed &lt;em&gt;Vampire: The Masquerade Rivals&lt;em&gt;, a thrilling expandable card game set in the World of Darkness, as well as &lt;em&gt;The Wolf and the Rat&lt;/em&gt; expansion and two bonus promo cards (shipping and handling not included). Succumb to the deadly allure of this legendary RPG setting, and help support charity with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ef9741;"&gt;Note: The $40 physical tier is only available in US/CAN/AUS/NZ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/dc2a57e4b28e603888b4c4ae44018d59faafe404.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2eb33822d0274a9838be5ab30e454f14" length="71886" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books That Will Radically Improve Your Sleep</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/books-that-will-radically-improve-your-sleep-books</link>
      <description>Rest, recharge, and rejuvenate</description>
      <content:encoded>Snooze your way to a healthy body and sound mind with this collection of 20 books covering the topic of sleep in all its dreamy dimensions. &lt;em&gt;The Book of Sleep&lt;/em&gt; provides 75 strategies to alleviate insomnia, based in cognitive behavioral therapy. In &lt;em&gt;The Complete Book of Dreams&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll learn techniques that will allow you to harness the healing potential of your nocturnal journeys. And if the sandman needs a nudge, &lt;em&gt;This Book Will Put You to Sleep&lt;/em&gt; is full of stories written to make your eyelids heavy. Don’t compromise on the immeasurable benefits of sound sleep! Pick up this dream-inducing bundle, and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ba2bf9db80ff44824ac1f1d766f8f4ae7544254d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8568515cb015b034bc4c4008d821b796" length="45083" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization by Taylor &amp; Francis</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-visualization-taylor-francis-books</link>
      <description>Turn raw data into tangible insights</description>
      <content:encoded>Transform your data into visual models that spark new insights for your project or organization with the help of the experts at Taylor &amp; Francis. The library of 20 ebooks explores multiple facets of data visualization. Learn to tell stories with your data, and uncover graphics techniques to aid in analysis. Explore the world of modern input devices, and derive meaning from your data using R visualizations. Translate your data into more human terms, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f6d4ec5e74f7083323c43faae0dcd87b81104f0a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7c38376a54eed82bf94a9faaf888b41e" length="126319" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assassin's Creed Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/assassins-creed-mega-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Take the leap from screen to page</description>
      <content:encoded>Peek into the chronicles of the ages-old battle between the Assassin Brotherhood and the Templar Order in this massive bundle of books and comics set in the &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed&lt;/em&gt; universe! Get a gritty account of the life of the mighty Eivor before the events of the game in the comic series &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed Valhalla: Song of Glory&lt;/em&gt;. Witness the clash between the Brotherhood and Templars in Tang Dynasty–era China in the stunning manga &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed: Dynasty&lt;/em&gt;. Join a crew of young Assassins on a journey that spans early 20th Century Spain and the modern day in the comic &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed: Uprising&lt;/em&gt;. Get all these and more—a total over 20 books and comics—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/e426c85adbb9409a9f009fe8f0ef52bd6afb7193.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=95cce1ce0336b67bab1bd494657229aa" length="130748" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Manga by Saturday AM</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/diverse-manga-saturday-am-books</link>
      <description>Awesome manga from diverse creators</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover your new favorite series with this collection of diverse manga from diverse creators across the globe, in partnership with publisher Saturday AM! In &lt;em&gt;Apple Black&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll meet Sano, a young sorcerer with an epic destiny who must battle sinister temptations. Join &lt;em&gt;Clock Striker&lt;/em&gt;’s aspiring warrior-engineer Cast as she pursues her dreams amidst hidebound tradition and discrimination. Explore the &lt;em&gt;Massively Multiplayer World of Ghosts&lt;/em&gt; alongside Nil, an average kid who must do extraordinary things to survive its mysteries and hazards. Lose yourself in these great manga and more, and support BINC with your purchase</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/152f8f2d1e8e1645f8bbe5706b1070b196ee7d7f.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=74fef6a4eeda1e0a3474d7d03ae53582" length="137750" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Month MEGA Bundle by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-month-mega-bundle-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Unlock a library of cybersecurity knowledge</description>
      <content:encoded>October marks Cybersecurity Awareness Month, and the tech experts at O’Reilly are here to help programmers, engineers, and IT pros keep systems safe all year round. Learn about identity-native access management and intelligence-driven incident response. Wrap your head around the principles of security chaos engineering and security-as-code methodology. Build the know-how you need to create systems that can withstand today’s ever-evolving cybersecurity threats, and help support Code for America with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d040a836d78b4140afaae4d4b975dbda83435c93.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3c263f0ad34833210076dd7dfece3cd4" length="100588" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eerie Comics Collection by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/eerie-comics-collection-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>A groundbreakingly gruesome horror comic library</description>
      <content:encoded>Looking for some macabre reading for the spookiest season of the year? Fix your gaze upon this massive &lt;em&gt;Eerie&lt;/em&gt; archive from Dark Horse, collecting over 130 issues of the long-running horror comics magazine! Featuring terrifying tales and astonishing artwork from legends like Gray Morrow, Frank Frazetta, Alex Toth, Neal Adams, and Joe Orlando, this &lt;em&gt;Eerie&lt;/em&gt; library is for everyone who loves strange and twisted tales of terror, fantasy, and science fiction. Lose yourself in the &lt;em&gt;Eerie Archives&lt;/em&gt;, and help support the Hero Initiative with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1625e695ec6054c8a5ec1cf40ec25d6958ea9ea0.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=85bce213a6db2ea07d65992763ee4c53" length="126627" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
