<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 08:10:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:10:49 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Photoshop, Illustrator, and More for Creatives by Peachpit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/photoshop-illustrator-and-more-for-creatives-peachpit-books</link>
      <description>Master your visual tools</description>
      <content:encoded>Designers and artists, get the most out of tools like Photoshop, Illustrator and more with this bundle, packed with books from leading imprints like Peachpit, Adobe Press, and New Riders. &lt;em&gt;The Adobe Photoshop Book for Digital Photographers&lt;/em&gt; teaches you today’s cutting edge editing techniques step-by-step with zero fluff. &lt;em&gt;Adobe Creative Cloud Classroom in a Book&lt;/em&gt; will teach you the ins and outs of this essential suite covering web, print, video, and more. &lt;em&gt;Photoshop on the iPad&lt;/em&gt; provides expert instruction to help you take your creativity on the go. Get all these and more—20+ books in total—and help support the Hidden Genius Project with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/caaabde76ac27db2a43902fa34283ea068263f10.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ac620eed54ecf7092e15e7308c12a7cb" length="37103" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paranoia 25th Anniversary RPG Mega Bundle by Mongoose Publishing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/paranoia-25th-anniversary-rpg-mega-bundle-mongoose-publishing-books</link>
      <description>Dive into dystopian hilarity</description>
      <content:encoded>Get ready for countless evenings of misadventure and mistrust with the long-running and darkly comic sci-fi TTRPG &lt;em&gt;Paranoia&lt;/em&gt;! This bundle includes everything you need to play this cult classic RPG, packed with over 30 rulebooks, sourcebooks, adventures, and more! The &lt;em&gt;Paranoia Service Pack 1 Core Rulebook&lt;/em&gt; gives you the ground rules for the classic &lt;em&gt;Paranoia&lt;/em&gt; experience—you’re an enforcer serving the Computer that runs this dystopian society, and your job is to eliminate any threats to the status quo (which often includes your fellow players). You’ll also get other core rulebooks that span the scope of this zany world, including the &lt;em&gt;High Programmers Core Rulebooks&lt;/em&gt;, which puts you in the shoes of some of the Computer’s more exalted servants, and the &lt;em&gt;Internal Security Core Rulebook&lt;/em&gt;, where you’ll play as &lt;em&gt;Paranoia&lt;/em&gt; version of special ops. Pay what you want for the ultimate passport to this classic RPG and help support One Tree Planted.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2a8c1939175939fd019a50fc928baf027f408e8a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0964d1eff7cc543106f08e8e6e61aede" length="97614" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be a Graphic Designer &amp; Visual Artist by Chronicle Books</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/be-graphic-designer-visual-artist-chronicle-books-books</link>
      <description>Unleash your visual brilliance</description>
      <content:encoded>Chart your course through the worlds of art and design with this bundle of books, full of indispensable instruction, guidance, and inspiration. The acclaimed &lt;em&gt;How to Be A Graphic Designer Without Losing Your Soul&lt;/em&gt; provides practical advice and philosophical guidance to help you kick off and maintain a successful career in the field. The &lt;em&gt;Creative Business Handbook&lt;/em&gt; gives you concrete, actionable advice about making a living from your creative work. If you want to dive deep in typographic design, &lt;em&gt;Grid Systems&lt;/em&gt; teaches you the ins-and-outs of compositions via extensive examples from top design houses and ad firms. Pay what you want for an invaluable education in art and design and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d479ee442796d3df14e5d9825422522617181295.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2e3b77781ccefd22e9b19ea6f061a4ec" length="87587" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java 2024 by O'Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/java-2024-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>It’s time to learn Java</description>
      <content:encoded>Add one of the most popular programming languages to your coding repertoire with this bundle of books on all things Java from O’Reilly! You’ll get a host of books on this powerful and versatile language, like &lt;em&gt;A Functional Approach to Java&lt;/em&gt;, which will bring you up to speed on the essential concepts and practices of the functional programming paradigm. Also included are books that cover other languages relevant to Java devs, like &lt;em&gt;Java to Kotlin&lt;/em&gt;, which will help you get up and running on the most popular language for native Android apps. Pay what you want for 15 books in total, and help support Code for America with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/3006a326b4beb635fa49652512e0cdc74ef3c658.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=00daade7d37e3ae2020864c584ed91a9" length="72622" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amigurumi and Crochet from Open Road Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/amigurumi-and-crochet-from-open-road-media-books</link>
      <description>Amigurumi + crochet = cute overload.</description>
      <content:encoded>Dive into the charming world of amigurumi and all things crocheting with this captivating collection of books! Included are a host of books designed to guide you through creating your very own cute crocheted companions, including the sumptuously illustrated &lt;em&gt;Edward's Menagerie&lt;/em&gt;, which provides patterns and instructions for 40 adorable animals. With &lt;em&gt;Crochet Iconic Women&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll bring to life some of history’s greats with your hook, from Marie Curie to Billie Holiday. And if you need a primer, the &lt;em&gt;Complete Crochet Course&lt;/em&gt; has you covered for the basics. Pay what you want for this collection of 20+ books and help support Children’s Miracle Network!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/5df466109f251cd2c62320a9d9bb490e92291960.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=fa0de60e0c336e83c42ba3744448a782" length="77569" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spice Up Your Love Life by Chronicle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/spice-up-your-love-life-chronicle-books</link>
      <description>Find fulfillment in love and intimacy</description>
      <content:encoded>Enrich your most intimate relationships in the spirit of Valentine’s Day with this bundle of books full of tips, stories, and candid guidance on the topics of love and intimacy. In &lt;em&gt;My Pleasure&lt;/em&gt;, sexual wellness expert Laura Delarato provides a guide to cultivate an enriching sex life regardless of your relationship status. &lt;em&gt;Me Without You&lt;/em&gt; will help you celebrate enduring love with heartwarming cartoons by famed illustrators Lisa Swerling and Ralph Lazar. Get these and more—over 20 books in total covering a range of topics related to the heart and the bedroom—and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1f4e805eb9ec572112d7bf4a9a92517588619d46.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d0e1394bf89a2a4477c015cbdc015808" length="95156" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity 2024 from Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-2024-from-packt-books</link>
      <description>A full spectrum cybersecurity library</description>
      <content:encoded>Get up-to-date skills that’ll help you keep your systems locked down and hackerproof with this bundle of books on all topics cybersecurity. Looking for a new job in this exciting field? &lt;em&gt;Hack the Cybersecurity Interview&lt;/em&gt; will arm you with the knowledge to nail the technical interview and impress potential employers. &lt;em&gt;Practical Threat Detection Engineering&lt;/em&gt; will teach you how to enhance your organization's security using open source tools via practical examples and hands-on projects. &lt;em&gt;Cryptography Algorithms&lt;/em&gt; explores the cutting edge of modern cryptography, from classical techniques to quantum cryptography and blockchain innovations. Pay what you want for all these and more—over 20 books in total—and help support Special Effect with your purchase. </content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/5029716fb8399d0ea702b88afbbc035b133453af.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7db5114c6de2c64c72e7c23b1d7093e4" length="99875" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romantasy Dramatized Audiobooks Featuring Jeaniene Frost, K.F. Breene, &amp; More!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/romantasy-dramatized-audiobooks-featuring-jeaniene-frost-kfbreene-more-books</link>
      <description>A bundle of sexy supernatural love</description>
      <content:encoded>Tempt your paranormal desires with this bundle of sexy fantasy romance audiobooks, including pitch-perfect adaptations of beloved novels from some of the most revered authors in the genre! In Jeaniene Frost’s &lt;em&gt;Halfway To The Grave&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll join half-vampire Catherine Crawfield on a mission for revenge alongside an irresistible vampire partner whose motives seem &lt;em&gt;mostly pure&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Tempting Danger&lt;/em&gt; by Eileen Wilks stars Lily Yu, a detective investigating a series of murders that have “werewolf” written all over them, which puts her on a collision course with a sexy lycanthrope who appears eager to help. &lt;em&gt;An Easy Death&lt;/em&gt; by Charlaine Harris (of &lt;em&gt;True Blood&lt;/em&gt; fame) takes you to a fractured, alternate history United States where rogue wizards meet hardened gunslingers in an inventive Wild West setting. Pay what you want for this bundle of over 20 audiobooks and help support charity: water with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d43ee88832b8b86d145f16d2328f0b3e262ae2ce.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=38d849724595b45897dc458a45d25b97" length="110009" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberpunk RED 2024 by R. Talsorian Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cyberpunk-red-2024-r-talsorian-games-books</link>
      <description>Tabletop adventures in Night City</description>
      <content:encoded>Calling all solos, netrunners, and rockerboys—it’s time to bring the edgy allure and explosive excitement of the legendary &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk&lt;/em&gt; pen and paper RPG to your table! This bundle is bursting at the seams with all the rulebooks, sourcebooks, and more that you’ll need to play both &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk RED&lt;/em&gt; —the latest edition of the seminal RPG—as well as &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2020&lt;/em&gt;, the classic that started it all. You’ll get over 20 books and game aids for both editions, including the &lt;em&gt;Interface RED Volume 3&lt;/em&gt; sourcebook, packed with new weapons, gear, rules, and more, and &lt;b&gt;available for the first time anywhere as part of this bundle!&lt;/b&gt; Pay what you want for all the tools you need to take Night City by storm, and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/205b191c1d43df756f2d51b49659dfb0e5f0fb58.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=423027e5f9743844c84c7decdfe74304" length="105879" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiant Black &amp; The Massiverse from Image</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/radiant-black-massiverse-from-image-books</link>
      <description>Your ticket to the Massive-Verse</description>
      <content:encoded>Dive into the Massive-Verse, the interconnected comic universe that bridges genres, artistic styles, and even mediums to offer some of the boldest superhero stories out there! This bundle, packed with 15 volumes, will get you up to speed on these essential stories. Start at the beginning with &lt;em&gt;Radiant Black&lt;/em&gt;, which follows a down-on-his-luck 30 year old who discovers immense cosmic power… and its attendant perils. You’ll also get Inferno &lt;em&gt;Radiant Red&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Radiant Pink&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Inferno Girl&lt;/em&gt;, and a ton more series collections and one-shots, serving as the perfect vehicle for immersion into this hot new universe. Pay what you want for this killer bundle and help support charity!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/57d68da998049575189f82aecb4e96441ed8b060.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=aaee9885750b867e2ce8cb42c3475c44" length="103071" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kodansha Award-Winning (&amp; Nominated) Manga</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/kodansha-awardwinning-nominated-manga-books</link>
      <description>Acclaimed manga across the genres</description>
      <content:encoded>Get ready to discover your new favorite manga with this amazing bundle from Kodansha, full of fan-favorite titles that span the genres! In &lt;em&gt;The Drops of God&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll witness the gripping human drama surrounding an inheritance battle over a wine collection worth millions. &lt;em&gt;Nina the Starry Bride&lt;/em&gt; tells the captivating tale of an orphan turned princess navigating royal deceit and unexpected love. In &lt;em&gt;Shangri-la Frontier&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll join a seasoned gamer as he faces formidable foes and mysterious figures in a captivating and deadly virtual world. Pay what you want for this incredible bundle packed with dozens of volumes and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/54d19ecf6487daa0c6ac8d9af0bb226357cd6506.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d1db71372de9ddc326b8fe76870ad1fd" length="93229" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Design and Programming by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/game-design-and-programming-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Game development skills within reach</description>
      <content:encoded>Start your journey into game development today with this bundle of books from Pearson, full of critical instruction for beginners and invaluable skill-up material for seasoned devs! Learn how to create compelling and profitable content for one of the hottest games around in &lt;em&gt;Roblox Game Development in 24 Hours: The Official Roblox Guide&lt;/em&gt;. Bone up on the basics required to truly understand the craft in &lt;em&gt;Fundamentals of Game Design&lt;/em&gt;. Empower yourself with the skills to create your own bespoke art assets with &lt;em&gt;Learning Blender&lt;/em&gt;. Get all these books and more—a value of over $800—and help support Women Who Code with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/293583a36db5d65c0e5de37281651d5ad8f93599.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=256b91ea9820c090f5feaadbfcb8729e" length="95057" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
