<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Books</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Books bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/books" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 08:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 10:09:04 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Wheel of Time and More Dynamite Books!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/wheel-time-and-more-dynamite-books-books</link>
      <description>Legends and myths from across ages</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore worlds of fantasy in this treasury of digital comics—featuring Robert Jordan’s beloved epic &lt;em&gt;The Wheel of Time&lt;/em&gt; and more! Discover the saga of the Dragon Reborn in the adaptations of &lt;em&gt;The Eye of the World&lt;/em&gt; (#1–35) and &lt;em&gt;New Spring&lt;/em&gt; (#1–8). Leap into stories of swords and sorcery from a range of characters and creators in &lt;em&gt;Savage Tales&lt;/em&gt;, featuring Red Sonja, Vampirella, and more. Get &lt;em&gt;Damsels&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Warlords&lt;/em&gt;, and more digital comics &amp; graphic novels from Dynamite!, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase. </content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/669bf83e5177eef23efb29f29150fe0b7a3512b5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c995cce8a4f7fd6f53d6cd7a0e909362" length="90313" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning and AI 2023 by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-and-ai-2023-packt-books</link>
      <description>Guides to cutting-edge AI tech</description>
      <content:encoded>Deepen your understanding of artificial intelligence and machine learning technology with this library of resources from Packt. The 25 ebooks in this bundle provide practical knowledge on working with some of today’s most talked-about technologies, including &lt;em&gt;Machine Learning with R&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Data Augmentation with Python&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Computer Vision on AWS&lt;/em&gt;, and more—ideal for programmers, engineers, data scientists, and anyone interested in expanding your knowledge in this constantly evolving field. Plus, your purchase helps support Direct Relief!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/21f5a0ca59340381063f2cc31ae20c0464daebbf.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=b2f2ec72657eb1164af459dca7bf9483" length="66089" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seanan McGuire: The Urban Fantasy Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/seanan-mcguire-urban-fantasy-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Dive into the worlds of Seanan McGuire</description>
      <content:encoded>Immerse yourself in the intricate and imaginative worlds of renowned urban fantasy author Seanan McGuire, winner of multiple Hugo, Nebula, and Alex Awards! You’ll discover two of the author's most-loved worlds through this carefully curated bundle of over 25 books. The &lt;em&gt;October Daye&lt;/em&gt; series, starting with &lt;em&gt;Rosemary and Rue&lt;/em&gt;, sends you a thrilling journey into fae politics and folklore alongside Toby Daye, a half-fae detective caught between two worlds. Beginning with &lt;em&gt;Discount Armageddon&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;InCryptid&lt;/em&gt; series follows cryptozoologist Verity Price as she navigates the hidden world of legendary creatures—and the dangers posed by those who wish to exploit them. Lose yourself in an immense library of award-winning urban fantasy, and help support The Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/54233d3634a0167e792deb7d7dffed3265ef76ba.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=be76195b498fded902672d9d09cd2c1d" length="98015" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Crawl Classics MEGA Bundle by Goodman Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dungeon-crawl-classics-mega-bundle-goodman-games-books</link>
      <description>Ages of role-playing adventure</description>
      <content:encoded>Get ready to put your players through the meat grinder with this gargantuan collection of modules and supplements for the &lt;em&gt;Dungeon Crawl Classics&lt;/em&gt; RPG system from Goodman Games! This bundle includes 70+ &lt;em&gt;DCC&lt;/em&gt; books, ranging from essential modules like &lt;em&gt;Idylls of the Rat King&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Lost Vault of Tsathzar Rho&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;The Mysterious Tower&lt;/em&gt;, to mammoth supplements like &lt;em&gt;Castle Whiterock&lt;/em&gt;, a veritable campaign-in-a-virtual-box. Pay what you want for enough material to keep your campaign going for ages—valued at over $1,000—and support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/57c1bf2e798c8d767685d217853bf241ed0d8a08.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=16533efa980046812405b8a9ce0c3f2d" length="177020" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Coding 2023 by Apress</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/game-coding-2023-apress-books</link>
      <description>Learn the functions of fun</description>
      <content:encoded>Level up the technical skills you need to create games and lead a successful career in development with this bundle of ebooks from Apress! Deepen your understanding of digital audio, get a handle on 3D graphics, and learn the fundamentals of crafting game mechanics. Familiarize yourself with popular tools and platforms like GameMaker and MonoGame. Build a foundation for a wide range of game programming and development disciplines, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/cdc7ff7efa9f6cc3e3dd2e5830afa1567ec1812a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f57b881c123608cb074a7dceb333919e" length="110543" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Erikson's Malazan Book of the Fallen by TOR Publishing Group</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/steven-eriksons-malazan-book-fallen-tor-publishing-group-books</link>
      <description>Lose yourself in an epic fantasy masterpiece</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover the sweeping saga of gods, mages, mortals, and warring nations in &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;–bestselling author Steven Erikson’s Malazan Book of the Fallen, heralded as one of the most ambitious, complex, and masterful epic fantasy series of all time. This epic ebook bundle features the complete main 10-volume saga (from &lt;em&gt;Gardens of the Moon&lt;/em&gt; to the gripping final volume &lt;em&gt;The Crippled God&lt;/em&gt;), as well as seven additional titles that further explore the history and conflicts of the Malazan Empire. Journey deep into one of fantasy literature’s most celebrated worlds, and help support Covenant House with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4ebc0d66ffcd759403c5e8bbaf98bb9ca30fbda7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=43ec62baaa8ad52c9548afd2b1d152ca" length="92131" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hinamatsuri by One Peace Books</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hinamatsuri-one-peace-books-manga</link>
      <description>Get caught up in the hit manga series</description>
      <content:encoded>Get caught up in the hit manga series.&lt;/strong&gt; Discover the story of yakuza member Nitta and the telekinetic girl who falls onto his head and into his life in Masao Ohtake’s manga series &lt;em&gt;Hinamatsuri&lt;/em&gt;, basis of the hit anime! This bundle collects all 18 digital volumes currently available in English from publisher One Peace Books, making it the perfect way to catch up before the final volume arrives. Get swept up in a saga of time travel, crime syndicates, superpowers, and school days, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a style="color: #ef9741;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The titles in this bundle are available through BOOK☆WALKER. To access the content, create or log in to your BOOK☆WALKER account at&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://global.bookwalker.jp"&gt;https://global.bookwalker.jp&lt;/a&gt;.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/01ce1ea3bbe7a1fea944b7fb50b47ba1040def95.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=83eb0601dec664a1d70f33fdec00883c" length="146306" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Press Exam Ref Certification MEGA Bundle by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/microsoft-press-exam-ref-certification-mega-bundle-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Ace your Microsoft certification exams!</description>
      <content:encoded>Got some looming certification exams you want to knock out of the park? Or are you a developer or IT professional looking to bolster your qualifications? This bundle of exam reference guides from Microsoft Press will give you the edge you need! Included are comprehensive, expertly crafted study materials packed with information pulled straight from Microsoft’s exam curriculum. Whether you’re looking to become certified as a Microsoft Cybersecurity Expert, get credentialed for numerous facets of the Azure cloud platform, or achieve other cert-related goals, these reference guides are your secret weapon. Plus, your purchase supports Women Who Code!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0823b3868eee9aee51cb2e0bd115656a7aaea435.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7f39625d75c512ab0eac07ba38becf5f" length="64636" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tabletop RPG Resources by Dicegeeks</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/tabletop-rpg-resources-dicegeeks-books</link>
      <description>Let the dice decide!</description>
      <content:encoded>Embrace the will of the dice gods with this bundle of gamemaster resources from Dicegeeks, designed to help you improvise fun and imaginative scenarios at the table! You’ll get more than 30 books to help quickly randomly generate content for your tabletop RPGs, including the &lt;em&gt;The Great Book of Random Tables&lt;/em&gt; and a vast library of spin-offs, covering genres from fantasy to cyberpunk, and a multitude of scenarios, like adventure hooks, dungeons, inns and taverns, and more. Also included are titles packed with GMing guidance, like &lt;em&gt;The No-Prep Gamemaster&lt;/em&gt;, full of practical advice for running spontaneous RPG sessions. Pay what you want for this bundle of handy GM tools, and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c7879b211b41ce27606f208d330181d01a969510.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=6c6b9e63ea229cb562ad2a44bc5bb0e0" length="78030" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
