<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 08:08:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 10:08:55 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Laugh Til You Die: Multiplayer Mayhem</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/laugh-til-you-die-multiplayer-mayhem</link>
      <description>An absurdly fun multiplayer collection</description>
      <content:encoded>Gather up your friends and frenemies for some mischief and mayhem with this bundle of wild multiplayer games! Cook up chaos in the 4-player roguelike restaurant game &lt;em&gt;PlateUp!&lt;/em&gt; Race through an obstacle course that you’re building as you go in &lt;em&gt;Ultimate Chicken Horse&lt;/em&gt;. Master dueling skills as the tension mounts in &lt;em&gt;Rounds&lt;/em&gt;. Plot a preposterous party, and help support International Medical Corps &amp; International Rescue Committee with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2175bf081cc41ac068dd05745c33148d649795a7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3ff32600692de2c22a7014a349a289fb" length="104332" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Indies from Humble Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/awesome-indies-from-humble-games</link>
      <description>Tons of good fun from Humble Games</description>
      <content:encoded>Discover awesome games from some of the world’s most creative, visionary independent developers in this eclectic collection of titles published by Humble Games (hey, that’s us)! Meet your maker in the unforgiving world of &lt;em&gt;Moonscars&lt;/em&gt;. Explore a forgotten city and race to save your friends in &lt;em&gt;UNSIGHTED&lt;/em&gt;. Become a champ in the vibrant school sports RPG &lt;em&gt;Dodgeball Academia&lt;/em&gt;, journey into the Deep Woods of &lt;em&gt;The Wild at Heart&lt;/em&gt;, and much more—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/b450f206e10e545bf5b037814144a8886d7a8b7e.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a21c73ba6bc25c0bcc3c239775e6189d" length="123275" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control the Narrative</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/control-narrative</link>
      <description>Make the story yours</description>
      <content:encoded>Bask in the freedom of choice and face the finality of consequence in this bundle of player-driven narrative games! Guide an eclectic ensemble through a series of madcap sci-fi trials and tribulations in &lt;em&gt;New Tales From the Borderlands&lt;/em&gt;. Drive the fates of two characters who share a psychic bond in the critically acclaimed &lt;em&gt;Beyond: Two Souls&lt;/em&gt;. Confront your hometown’s troubled past in &lt;em&gt;Twin Mirror&lt;/em&gt;, get lost in the visual novel-style adventure of &lt;em&gt;Opus: Echoes of Starsong&lt;/em&gt;, and much more—and help support the National Videogame Museum and the charity of your choice!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/b652e89cc7c267f23d4ecc2514440923315f0431.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=79bba98fe582a0e10281458bf49ee33b" length="80248" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeroCraft PC Complete Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/herocraft-complete-collection</link>
      <description>A massive indie gaming treasury</description>
      <content:encoded>Delve into the adventurous, strategic, humorous games of indie publisher HeroCraft PC with this massive new bundle! Rebuild humanity on an ever-changing Earth in the post-apocalyptic 4X strategy game &lt;em&gt;Revival: Recolonization&lt;/em&gt;. Take control of a grim recycling facility in the darkly satirical sim &lt;em&gt;Organs Please&lt;/em&gt;. Take command of a Space Wolves squad on the turn-based, card-based battlefields of &lt;em&gt;Warhammer 40,000: Space Wolf&lt;/em&gt;*. Get &lt;em&gt;Anvil Saga&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Tempest&lt;/em&gt;, and more, and support International Medical Corps with your purchase. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Warhammer 40,000: Space Wolf and associated DLC will no longer be available for purchase after October 12, 2023. Get it while you can!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ae3955ad5aa6cda717625ecdefa3b040b594962a.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=87d7713eb74ac2a58d2a18a18d505d7d" length="116663" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Your Head in the Game VR</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/get-your-head-in-game-vr</link>
      <description>Get in the middle of the action</description>
      <content:encoded>Stay focused and face your foes head-on in this intense new collection of virtual reality games! Annihilate anyone who dares to stand between you and your destiny in the dark fantasy RPG &lt;em&gt;Grimlord&lt;/em&gt;. Search for your lost sister in the sinister survival-horror halls of &lt;em&gt;Propagation: Paradise Hotel&lt;/em&gt;. Escape the super-spy situations of &lt;em&gt;I Expect You to Die 2&lt;/em&gt;, crawl the dungeons of &lt;em&gt;Demeo&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support Direct Relief and International Medical Corps with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/214bbfc93154c9915a53a2b0c235d881c0d3601c.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=722699d2125c17c7455dc9cec444958f" length="89023" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
