<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:10:25 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Take Your Turn: Tactics &amp; RPGs</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/take-your-turn-tactics-rpgs</link>
      <description>Lead. Strategize. Conquer!</description>
      <content:encoded>Use your head, plan your next move, and take command of the battlefield in this bundle of turn-based tactics and role-playing games! Lead powerful Wielders into the unknown lands of &lt;em&gt;Songs of Conquest&lt;/em&gt;. Become a 90s-era sci-fi action hero in the brutal world of &lt;em&gt;Jupiter Hell&lt;/em&gt;. Tame monsters as a freshly minted Battle Researcher in &lt;em&gt;Coromon&lt;/em&gt;. Get &lt;em&gt;Dungeon of Naheulbeuk: The Amulet of Chaos - Deluxe Edition&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Banner Saga Trilogy: Deluxe Pack&lt;/em&gt;, and more, and help support Girls Who Code and Code.org with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7160aca99715797e02226ef8a62ec4c91a543565.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=524edee867f3cecf62fda310f0bbc3f7" length="89289" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resident Evil: Decades of Horror - Village Edition</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/resident-evil-decades-horror-village-edition</link>
      <description>The ultimate survival horror saga</description>
      <content:encoded>From the emergence of the T-Virus to the horrifying secrets of the Village… we've joined forces with Capcom for a &lt;em&gt;Resident Evil&lt;/em&gt; anthology for the ages! This decades-spanning collection of iconic games from the legendary survival-horror series features:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The latest acclaimed main entry in the series, the multiple Game of the Year award-winning &lt;em&gt;Village&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The HD remaster of the original &lt;em&gt;Resident Evil&lt;/em&gt; and acclaimed next-gen remakes of &lt;em&gt;Resident Evil 2&lt;/em&gt; &amp; &lt;em&gt;3&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Classics like &lt;em&gt;Resident Evil 4 (2005)&lt;/em&gt; &amp; &lt;em&gt;5&lt;/em&gt; and more major entries with low system requirements—great for a wide range of PC hardware and laptops.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;em&gt;Bonus deal! Pick up a coupon for 25% off the Resident Evil Village Winters' Expansion, featuring brand-new content and third-person mode.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your purchase of this bundle helps support One Tree Planted and Code.org.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1ecb4be87aea49e10ace7e060402761b049b1cf4.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a218c87810d996ba626c4de787b8d336" length="70832" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackbox Jukebox: Playing the Odds</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/jackbox-jukebox-playing-odds</link>
      <description>Bring Jackbox to the party</description>
      <content:encoded>Invite some rowdy merrymaking and hilarity to your next gathering with this bundle of &lt;em&gt;Jackbox&lt;/em&gt; party game collections for PC! You’ll get &lt;em&gt;Jackbox Party Pack 9&lt;/em&gt;—the latest compilation in the series—plus the rest of the odd-numbered &lt;em&gt;Party Packs&lt;/em&gt;, each brimming with individual games. Duel your friends with witty rejoinders in &lt;em&gt;Quiplash&lt;/em&gt;. Test your high-speed trivia acumen in &lt;em&gt;Quixort&lt;/em&gt;. Put your mastery of pop culture where your mouth is in &lt;em&gt;You Don’t Know Jack: Full Stream&lt;/em&gt;. You’ll also get two standalone party games sure to win over the crowd—all while supporting World Central Kitchen, Girls Who Code, and The Trevor Project with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/5a0f7bb3b0ce9e874b60a385520b49114add7d1a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=fca464021d967b70337187a4725bfd82" length="144546" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Racing Sim Bundle - Victory Lap</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/ultimate-racing-sim-bundle-victory-lap</link>
      <description>Get back in the driver’s seat </description>
      <content:encoded>Our ultra-popular bundle of acclaimed, authentic racing sims returns for a victory lap! Experience the realistic thrill and atmosphere of the VR-supported &lt;em&gt;Assetto Corsa Ultimate Edition&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Assetto Corsa Competizione&lt;/em&gt;. Buckle up for the comprehensive Brazilian motorsports sim &lt;em&gt;Automobilista 2&lt;/em&gt; (VR supported). Get revved up for &lt;em&gt;NASCAR Heat 5 Ultimate Edition&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;rFactor 2&lt;/em&gt;, and more, and help support the charity of your choice!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/6a44e255eed0d82d32d9d971e09993cb794b2c22.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7989c3dedb4dd11d195982b1d8ef2250" length="77756" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuneScape: Paths to Adventure - The Return</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/runescape-paths-to-adventure-the-return-bundle</link>
      <description>Equip yourself for your RuneScape journey</description>
      <content:encoded>Gear up for adventure in the legendary high-fantasy open world MMORPG RuneScape! Our epic, popular bundle returns with a 1-month membership granting access to additional content and features, along with a treasure vault full of Keys, Umbral Chests, RuneCoins, cosmetics, and more to enhance your journey. Explore the land of Gielinor and get ready for the upcoming &lt;em&gt;Necromancy&lt;/em&gt; update on August 7, and help support Gameheads and Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund with your purchase! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;em&gt;Buyers who already own cosmetic items will not receive duplicates.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Restrictions:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bundle purchase grants single key that will redeem all items on one Runescape account. Limit one key redemption per account.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ironman restrictions apply to this bundle. Ironman accounts are ineligible to redeem this bundle. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;Accounts with an active RuneScape Mobile Subscription will not be able to redeem this code for membership or the items. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Accounts with two and a half years or more of membership stacked will not be able to redeem.&lt;/i&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ec4acf838b7e0b5f4d1beab214ff5d727c7ebc4d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ab4b234ee50f481b99b1f73e60370268" length="69117" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPG Legends: Baldur's Gate &amp; Beyond</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/rpg-legends-baldurs-gate-beyond</link>
      <description>Mythic adventures and modern classics</description>
      <content:encoded>Lose yourself in some of the most immersive, beloved, legendary PC role-playing experiences of all time—and get Lose yourself in some of the most immersive, beloved, legendary PC role-playing experiences of all time! Rediscover a genre-defining saga in the Enhanced Editions of &lt;em&gt;Baldur’s Gate&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Baldur’s Gate II&lt;/em&gt; from Beamdog. Embark on an epic journey in 2021’s acclaimed &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous&lt;/em&gt;. Return to the Forgotten Realms in &lt;em&gt;Neverwinter Nights: Complete Adventures&lt;/em&gt; and more, and help support Active Minds with your purchase! &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Active Minds is grateful for Humble Bundle's support of our organization's important mental health mission. Active Minds was not involved in the selection of the books in this promotion and does not necessarily endorse those books or agree with the advice or ideas expressed in them.&lt;/em&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/b9535024ac6ae78f2b3e956022b3bf5eb18dd5e5.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f838df0708b79f2dfae6c9dd60f0116b" length="88741" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
