<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:10:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:10:49 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Exceptional Indie Allies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/exceptional-indie-allies</link>
      <description>Honor Black history with indie hits</description>
      <content:encoded>Celebrate Black History Month with this bundle of critically acclaimed and award-winning indie games, in support of NPower’s mission to create pathways for prosperity for veterans and young adults from underserved communities. You’ll get &lt;em&gt;Endling - Extinction is Forever&lt;/em&gt;, where you take on the role of the last mother fox on Earth who must make sure that her pups thrive and survive in a hostile world. In the resonant point &amp; click adventure &lt;em&gt;Norco&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll explore a surreal and intimate rendition of Southern Louisiana in search of answers to a multigenerational mystery. &lt;em&gt;Wytchwood&lt;/em&gt; invites you to a dark fairytale world where you’ll concoct witchy brews, battle wits with monsters, and pass judgment on the unvirtuous. Pay what you want for these and more—a total of 7 games—and help support NPower’s critical work!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/83288f8aa8b3a20bb1051c728d3c0b6d522f7d6c.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9de37895c3a941ad1852fa449c838cef" length="99995" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controller'd Chaos</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/controllerd-chaos</link>
      <description>Give your controller a workout</description>
      <content:encoded>You’re going to want to pick up your controller for this bundle, jam-packed with high-octane action that will test your twitch reflexes! In &lt;em&gt;Maneater&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll assume the role of a fierce bull shark as you navigate an open world, evolve your abilities, and seek revenge against the vile fisherman who has wronged you. &lt;em&gt;No More Heroes&lt;/em&gt;, by the inimitable video game auteur Suda51, casts you as an upstart assassin in a wild quest to hack and slash your way up the hierarchy of hired killers. Get all these games and more–a total of 7 awesome titles–and help support charity with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0d596ef6361e8d9f5f7c27c37f61308f26c18deb.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=cd7de499ec5c8c8a37cf2f24c1f993c2" length="109891" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Soulslike These... You Need Enemies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/with-soulslike-these-you-need-enemies</link>
      <description>Brutal Soulslikes to test your might</description>
      <content:encoded>Take on steep challenges and reap the rewards of mastery in this bundle of epic Soulslike adventures! Shoot and slash, and explore your way through a twisted interdimensional post-apocalypse in &lt;em&gt;Remnant: From the Ashes&lt;/em&gt;. Engage in thrilling, kinetic, and skill-testing hand-to-hand combat and take in the otherwordly wonders in &lt;em&gt;Clash: Artifacts of Chaos&lt;/em&gt;. Help the valiant king of the rats fight off brutal frog invaders in the stunning hand-drawn 2D adventure &lt;em&gt;Tails of Iron&lt;/em&gt;. Pay what you want for all these games and more, and help support buildOn with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/874947738a6faf2bd33041eb41a33cede697cce7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0d5dbd6c457d3d6f43adac37a881c5e1" length="123035" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
