<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 08:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:10:23 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>WB 100: Play the Legends</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wb-100-play-legends</link>
      <description>Celebrating 100 years of Warner Bros heroes &amp; legends</description>
      <content:encoded>This year, Warner Bros is celebrating a century of storytelling—and you can join the party with this bundle filled with the legendary heroes, series, and titles from WB Games! Protect Gotham City city as iconic DC superheroes in &lt;em&gt;Gotham Knights&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Batman: Arkham Knight Premium Edition&lt;/em&gt;. Battle to save existence in the mythic fighting game series entry &lt;em&gt;Mortal Kombat 11: Ultimate Edition&lt;/em&gt;. Get &lt;em&gt;Back 4 Blood&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Middle-earth: Shadow of War Definitive Edition&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Mad Max&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/6a4ba04a19d2c76847e123fdfe0cd840d3920536.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a78d47ddfc75fc03012689bc15498f86" length="89051" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sid Meier's Ultimate Collection: One More Turn</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/sid-meiers-ultimate-collection-one-more-turn</link>
      <description>A treasury of strategy &amp; sim games from the master</description>
      <content:encoded>Our incredible bundle of games from legendary designer Sid Meier returns! Command the fate of the world in two decades worth of &lt;em&gt;Sid Meier’s Civilization&lt;/em&gt; titles, including the latest entry &lt;em&gt;Civilization VI&lt;/em&gt;—plus a wealth of expansions and add-on content that give you new civs and scenarios to play. Plunder the high seas of the modern classic &lt;em&gt;Sid Meier’s Pirates!&lt;/em&gt;. Explore a career-spanning treasury games that’ll have you taking just one…more…turn…all night, and support the charity Trees, Water &amp; People with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ebe533d92d7835c117669420568bf6db3c909289.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=28ca5834cd6ba4ecc88a2f7824fc952f" length="107260" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living in a Simulation</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/living-in-simulation</link>
      <description>The fantasy of everyday life</description>
      <content:encoded>Escape into the cozy embrace of the mundane with this bundle of simulation games that capture the strangely satisfying routines of everyday occupations. Live out your renovation fantasies, whether they involve delicate, tasteful remodels, or rough and ready demolitions in &lt;em&gt;House Flipper&lt;/em&gt; plus the &lt;em&gt;Luxury&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Garden&lt;/em&gt; DLC. Build your agrarian empire by growing crops, raising livestock, and harnessing cutting-edge farm tech in &lt;em&gt;Farming Simulator 19&lt;/em&gt;. Live another life in &lt;em&gt;Firefighting Simulator: The Squad&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Juno: New Origins&lt;/em&gt;, and more, and help support Active Minds with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9437e10255f3ffd3b4a47c3046c525dcd97158a7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9e37b9b3cf854f0d87d897439480fbc7" length="102188" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fright of your Life</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/fright-your-life</link>
      <description>Harrowing Halloween-time horror</description>
      <content:encoded>Seeking something sinister to unnerve you this season? Summon forth this anthology of horror games, and prepare for the fright of your life. Dive to the pitch black depths of &lt;em&gt;STASIS: BONE TOTEM&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Hidden Deep&lt;/em&gt;. Survive the creepy cartoon studio of &lt;em&gt;Bendy &amp; the Ink Machine&lt;/em&gt; and its sequel &lt;em&gt;Dark Revival&lt;/em&gt;. Explore the dark places of Bright Falls in &lt;em&gt;Alan Wake Collector's Edition&lt;/em&gt;, the perfect way to prep for the sequel. Get &lt;em&gt;Tormented Souls&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Pathologic 2&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support International Medical Corps and Direct Relief with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/576a9ac84d23ba3aadc6e20b663fb6fa9fba654d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=5be86d95db5dcf15722e8d927d85288d" length="83831" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandai Namco: Fights, Frights, and Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/bandai-namco-fights-frights-and-fantasy</link>
      <description>Kick, slay, chomp, and roll</description>
      <content:encoded>Get ready to experience the legendary fighting, fantastic worlds, horrific foes, and timeless games of Bandai Namco! Take on your rivals in &lt;em&gt;TEKKEN 7&lt;/em&gt;, the most recent release in the iconic series. Embark on a journey to escape the living nightmare of &lt;em&gt;Code Vein&lt;/em&gt;. Restore the stars as the Prince of All Cosmos in &lt;em&gt;Katamari Demacy REROLL&lt;/em&gt;. Get &lt;em&gt;God Eater 3&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Tales of Vesperia: Definitive Edition&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/498767744556d6ce1971b36b39bca0541609a665.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=6aadd46d9d4143520acc6b48f6ca4915" length="127104" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
