<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 08:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 09:09:09 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Capcom Cup: Fighters &amp; Arcade Classics Pack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/capcom-cup-fighters-classics-pack</link>
      <description>40 years of Capcom history</description>
      <content:encoded>Get hyped for the upcoming Capcom Cup X with this amazing bundle, full of fighting games and arcade classics that span the legendary publisher’s storied history! Experience the entirety of Capcom’s titanic fighting franchise with &lt;em&gt;Street Fighter V - Champion Edition&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Ultra Street Fighter IV&lt;/em&gt; and the exhaustive compilation &lt;em&gt;Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection&lt;/em&gt;. You’ll also get a coupon good for 34% off of &lt;em&gt;Street Fighter 6&lt;/em&gt;! On top of that, you’ll get a vast library of classics in the CAPCOM Arcade Stadium Complete Pack, like &lt;em&gt;Ghouls ‘N Ghosts&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Final Fight&lt;/em&gt;, and many, many more. Pay what you want for 70+ games total and help support Children's Miracle Network!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Games from the CAPCOM Arcade Stadium Complete Pack are collected into two total keys: one for CAPCOM Arcade Stadium and the second for CAPCOM Arcade 2nd Stadium.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/2259dcba01dd73170a0214e78ae33e9abbeb7600.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8b3ab78ff5af31856cd530c9cbf52768" length="139530" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2: The Story So Far</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/destiny-2-the-story-so-far</link>
      <description>Prepare for The Final Shape</description>
      <content:encoded>Guardians! Add this epic bundle to your loadout in preparation for &lt;em&gt;The Final Shape&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Destiny 2&lt;/em&gt;’s upcoming expansion that will mark the conclusion of the Light and Darkness Saga. Included is &lt;i&gt;the last five years' &lt;/i&gt;worth of expansion content* released for &lt;em&gt;Destiny 2&lt;/em&gt;, giving you everything you need, with plenty of time, to level up ahead of &lt;em&gt;The Final Shape&lt;/em&gt;’s release this Summer. You’ll get:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Destiny 2: Lightfall&lt;/em&gt; and the Annual Pass &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Destiny 2: The Witch Queen&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Destiny 2: Beyond Light&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;And more! Whether your service to the Light is just beginning, or you’re an errant Guardian looking to return to the fight, this is the perfect opportunity to get the whole &lt;em&gt;Destiny 2&lt;/em&gt; experience in one bundle. Your purchase will help support the Bungie Foundation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a style="color: #ef9741;" data-darkreader-inline-color=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Customers must download the free edition of Destiny 2 on Steam in order to redeem the keys for expansion content.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/cd644657def5056c1ac3001dfdeeadfea8860eca.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=b3f2ea48eab865de735e5eb5adaea481" length="95428" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind-Bending Masterpieces</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/mindbending-masterpieces</link>
      <description>Brain-teasing adventure awaits</description>
      <content:encoded>Engage in the more cerebral part of gaming with this bundle of outstanding puzzle games, which includes some of the most ingeniously designed titles of recent years. In the award-winning &lt;em&gt;Patrick’s Parabox&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll expand your perception of geometry, space, and recursion as you puzzle out how to fit boxes within boxes within boxes, ad infinitum. &lt;em&gt;Manifold Garden&lt;/em&gt; has you solving physics-defying conundrums in a striking Escher-esque world of infinite architecture. &lt;em&gt;Superliminal&lt;/em&gt; tasks you with escaping a mind-bending dream world where depth and perception don’t behave as you’d expect. Pay what you want for 7 mind-bending masterpieces and help support the Global FoodBanking Network with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/3ad6aaf562c2760d8c19b1400f494eaa4441bc56.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f1e9d9d9cc0e3f764b78ea1e33c37fe0" length="106934" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega Man Franchise Pack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/mega-man-franchise-pack</link>
      <description>An unbelievable Mega Man collection</description>
      <content:encoded>Dust off your side-scrolling skills and dive into some of the best 2D games ever created with this massive collection of &lt;em&gt;Mega Man&lt;/em&gt; games! A substantial chunk of the Blue Bomber’s storied history is at your fingertips, starting with &lt;em&gt;Mega Man Legacy Collection 1&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;2&lt;/em&gt;, which compiles all the mainline titles. You’ll also get &lt;em&gt;Legacy Collections&lt;/em&gt; for the &lt;em&gt;Mega Man X&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Mega Man Zero&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;ZX&lt;/em&gt; series, plus the standalone &lt;em&gt;Mega Man 11&lt;/em&gt;. It adds up to a total of 25 games across 36 years of &lt;em&gt;Mega Man&lt;/em&gt;! Pay what you want for this bundle of essential gaming, and help support JDRF with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d56a008528f6e16f57e71215c13b99b2a014d5b3.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ea746753746f3f047e7b0cad49a52b27" length="130493" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exceptional Indie Allies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/exceptional-indie-allies</link>
      <description>Honor Black history with indie hits</description>
      <content:encoded>Celebrate Black History Month with this bundle of critically acclaimed and award-winning indie games, in support of NPower’s mission to create pathways for prosperity for veterans and young adults from underserved communities. You’ll get &lt;em&gt;Endling - Extinction is Forever&lt;/em&gt;, where you take on the role of the last mother fox on Earth who must make sure that her pups thrive and survive in a hostile world. In the resonant point &amp; click adventure &lt;em&gt;Norco&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll explore a surreal and intimate rendition of Southern Louisiana in search of answers to a multigenerational mystery. &lt;em&gt;Wytchwood&lt;/em&gt; invites you to a dark fairytale world where you’ll concoct witchy brews, battle wits with monsters, and pass judgment on the unvirtuous. Pay what you want for these and more—a total of 7 games—and help support NPower’s critical work!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/83288f8aa8b3a20bb1051c728d3c0b6d522f7d6c.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9de37895c3a941ad1852fa449c838cef" length="99995" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controller'd Chaos</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/controllerd-chaos</link>
      <description>Give your controller a workout</description>
      <content:encoded>You’re going to want to pick up your controller for this bundle, jam-packed with high-octane action that will test your twitch reflexes! In &lt;em&gt;Maneater&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll assume the role of a fierce bull shark as you navigate an open world, evolve your abilities, and seek revenge against the vile fisherman who has wronged you. &lt;em&gt;No More Heroes&lt;/em&gt;, by the inimitable video game auteur Suda51, casts you as an upstart assassin in a wild quest to hack and slash your way up the hierarchy of hired killers. Get all these games and more–a total of 7 awesome titles–and help support charity with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0d596ef6361e8d9f5f7c27c37f61308f26c18deb.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=cd7de499ec5c8c8a37cf2f24c1f993c2" length="109891" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
