<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:11:20 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Games Done Quick 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/awesome-games-done-quick-2024</link>
      <description>Play along with AGDQ</description>
      <content:encoded>Think you can keep pace with some of the most talented speedrunners out there? Test your mettle–and help support charity–with this bundle of stellar games, presented in partnership with Awesome Games Done Quick! Every game in the bundle will be featured during the marathon, which kicks off on January 14th, so you have plenty of time to get your reps in. Master the witchy, stylish action of &lt;em&gt;Bayonetta&lt;/em&gt;. Fine tune your build to effectively conquer the madcap world of &lt;em&gt;Borderlands 2: Game of the Year Edition&lt;/em&gt;. Hone your twitch reflexes in preparation for &lt;em&gt;Celeste&lt;/em&gt;’s sublime platforming challenges. Get all these games and more, and help support the Prevent Cancer Foundation alongside AGDQ!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep up with Games Done Quick via their nightly Hotfix Streams, focusing on different genres and speedrun categories, as well as the AGDQ24 replays at  &lt;a style="color: #ef9741;"href="https://www.twitch.tv/gamesdonequick" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.twitch.tv/gamesdonequick&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a1ad5cf69432606d36f23b2a066d94892bf74968.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a4828863e11508284903f911ff78f11f" length="114076" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play Pink With Twin Sails</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/play-pink-with-twin-sails</link>
      <description>Smash-hit digital board games</description>
      <content:encoded>Snag digital versions of some of the most beloved tabletop board games ever created while supporting breast cancer research with the Play Pink bundle from Twin Sails! Get the epic masterpiece &lt;em&gt;Gloomhaven&lt;/em&gt;, known for its intricate and innovative persistent world and high-stakes tactical combat. Engage in a cutthroat game of competitive economic strategy in the cult classic &lt;em&gt;Terraforming Mars&lt;/em&gt;. Pad your collection with hits like &lt;em&gt;Small World&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;A Game of Thrones: The Board Game&lt;/em&gt;, and get some great non-board games like the management sim &lt;em&gt;Innchanted&lt;/em&gt; and much more! Pay what you want for 30+ games, expansions, and more, and help support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/8cdba03d7661d9effba4f1cb96f9d6fe1f31f475.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=484526fdeedb7f368d7d37c8d56f0345" length="108827" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outright Heroes of Film &amp; Television</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/outright-heroes-film-television</link>
      <description>Big name family-friendly hits</description>
      <content:encoded>Ring in the New Year with the Heroes of Film &amp; Television bundle from Outright Games, packed with a selection of family-friendly titles featuring some of the world’s biggest names in film, TV, and animation. Included in this star-studded bundle are games like:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;DC's Justice League: Cosmic Chaos&lt;/em&gt;: Suit up as Batman, Wonder Woman and Superman and go face off against some of the DC universe’s most powerful villains in this open-world adventure.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;DreamWorks Dragons: Legends of The Nine Realms&lt;/em&gt;: Soar through the skies, unlock and level up a team of draconic heroes, and save the legendary dragon kingdoms in this thrilling action adventure.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Transformers: Battlegrounds&lt;/em&gt;: Assemble a squad of your favorite Transformers, like Bumblebee, Optimus Prime and more, and defend Earth from Decepticon invasion in high-stakes turn-based battles.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a style="color: #ef9741;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outright Games will donate 100% of their net profits to UNICEF UK. This will support UNICEF’s programs for children worldwide and its vital work in promoting education, health and nutrition, and responding to the needs of children impacted by conflict and natural disasters. More info can be found on Outright Games' blog post &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://outrightgames.com/news/outright-games-unicef-partnership/"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;*UNICEF does not endorse any company, brand, product, or service.&lt;/em&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d9a995857394dac5b596a373bda6048ed2e6dcd3.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f6ce55ff28f507a8d8ac673cdbcb01a1" length="133981" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
