<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 08:09:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:09:12 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>With Soulslike These... You Need Enemies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/with-soulslike-these-you-need-enemies</link>
      <description>Brutal Soulslikes to test your might</description>
      <content:encoded>Take on steep challenges and reap the rewards of mastery in this bundle of epic Soulslike adventures! Shoot and slash, and explore your way through a twisted interdimensional post-apocalypse in &lt;em&gt;Remnant: From the Ashes&lt;/em&gt;. Engage in thrilling, kinetic, and skill-testing hand-to-hand combat and take in the otherwordly wonders in &lt;em&gt;Clash: Artifacts of Chaos&lt;/em&gt;. Help the valiant king of the rats fight off brutal frog invaders in the stunning hand-drawn 2D adventure &lt;em&gt;Tails of Iron&lt;/em&gt;. Pay what you want for all these games and more, and help support buildOn with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/874947738a6faf2bd33041eb41a33cede697cce7.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0d5dbd6c457d3d6f43adac37a881c5e1" length="123035" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Games Done Quick 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/awesome-games-done-quick-2024</link>
      <description>Play along with AGDQ</description>
      <content:encoded>Think you can keep pace with some of the most talented speedrunners out there? Test your mettle–and help support charity–with this bundle of stellar games, presented in partnership with Awesome Games Done Quick! Every game in the bundle will be featured during the marathon, which kicks off on January 14th, so you have plenty of time to get your reps in. Master the witchy, stylish action of &lt;em&gt;Bayonetta&lt;/em&gt;. Fine tune your build to effectively conquer the madcap world of &lt;em&gt;Borderlands 2: Game of the Year Edition&lt;/em&gt;. Hone your twitch reflexes in preparation for &lt;em&gt;Celeste&lt;/em&gt;’s sublime platforming challenges. Get all these games and more, and help support the Prevent Cancer Foundation alongside AGDQ!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep up with Games Done Quick via their nightly Hotfix Streams, focusing on different genres and speedrun categories, as well as the AGDQ24 replays at  &lt;a style="color: #ef9741;"href="https://www.twitch.tv/gamesdonequick" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.twitch.tv/gamesdonequick&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a1ad5cf69432606d36f23b2a066d94892bf74968.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a4828863e11508284903f911ff78f11f" length="114076" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
