<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 08:08:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 10:08:39 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tales from Wales Interactive</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/tales-from-wales-interactive</link>
      <description>Decide how the story unfolds</description>
      <content:encoded>Guide the action, steer the conversation, and be the arbiter of characters’ fates in this collection of interactive live-action movies and games from Wales Interactive! Uncover the perilous scientific secrets waiting in the locked-down laboratories of &lt;em&gt;The Complex&lt;/em&gt;. Try to prove your innocence in the high-stakes crime thriller &lt;em&gt;Late Shift&lt;/em&gt;. Navigate the landscape of modern love in the romantic comedy &lt;em&gt;Five Dates&lt;/em&gt;, and more, and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/12b47b4ff07494d03f8daf37be1bcbf3cebc558a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=eddc1f6591c5fdd624f42565a0b369aa" length="74871" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dino Fever</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/dino-fever</link>
      <description>A roaring, rampaging good time</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether your dinosaur fever started with a T-Rex toy, a Mesozoic magazine, or seeing &lt;em&gt;Jurassic Park&lt;/em&gt; in theaters 30 years ago, you’ll find something to satisfy your carnivorous cravings in this bronto-sized bundle of games! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Pit mighty beasts against each other in the physics-based sandbox sim &lt;em&gt;Animal Revolt Battle Simulator&lt;/em&gt;. Travel back in time to hunt the lost lands of &lt;em&gt;Turok&lt;/em&gt; &amp; &lt;em&gt;Turok 2: Seeds of Evil&lt;/em&gt;. Play paleontologist and dig up the past in &lt;em&gt;Dinosaur Fossil Hunter&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support World Central Kitchen &amp; Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c8f10acd435d5051a9e1751eee28f2e5297246a1.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d614442e9c1c1edcb44a1e6cd3b46f0d" length="135843" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterful Modern 3D Platformers</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/masters-modern-3d-platformers</link>
      <description>Channel the spirit of the 32-bit era</description>
      <content:encoded>Warp yourself back to the days of yore, when mascots and collectibles ruled the day, with this bundle of modern 3D platformers! Explore vibrant worlds and don magical headwear that grants awesome special abilities in &lt;em&gt;A Hat in Time&lt;/em&gt;, plus the &lt;em&gt;Seal the Deal&lt;/em&gt; DLC. Hop into action as the valiant marsupial &lt;em&gt;Kao the Kangaroo&lt;/em&gt;, a rollicking platformer brimming with classic vibes. Do the bidding of the devil himself in &lt;em&gt;Pumpkin Jack&lt;/em&gt;, an eerie Halloween-themed action-platformer that oozes style. Get all these games and more, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/6302e43f631c1936adb25555c5d798ee44dd8dbd.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=92052bd8ebf46533aa580911506724ec" length="125893" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You Build It- Cities &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/if-you-build-it-cities-more</link>
      <description>Bring your master plan to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Build bustling cities, rule mythic kingdoms, and shepherd entire civilizations in this god-like bundle of management sims! Shape the fate of planets as you strive to create the ultimate empire in &lt;em&gt;The Universim&lt;/em&gt;. Create the perfect hideout for a diabolical, minion-commanding mastermind in &lt;em&gt;Evil Genius 2: World Domination&lt;/em&gt;. Become a landlord dreaming of a real-estate empire in &lt;em&gt;The Tenants&lt;/em&gt;. Make dinosaur zoos, airborne metropolises, and more, and help support Lotus Outreach International with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/06def6fb55b7beea7daacb6b5bcf7453278b65f8.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c31b819e92972c9bcc1f632fcd070d26" length="91977" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaced Out</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/spaced-out</link>
      <description>Set course for wacky, wild space fun</description>
      <content:encoded>Explore strange new worlds (with a capital “S”) in this bundle of quirky, genre-spanning space games, set in some of the wackiest corners of the cosmos! Blast your way through an alien-occupied Earth accompanied by a star-studded cast of talking guns in the comedy FPS &lt;em&gt;High on Life&lt;/em&gt;. Catalog the mysteries of an exoplanet brimming with zany life as a fourth-rate space explorer in &lt;em&gt;Journey to the Savage Planet&lt;/em&gt;. Embark on a wild trek through a corporate-controlled solar system full of eccentric characters and offbeat humor in the role-playing adventure &lt;em&gt;The Outer Worlds&lt;/em&gt; (plus the &lt;em&gt;Expansion Pass&lt;/em&gt; featuring &lt;em&gt;Peril on Gorgon&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Murder on Eridanos&lt;/em&gt;). Pay what you want for all these games and more, and help support Covenant House &amp; your choice of charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/27d98acaa5ef5ee758581a5559adfe935236305f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c419f6e72d2aee1435edd36d4bd59708" length="123660" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
