<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Games</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Games bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/games" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 08:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:10:19 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Strike from the Shadows: Top-Down Stealth</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/strike-from-shadows-topdown-stealth</link>
      <description>Get the drop on your foes</description>
      <content:encoded>Execute espionage, sabotage, and subterfuge from above in this collection of stealth games played from a hawk’s eye perspective! Mop up murder scenes for the mob in the homage to 90s crime movies &lt;em&gt;Serial Cleaners&lt;/em&gt;. Plan your tactics on the eastern front of WW2 in &lt;em&gt;War Mongrels&lt;/em&gt;. Stalk your foes in &lt;em&gt;Shadow Tactics: Blades of the Shogun&lt;/em&gt; and its acclaimed standalone expansion &lt;em&gt;Aiko's Choice&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support Active Minds and the charity of your choice with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/b5b5abeb50e6afbd8816475d036888e9fc1798e4.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=f057913b2e8589ce44edbf30905f373c" length="148231" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC Building Simulator Rebooted</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/pc-building-sim-rebooted</link>
      <description>A PC builders’ dream bundle</description>
      <content:encoded>Build, boot up, and benchmark the high-end machines of your dreams in PC Building Simulator, the acclaimed sim that draws on real-world components and part makers. Pick up the core game and a virtual warehouse of extra content, including the &lt;em&gt;Esports Expansion&lt;/em&gt; that puts a new spin on career mode, plus a collection of &lt;em&gt;Workshop&lt;/em&gt; add-ons that give you tons more options to choose from for your rig. Whether you’re a novice hobbyist looking to learn or a &lt;em&gt;PC Building Simulator&lt;/em&gt; pro rounding out your collection, this bundle has something for you. Plus, your purchase helps support the charity of your choice!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1a74e3fea0bb17df945d7d9470d7863f1f353191.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=50eff4e684c54001c2bbf9283869a3d7" length="80282" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tales from Wales Interactive</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/tales-from-wales-interactive</link>
      <description>Decide how the story unfolds</description>
      <content:encoded>Guide the action, steer the conversation, and be the arbiter of characters’ fates in this collection of interactive live-action movies and games from Wales Interactive! Uncover the perilous scientific secrets waiting in the locked-down laboratories of &lt;em&gt;The Complex&lt;/em&gt;. Try to prove your innocence in the high-stakes crime thriller &lt;em&gt;Late Shift&lt;/em&gt;. Navigate the landscape of modern love in the romantic comedy &lt;em&gt;Five Dates&lt;/em&gt;, and more, and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/12b47b4ff07494d03f8daf37be1bcbf3cebc558a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=eddc1f6591c5fdd624f42565a0b369aa" length="74871" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dino Fever</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/dino-fever</link>
      <description>A roaring, rampaging good time</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether your dinosaur fever started with a T-Rex toy, a Mesozoic magazine, or seeing &lt;em&gt;Jurassic Park&lt;/em&gt; in theaters 30 years ago, you’ll find something to satisfy your carnivorous cravings in this bronto-sized bundle of games! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Pit mighty beasts against each other in the physics-based sandbox sim &lt;em&gt;Animal Revolt Battle Simulator&lt;/em&gt;. Travel back in time to hunt the lost lands of &lt;em&gt;Turok&lt;/em&gt; &amp; &lt;em&gt;Turok 2: Seeds of Evil&lt;/em&gt;. Play paleontologist and dig up the past in &lt;em&gt;Dinosaur Fossil Hunter&lt;/em&gt;, and more—and help support World Central Kitchen &amp; Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/c8f10acd435d5051a9e1751eee28f2e5297246a1.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d614442e9c1c1edcb44a1e6cd3b46f0d" length="135873" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterful Modern 3D Platformers</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/masters-modern-3d-platformers</link>
      <description>Channel the spirit of the 32-bit era</description>
      <content:encoded>Warp yourself back to the days of yore, when mascots and collectibles ruled the day, with this bundle of modern 3D platformers! Explore vibrant worlds and don magical headwear that grants awesome special abilities in &lt;em&gt;A Hat in Time&lt;/em&gt;, plus the &lt;em&gt;Seal the Deal&lt;/em&gt; DLC. Hop into action as the valiant marsupial &lt;em&gt;Kao the Kangaroo&lt;/em&gt;, a rollicking platformer brimming with classic vibes. Do the bidding of the devil himself in &lt;em&gt;Pumpkin Jack&lt;/em&gt;, an eerie Halloween-themed action-platformer that oozes style. Get all these games and more, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/6302e43f631c1936adb25555c5d798ee44dd8dbd.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=92052bd8ebf46533aa580911506724ec" length="125893" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
