<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 10:10:34 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Mini but Mighty Fantasy Unreal Engine Environments</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/the-mini-but-mighty-fantasy-unreal-engine-environments-software</link>
      <description>Fantastic fantasy environments for your Unreal game</description>
      <content:encoded>Want to build an epic-quality fantasy world for your game or visual project? Pick up this set of three environmental asset packages from Laertes Studios! In this focused collection for Unreal developers, you’ll find: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;A grand fantasy castle suited for a gothic tale or game with souls-like style.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;A stately medieval castle interior, the ideal setting for dramatic moments.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;A medieval tavern exterior and interior, ideal for scenes of rest and reverie.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Their packs also come compete with demo scenes to help get you started. Make something fantastic, and help support charity with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a2e2b1219a1972f61025a5124edddac4138ffb50.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c88c6bfcf24dad0a298e6f6da4b53102" length="93260" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon &amp; Monsters 3 - 3D Printable Tabletop Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/dungeon-monsters-3-3d-printable-tabletop-bundle-software</link>
      <description>3D printable monsters, heroes, and more</description>
      <content:encoded>Warm up your 3D printer and make sure you’re stocked on resin because a veritable horde of 3D printable fantasy minis is heading your way! This expansive bundle contains over 150 items &amp; sets ready to print off, including all the monsters, heroes, terrain, and scenery bits you need to bring the vivid fantasy world of your imagination to life. And if you’re looking for an excuse to field the mighty armies you’ll build, look no further than the included &lt;em&gt;Pirates of the Dread Sea&lt;/em&gt; rulebook, a skirmish game that pits crews of scalawags against each other in fast-paced scenarios. Pay what you want for this massive collection of 3D printable minis and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/68009e3a4ace3f6bfe4616de887dd8e379130a89.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2458fd3088de63ab248d289c0a4d13d2" length="104979" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/level-up-remix-software</link>
      <description>Take your sound to the next level</description>
      <content:encoded>Get an instant, complete music production suite with this value-packed bundle—featuring a pro-level DAW (digital audio workstation), virtual synths &amp; instruments, SFX, and an epic library of thousands of loops and samples! &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Record and mix tracks with the powerful, easy-to-use &lt;em&gt;Mixcraft 9 Recording Studio&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Recreate sounds of legendary instruments with &lt;em&gt;Mercury-4&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Eight Voice Synthesizer&lt;/em&gt;, and more.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tap into loops, vocals, one-shots, and MIDI for a huge variety of styles and genres.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Whether you’re a beginner or a professional already deep into production, this bundle’s got everything you need. Plus, your purchase helps support Music Will!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/989057a30e10e0bb94b3ccf3f4765725a0bf6e8d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=872a7ecaea73989f65f66ccc56f2cdeb" length="160700" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Asset Compendium: Cosmic Sagas and Urban Legends</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/game-asset-compendium-cosmic-sagas-and-urban-legends-software</link>
      <description>Creatures, heroes, and locations for your game</description>
      <content:encoded>Create science-fiction worlds, fantastical adventures, and much more with this vast and varied collection of game assets! This far-reaching library features 2D tile sets for retro-styled role-playing games, character creation kits to help assemble your cast, monsters ready-made to slay, UI elements, music, and more. Gear up to make games from a range of genres, and help support JDRF with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ca55371648afb268fad0c6a982e4f92630d3c42d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=6b3fcae5ab32a949a81a6f8efb46f3bf" length="122804" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Excel, Python and Machine Learning Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-excel-python-and-machine-learning-mega-bundle</link>
      <description>Harness the power of machine learning</description>
      <content:encoded>Are you a game developer, data scientist, business analyst, or someone whose work touches these ever-evolving fields? This bundle of online courses from Mammoth Interactive—covering topics like machine learning, sales analytics, data visualization, and more—will get you up to speed on the cutting-edge technologies that are driving the future of these disciplines. Included in the bundle are several first-time Humble Bundle exclusive courses diving deep into machine learning and neural networks in Godot 4, plus a whole lot more. Get invaluable bleeding-edge instruction, and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/835e0da44d22b4a7cfde5d017be631d490affa11.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e27e2fef8ced172622e8b11feae23f42" length="84378" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Sky Navigators Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/red-shift-9-software</link>
      <description>Your gateway to the stars</description>
      <content:encoded>View the night sky, travel to distant stars, and get a unique glimpse at the wonders of the galaxy with this bundle of astronomy software! Explore the universe from your PC with the award-winning &lt;em&gt;Redshift 9 Premium&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Redshift 8: The Planetarium Software&lt;/em&gt;. Follow the course of planets, moons, and stars on your phone with &lt;em&gt;Redshift Sky Pro&lt;/em&gt; for Android. Observe and understand a marvelous celestial phenomenon with &lt;em&gt;Solar Eclipse&lt;/em&gt;. Plus, your purchase helps support International Medical Corps.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/85b78a3c36f200a1f6e4b67a537ffe2238385088.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1d7369c91f1dfdf53a290fef9cf99f8e" length="99810" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture, Edit, Create! Video &amp; Gameplay Tools by Movavi</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/capture-edit-create-video-gameplay-tools-by-movavi-software</link>
      <description>A content creator’s workshop</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring your ideas for videos, gaming streams, and other creative content to life with this bundle of software from Movavi! Make movies with filters, transitions, and style using the powerful &lt;em&gt;Movavi Video Editor Plus 2022&lt;/em&gt;, plus 9 sets of effects. Capture your best gameplay moments and share them with the world using the lightweight &lt;em&gt;Gecata&lt;/em&gt; game recording software. Take your photo editing to the next level with the AI-powered &lt;em&gt;Picverse&lt;/em&gt;. Bring your creative vision to life, and help support Oceana with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d39127ede1c01df38ec0936ad693d856500eed46.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=462fad5aff6a408f1f9a2ceca8ad69b5" length="136009" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio FX Plugins &amp; Royalty Free Sounds Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-fx-plugins-royalty-free-sounds-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Take your sound to the next level</description>
      <content:encoded>Create music, craft SFX, and make your sound even more spectacular with this awesome audio bundle! This eclectic collection features plug-ins like Obsidian and Outlaw designed to make it easy to transform your sound with spectral delay, reverb, gain leveling, and more. You’ll also get a library of dozens of royalty-free sound packs, including music samples and loops for K-pop, hip-hop, synthwave, or EDM styles. Get the sound you’re seeking, and help support Child’s Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/53daaa8ed4c1059a70463fa743a15a74c001cd40.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7f23774422a455754bbce5bf2922a2e4" length="146182" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Audio Odyssey Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-odyssey-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A universe of royalty-free audio</description>
      <content:encoded>Get all the audio you’ll ever need for your games, films, and other creative projects with this jam-packed bundle of royalty-free music and sound FX! Regardless of the vibe you’re trying to weave, you’ll be covered when it comes to music, with dedicated packs that span themes and genres—from fantasy, horror, and sci-fi, to ambient, classical, and chiptunes. Get ready to paint soundscapes with sound FX including creature sounds, combat clanks, futuristic beeps and chirps, and much more. Embark on an audio odyssey, and help support American Cancer Society with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4ae04fc7fada6735e24561d9a0d444d9caeb2cda.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=03049bf4110172b60ffec9482b4dbfca" length="128229" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know about Godot 4 Encore Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/everything-you-need-to-know-about-godot-4-encore-software</link>
      <description>Create games with Godot</description>
      <content:encoded>Master Godot—the lightweight, fast, and free game engine behind hits like &lt;em&gt;Sonic Colors: Ultimate&lt;/em&gt;. Whether you want to use the brand new version 4 or the battle-tested version 3, these courses will get you building platformers, RPGs, first-person shooters, city-builders, strategy games, and more—no prior experience required! Plus, you’ll learn how to customize your games by creating your own art and assets, all while supporting Girls Who Code with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4fe0d49cab8715a6425171613819387506256216.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=081500b6ff7cfa09d7d1b10d472dac68" length="125128" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
