<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 08:09:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 09:09:30 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Games In Unreal Engine 5</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/make-your-own-games-in-unreal-engine-5-software</link>
      <description>From FPS to Multiplayer: Master Unreal 5 with Courses &amp; Assets</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to harness the power of Unreal Engine and bring your game ideas to life with this bundle of video courses and assets from GameDev.tv! Start concepting in record time with a comprehensive course on Blueprint, Unreal Engine’s intuitive visual scripting system. Jump into the deep end and learn how to get the most out of the engine with a course on C++ programming fundamentals. Apply the skills you acquire with courses focused on FPS and action adventure games, and boost the fidelity of your creations with a stockpile of assets and royalty-free music! Get all this and more–a package valued at over $1,900–and help support charity:water with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4369f054924ecde4dbc1e97ec1e94f9caa232793.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=812ffb879951786d93dea81cf98dda8f" length="74787" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Explorer's Bundle: Travel &amp; Speak Around the World</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-explorers-bundle-travel-speak-around-world-software</link>
      <description>Your passport to the world</description>
      <content:encoded>Equip yourself with the local knowledge and linguistic confidence to visit some of the world’s most exciting locales with this bundle from Lonely Planet and uTalk! Included are over 30 Lonely Planet guidebooks packed with up-to-date maps, travel tips, and itineraries for some of the globe’s most memorable destinations, including Japan, France, Italy, and much more. To help you brush up before your travels, you’ll also get 12 months of access to the popular uTalk’s app, designed by scientists, researchers and linguists to make the process of language acquisition fun and effective. Pay what you want for this indispensable traveler’s toolkit and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/edb4827b262fdd3bf113813dd2acd50bb97308cd.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=27cf6d09e33cb571798f53b8a98e8caa" length="164525" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Learn to Code Bundle 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-learn-to-code-bundle-2024-software</link>
      <description>Coding for AI, games &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded>Interested in learning about the intersection of game development and the rapidly advancing technologies driving AI? This bundle of video courses from Mammoth Interactive will get you up to speed! Learn how to implement, manage, and optimize large language models like GPT with the cutting edge toolkit Ollama. Drill down on the basics of popular game engines like Unity, Unreal, and Godot, hone your programming skills in languages like JavaScript and Python, and much more! Pay what you want for this bundle of over 40 comprehensive courses and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/673a1e57c482f28ec6d4bccdd23caa384ed90b5e.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8f2dd10bdbfd685f1632282325673f2e" length="59037" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Engine Space &amp; Sci-Fi Mastery Kit: Assets, Tutorials &amp; More!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-engine-space-and-sci-fi-mastery-kit-software</link>
      <description>Unreal assets on a cosmic scale</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring the majesty of the cosmos to your Unreal Engine project with Arghanion’s Puzzle Box! This bundle of stunning assets will help you implement all manner of awe-inspiring outer space phenomena into your project. At your disposal are the tools to craft rich asteroid fields and mesmerizing nebulas, generate space stations, planets, and colossal Dyson spheres, and even ready-to-use Unreal Engine blueprints to build functioning space ships. Pay what you want for this galactic treasure trove and help support Code.org with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1ca66ac12f247206e06f108f845d7d6cbebb8308.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0756f247bf4f6f24ff95b2691410aaaa" length="97934" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CZEPEKU's Multiversal Maps &amp; Scenes for Alchemy VTT</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/czepekus-multiversal-maps-scenes-for-alchemy-vtt-software</link>
      <description>Set the mood with awesome maps</description>
      <content:encoded>Stock up on high-quality virtual tabletop assets for your RPG campaign with this bundle from beloved map creators CZEPEKU! From lush mangrove wilds teeming with life and danger, to thrumming city marketplaces, this collection of over 20 maps will help you set the stage for countless memorable adventures. Alongside the maps, you’ll also get Scenes, which are cinematic vignettes handcrafted by CZEPEKU to help you set the stage for your adventures. Pay what you want for this bundle of gorgeous game aids and help support One Tree Planted!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/56bc6d71002d5a3db62d03cf1c9dc478549c9a06.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ec9a8ad3b5396664ee9cebe601865f09" length="144630" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Testing Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-testing-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Hack-proof skills in testing &amp; security</description>
      <content:encoded>Level-up your understanding of cybersecurity and software testing with this bundle of video courses, covering a spectrum of critical skills in today’s IT landscape. Learn to test the security of websites and web applications using the same tools and techniques as the black hat hackers you’re trying to ward off. Achieve mastery of Selenium, the powerful open source set of tools and libraries that lets you automate critical browser tasks for testing web apps and enhancing efficiency and accuracy in your dev process. Get up to speed with testing WiFi security, REST APIs, Ruby, and much more! Pay what you want for this bundle of cutting edge instruction, and help support charity with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/8d0a9084fb75cb819ab5ffce54999849ae772790.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a07423c27e8992a9c09cfcb0a9094243" length="61937" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
