<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 08:10:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:10:02 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Chinese: From Zero To Chinese Hero</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/skillet-learn-chinese-software</link>
      <description>Immerse in Chinese language and culture</description>
      <content:encoded>Take your first step on the road to mastering Mandarin and deepen your knowledge of Chinese culture with this bundle of online courses! You’ll get &lt;em&gt;From Zero to Chinese Hero&lt;/em&gt;, an immersive six-part online course that’ll take you from a beginner into a confident speaker of Mandarin with engaging lessons, cultural insights, and interactive practice sessions. You’ll also get specialized comprehensive courses that dive deep into various aspects of Chinese culture, including its cuisine, history, economy, and much more. Pay what you want for 17 courses in all—a value of over $1,000—and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/53964b3dc1484bb4c1d3e57a0d75610b2b7b48d0.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a98342a38098701d76488675be69ef87" length="133847" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fantasy Realms Bundle by Dragonsan</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/fantasy-realms-bundle-dragonsan-software</link>
      <description>Pro-quality MMO assets for Unity</description>
      <content:encoded>Get the expertly crafted character models that’ll bring your Unity MMO to life with this jam-packed bundle from the master artisans at Dragonsan Studios! Included are an array of separate asset packs that include distinct character models for dwarves, elves, humans, orcs, and more, as well as multiple awesome armor sets each. You’ll also get a vast selection of icon packs that’ll bring some pro-level polish to your UI, ranging from skill icons, to loot, crafting resources, consumables, and more! Pay what you want for over $1,200 worth of assets that’ll make your MMO ready for primetime, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase! </content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/50ec288e0594ed817a3d09c8e180d7f9421703b2.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=778f8bd06954d5e0040ac1d97e7ff72c" length="47972" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Apocalypse Essentials Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-apocalypse-essentials-reloaded-software</link>
      <description>A wonderland of Unreal Engine assets</description>
      <content:encoded>Game makers, give your Unreal Engine project a facelift with this bundle of assets covering all spectrums of the development process! Included are loads of high-quality character models, environments, music, animations, and more! Whether you’re creating a shattered post-apocalyptic dystopia, a soaring heroic fantasy, or anything in between, you’ll get a vast repository of ready-to-use assets to make your prototype ready for primetime. Pay what you want for over $1,200 worth of assets and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/51e5577e3d7b6b55b8a1c44895732db222de2a7d.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=bbfd0b30a68e259461eeda3d6725a193" length="119622" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Everyone</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/linux-for-everyone-software</link>
      <description>Linux mastery for everyone</description>
      <content:encoded>Master Linux, the open-source operating system behind much of the software that drives our world with this bundle of video courses from Packt! Whether you’re a complete newcomer or seasoned Bash-master, you’ll get all the instruction you need to leverage everything Linux offers. Establish your footing with the &lt;em&gt;Complete Linux Training Course to Get Your Dream IT Job&lt;/em&gt;. Refine your knowledge of the fundamentals with &lt;em&gt;Mastering Linux Command Line&lt;/em&gt;. Skill-up into an in-demand field with &lt;em&gt;Linux for Cloud and DevOps Engineers&lt;/em&gt;. Pay what you want for 15+ courses in all, valued at over $1,400, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1b6386a29d3a3c6a2b47cbcc2affdeb075c27823.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d89f88835b69269c57c359ff966bc20c" length="76264" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greater Health, Happiness, and Prosperity by DailyOM</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/find-your-dailyom-software</link>
      <description>The path to self-improvement and health</description>
      <content:encoded>Realize your potential and start the path toward becoming your best self with this bundle of online courses from DailyOM, a leader in holistic health, conscious living, and wellness. You’ll get access to 20 courses taught by world-class teachers across a variety of topics ranging from health, fitness, spirituality, and more, including: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Healing unhealthy patterns and navigate relationships more consciously&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Slowing down, creating more space, and simplifying your life&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Improving your sleep, flexibility, and posture while relieving body stiffness&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Gaining greater prosperity and abundance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; And much more! Pay what you want for this wealth of life-enriching guidance and help support the work of Trees, Water &amp; People with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/5ab22cb8afc1381c07e31a2924161eb9baf4c1f3.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=62268910e4c4a74fc6b83c7a43f38d22" length="60102" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Photography with Anthropics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ai-photography-with-anthropics-software</link>
      <description>Cutting edge photo editing software</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re trying to capture the perfect moment for social media or need to produce high quality images for your business, this bundle of cutting edge editing software from Anthropics is your shortcut to swoon-worthy images. &lt;em&gt;PortraitPro 23&lt;/em&gt; will help you put your best face(s) forward, with sophisticated features to smooth skin, adjust lighting, add makeup and effects, and much more! With &lt;em&gt;PortraitPro Body 3&lt;/em&gt;, you can retouch photos in addition to adjusting the height, proportions, and even the poses and postures of your photo subjects. &lt;em&gt;LandscapePro 2&lt;/em&gt; helps you create stunning vistas, with tools to alter an image’s weather, sky, atmosphere, and more. Get all these indispensable editing tools and more, and help support the Prevent Cancer Foundation with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/e0a113f809c6337f19c8900c974c217163d80967.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=514a940b5ced60b02f0bc6d58091ddd2" length="35045" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Games In Unreal Engine 5</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/make-your-own-games-in-unreal-engine-5-software</link>
      <description>From FPS to Multiplayer: Master Unreal 5 with Courses &amp; Assets</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn to harness the power of Unreal Engine and bring your game ideas to life with this bundle of video courses and assets from GameDev.tv! Start concepting in record time with a comprehensive course on Blueprint, Unreal Engine’s intuitive visual scripting system. Jump into the deep end and learn how to get the most out of the engine with a course on C++ programming fundamentals. Apply the skills you acquire with courses focused on FPS and action adventure games, and boost the fidelity of your creations with a stockpile of assets and royalty-free music! Get all this and more–a package valued at over $1,900–and help support charity:water with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4369f054924ecde4dbc1e97ec1e94f9caa232793.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=812ffb879951786d93dea81cf98dda8f" length="74755" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Explorer's Bundle: Travel &amp; Speak Around the World</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-explorers-bundle-travel-speak-around-world-software</link>
      <description>Your passport to the world</description>
      <content:encoded>Equip yourself with the local knowledge and linguistic confidence to visit some of the world’s most exciting locales with this bundle from Lonely Planet and uTalk! Included are over 30 Lonely Planet guidebooks packed with up-to-date maps, travel tips, and itineraries for some of the globe’s most memorable destinations, including Japan, France, Italy, and much more. To help you brush up before your travels, you’ll also get 12 months of access to the popular uTalk’s app, designed by scientists, researchers and linguists to make the process of language acquisition fun and effective. Pay what you want for this indispensable traveler’s toolkit and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/edb4827b262fdd3bf113813dd2acd50bb97308cd.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=27cf6d09e33cb571798f53b8a98e8caa" length="164525" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Learn to Code Bundle 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-learn-to-code-bundle-2024-software</link>
      <description>Coding for AI, games &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded>Interested in learning about the intersection of game development and the rapidly advancing technologies driving AI? This bundle of video courses from Mammoth Interactive will get you up to speed! Learn how to implement, manage, and optimize large language models like GPT with the cutting edge toolkit Ollama. Drill down on the basics of popular game engines like Unity, Unreal, and Godot, hone your programming skills in languages like JavaScript and Python, and much more! Pay what you want for this bundle of over 40 comprehensive courses and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/673a1e57c482f28ec6d4bccdd23caa384ed90b5e.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8f2dd10bdbfd685f1632282325673f2e" length="59037" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
