<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 08:09:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:09:36 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy and Sci Fi essentials for Unity</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/fantasy-and-sci-fi-essentials-for-unity-software</link>
      <description>Amazing sci-fi &amp; fantasy assets for Unity</description>
      <content:encoded>Propel your Unity game project to new heights of visual fidelity with this massive sci-fi and fantasy asset bundle, crafted by some of the dev scene’s most esteemed content creation studios! You’ll get all the building blocks needed to craft impressive and immersive game worlds, including a vast catalog of sci-fi and fantasy creatures, high-end animation sets for all manner of entities monstrous to mundane, stunning environment packs, and much more. As a bonus, you’ll also get a voucher for the Unity Asset Store good for 10% off your next purchase! Pay what you want for this enormous asset bundle valued at over $2,500, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/db01c5f225bb0ce3fcd88756f95dd13522569ff9.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=4f301a9df47ab5086076f7759cde234a" length="138754" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Managers Toolkit - Become a Productivity Powerhouse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/project-managers-toolkit-become-productivity-powerhouse-software</link>
      <description>The keys to PM success</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn the essentials project management professionals need to succeed with this bundle of courses from Packt! Discover best practices to plan, track, release, and support projects using tools like Trello and JIRA. Explore the benefits and drawbacks of PM methodologies like Agile and Scrum. Level up the skills that help your company and team succeed, and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/290768e2ee46664b781eaba31cdbe9569afec03c.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7724540cdea8a311a92284ffb1e99e64" length="75228" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solo Indie Game Dev Essentials Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/solo-indie-game-dev-essentials-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Succeed as a solo indie game developer</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you're making games as a hobby or your dream is to create video games for a living, this bundle of online courses from GameDev.tv will teach you the essentials that every solo indie developer needs! You’ll learn how to use engines like Godot, Unity, and Unreal to turn your vision into a playable game, get in-depth tutorials on how to create stunning pixel art and 3D assets, and more. You’ll also get a library of asset packs that’ll help you get your projects up and running in no time. Jumpstart your solo indie dev ambitions with this comprehensive curriculum, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/3988eaf663ee2c9dc899a175879d567166d0114b.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=02c2ad42f018a1f1d04f7937df4d8fd6" length="59168" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Character Management Tools for Pathfinder</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/wolflair-heros-lab-software-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Essential tools for Pathfinder 2nd Edition</description>
      <content:encoded>Take the plunge into &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition&lt;/em&gt;—or level up your existing characters or campaign—with Hero Lab Online. In addition to robust character creation and management features that you can access from any web browser, this invaluable suite of tools provides handy campaign management tools, integrated rules and sourcebook material, and more. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlock up to 6 months of Hero Lab Online service (new users only), plus a dragon’s hoard of material from over 20 &lt;em&gt;Pathfinder 2nd Edition&lt;/em&gt; rulebooks, supplements, and modules—including essentials like the &lt;em&gt;Gamemastery Guide&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Advanced Player’s Guide&lt;/em&gt;, and more. Whether you’re a player on the hunt for top-tier character support tools, or a GM looking to make your campaign management more seamless and enjoyable, Hero Lab Online is the upgrade you’ve been questing for. Plus, your purchase helps support The Trevor Project!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/4c5bdb5b8984f0cfcef967c4d3ca20fa6d485f56.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=eb2cc4e348df46385b21edddfa37af1f" length="129299" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectacular Sounds &amp; Marvellous Music Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/spectacular-sounds-marvellous-music-collection-software</link>
      <description>A universe of sound at your fingertips</description>
      <content:encoded>Looking to add some pro-level audio to your game, app, or video project? This bundle of expertly crafted audio assets has the sound effects, voices, ambient sounds, and background music you’ll need to bring a layer of aural polish to your creation. You’ll get the hum and whizz of arcane energy, the crisp flutter of a stack of bills, and weapons fire and melee clanks galore. Get 10,000+ SFX files and 20+ hours of music to cover every genre—even background tracks for your UI—valued at over $900, and support the work of SpecialEffect with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/14f3ab034a93770986a3cd33318da5a6f345d765.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=85151b15c026116ade1ccb689f8d75ed" length="81520" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Blender 3D Modeling Online Course MegaBundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-blender-3d-modeling-online-course-megabundle-software</link>
      <description>Boost your 3D modeling skills</description>
      <content:encoded>Get access to comprehensive tutorials that’ll help you bring your dreams to life with this mega bundle of  Blender 3D modeling courses from Mammoth Interactive! Featuring over 68 hours of online tutorials being made available first exclusively through Humble Bundle, this comprehensive series includes foolproof, step-by-step, cookbook-style instructions to build a variety of characters, environments, and more. Whether you're a complete beginner or looking to take your 3D modeling skills to the next level, this bundle has it all. Help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/8a83c4ebf1e45212f36c0ece9c728d26ff6509f2.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d7675638a4196924778fef041288dfaf" length="87010" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Engine Mega Pack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-engine-mega-pack-software</link>
      <description>Massive maps, modular environments, and more</description>
      <content:encoded>Viking villages, pirate islands, medieval towns, and more… build the game world you’re envisioning with this bundle of assets curated for Unreal Engine developers! This mega pack features fully modular environments to build your play spaces, VFX libraries, packs of Nanite meshes for props, massive ready-to-go maps, and more from the creators at Hivemind. Plus, your purchase helps support World Wildlife Fund!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/7d674332bdd4e5828990f9a416fb9f1ecf9fc584.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0e216eca6102a8d1da02486da3356e04" length="81598" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
