<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:10:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:10:39 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Best of Synty Game Dev Assets Remix Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/best-synty-game-dev-assets-remix-encore-software</link>
      <description>Incredible 3D game art by Synty</description>
      <content:encoded>Back for a Very Humble Holiday encore! Prepare to embark on a game development journey like no other with this bundle from Synty Studios, a leading asset publisher creating 3D low poly art game development assets for Unity and Unreal. Synty creates asset packs that share cohesive art styles, allowing you to mix and match modular 3D models to create the game of your dreams. Their packs also come compete with demo scenes to help get you started. Whether you’re a beginner or seasoned developer, this bundle can help elevate your projects and bring your game to life—and you’ll help support Girls Who Code, too! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a style="color:#EF9741"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quantities for our Very Humble Holiday encore bundles are highly limited, and this bundle will no longer be available for purchase after supplies run out.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; If you purchase the bundle, please be aware that keys may not be immediately available for certain items; we appreciate your patience while we work to restock them.&lt;/a&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/937a147482a758dd888eb01acc7b7e8c8d3df356.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=e6827234b8427a3ef4be8ccd795a5d1f" length="122941" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity RPG Beginners Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unity-rpg-beginners-collection-software</link>
      <description>Craft your dream RPG with Unity</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring your RPG vision to life with this bundle of video courses from Zenva, conceived from the ground up for Unity beginners! Offering hours of instruction in addition to source code that you can adapt, you’ll learn critical skills via hands-on practice that’ll enable you to create 2D action RPGs, 3D turn-based RPGs, mouse-only micro-RPGs, and much more. Also included are courses covering topics invaluable to RPG development, like procedural terrain generation and Unity debugging fundamentals. There’s even a course on how to harness Dall-E to create NPC portraits for your game! Get started on your dream project today, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/6f6b4515dffd89278c175614c3d5ec2bd2ca1b35.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=5e1a490ace34b08262a9153c8e021206" length="97376" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity Power Tools Dev Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unity-power-tools-dev-assets-software</link>
      <description>Supercharge your game development</description>
      <content:encoded>Make your game dev life easier with this power pack from the Unity Asset Store, featuring dozens of plug-ins, FX, and tools from a variety of developers to help you… &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Manage character movement and create animation more easily&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Add systems for dialogue, physics, or survival game mechanics&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Implement lens flare, lightning, projectiles, and other visual effects&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Build landscapes, manage assets, and a whole lot more!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Streamline your game dev processes, and help support Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/67ef5cbfdbd73239c506619bb61d2fcad19545e9.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=fd5bc30ec6d245261ac87f9fbbe5e9a5" length="85637" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Video Bundle by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/devops-video-bundle-pearson-software</link>
      <description>Mission-critical DevOps skills await</description>
      <content:encoded>Upgrade your proficiency with today’s most relevant DevOps tools and technologies with this all-encompassing bundle of video courses from Pearson. Delve into AWS services for defining encryption, compliance, and other critical processes. Get a handle on Kubernetes by diving into server-oriented infrastructure and container deployment. Get up to speed on current best practices of continuous delivery, integrating principles and practices for efficient software delivery. Taught by experts in each respective field, this bundle will help you upgrade your skills in cloud computing, security, containerization, deployment strategies, and more. Plus, your purchase supports Girls Who Code!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/36914aaf0eb90d3f5e373889a46d33921436f282.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3f9fd855248a7e4449ab2e599a7c50a0" length="79727" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS Pro Creative Frontier Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vegas-pro-creative-frontier-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Total content creator’s package</description>
      <content:encoded>Upgrade your video and audio creation capabilities with this comprehensive content creator’s toolkit, packed with world-class software and assets to make your output soar. VEGAS Pro 19 Edit is a comprehensive video editing software package that’s easy to learn, and includes sophisticated compositing features as well as integrated audio and effects. You’ll also get Sound Forge Pro 15, a powerhouse audio editing suite with extensive plugin support, designed to deliver flawless masters. You’ll also get the easy-to-use Magix Music Maker 2022 as well as a boatload of loops, instruments, effects, and more! Pay what you want for this content creator’s treasure trove and help support Save the Children!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/260d2ceca663f65d3f5cbb0c8accfe46befd26be.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=464516e10f7ae505051c9f1af50c7bf7" length="96372" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2D Game Creation Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2d-game-creation-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Full game asset kits for your 2D game</description>
      <content:encoded>Game developers, build your 2D game with this massive bundle of art and sound assets from GameDev Market! This varied and versatile collection features characters, creatures, UI elements, environments, music, and SFX for a variety of 2D game genres. Create your outer space epic, zombie apocalypse, or whatever game you’re imagining—and help support Save the Children with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/aa9300db3ea68f89c1ba74bef0b5c67e4e63b63e.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1f5806ab6556c17bf0cc5560b242ab51" length="99699" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Studio, UVI &amp; Friends - Hitmaking Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/fl-studio-uvi-friends-hitmaking-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Bring the music in your head to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Turn the songs in your soul into certified hits with this musicmakers’ software bundle! This powerhouse pack features a mix of presets, plugins, loops, sample packs, and more to help audio producers and DJs achieve the sound you’re going for. You’ll also get a coupon to save 20% off FL Studio Fruity Edition for a limited time. Get the software and sounds you need, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/09111143b686578f5fc53fb32b8a615419fd873f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=49029a96c9990a7f957f25a4fb7aa083" length="99658" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Game Development Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-game-development-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Build worlds beyond imagination</description>
      <content:encoded>Open the door to a dizzying universe of game development possibilities with this bundle of Unreal Engine and Unity assets. You’ll get a vast trove of ready-to-use game assets for the two most popular game engines in the world—everything from gritty cyberpunk sets and serene seaside vistas, to weapons from across history, high quality icons for your UI, and stunning special effects. Also included in the bundle are a host of tutorials to broaden your skillset, as well as handy plugins that you can quickly add to your workflow. Pay what you want for this vast toolbox of assets valued at over $3,000 and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f08c08afe9f9e692f1b21e6be2e9236f03e88a51.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=35f701299779a72b4587e23096b097d1" length="164247" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Create Game Art in Blender Bundle 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-create-game-art-in-blender-bundle-2023-software</link>
      <description>Your complete Blender learning kit</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn Blender with the help of the creators at GameDev.tv! This comprehensive bundle features everything you need to get started or level up your skills with the free, open-source 3D art software. Learn about animation, rigging, modeling, environmental art, and more with GameDev.tv’s courses. Pick up Alpha Brush Packs and materials to help carve out details in your creations. Get a complete kit for your Blender learning journey, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/319a678a5223667ae6d688f6e15162fffb86f694.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c3ae73b85a5fc9090c139f579065c219" length="70955" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cartographer's Vault: A Treasury of Expertly Crafted Maps</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cartographers-vault-treasury-expertly-crafted-maps-software</link>
      <description>Bring your RPG worlds to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Calling all Game Masters! Elevate your RPGs with this versatile collection of more than 450 meticulously crafted maps by expert cartographers suitable for printing or for virtual tabletop adventures. Explore distant realms, navigate perilous dungeons, and journey through cosmic landscapes. These high resolution maps save you precious time, and immerse your players in your game world. Don't miss this opportunity to unlock an array of immersive maps that will take your RPG narratives to the next level, and support charity: water with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ad6cfa106f256352e27a42445fa68305add422eb.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1f3e32820e2cc3964ca6ae43664cf946" length="211211" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday Python Generative AI Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/black-friday-python-generative-ai-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Stay ahead on AI tech</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re a fledgling coder or a seasoned Python pro, this bundle of courses from Zenva will give you the skills you need to leverage the exponential growth of AI tech. A strong grasp of Python is critical in this thriving domain, and this bundle includes comprehensive courses on a variety of topics to get you ready to dive in. You’ll get instruction ranging from the very basics of Python programming, to cutting edge material like neural networks, large language models, numerous topics across data science, and much more. Pay what you want for this bundle of essential learning valued at almost $1,500, and help support NPower with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9e0701e7cf536c841500cca30049f39dbc40adc5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8ce2e7804d290f8d7f6b5c71e0c6f801" length="50512" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
