<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 08:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 09:09:23 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS Pro Creative Frontier Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vegas-pro-creative-frontier-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Total content creator’s package</description>
      <content:encoded>Upgrade your video and audio creation capabilities with this comprehensive content creator’s toolkit, packed with world-class software and assets to make your output soar. Vegas Pro 19 Edit is a comprehensive video editing software package that’s easy to learn, and includes sophisticated compositing features as well as integrated audio and effects. You’ll also get Sound Forge Pro 15, a powerhouse audio editing suite with extensive plugin support, designed to deliver flawless masters. You’ll also get the easy-to-use Magix Music Maker 2022 as well as a boatload of loops, instruments, effects, and more! Pay what you want for this content creator’s treasure trove and help support Save the Children!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/260d2ceca663f65d3f5cbb0c8accfe46befd26be.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=464516e10f7ae505051c9f1af50c7bf7" length="96372" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2D Game Creation Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2d-game-creation-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Full game asset kits for your 2D game</description>
      <content:encoded>Game developers, build your 2D game with this massive bundle of art and sound assets from GameDev Market! This varied and versatile collection features characters, creatures, UI elements, environments, music, and SFX for a variety of 2D game genres. Create your outer space epic, zombie apocalypse, or whatever game you’re imagining—and help support Save the Children with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/aa9300db3ea68f89c1ba74bef0b5c67e4e63b63e.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1f5806ab6556c17bf0cc5560b242ab51" length="99699" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Studio, UVI &amp; Friends - Hitmaking Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/fl-studio-uvi-friends-hitmaking-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Bring the music in your head to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Turn the songs in your soul into certified hits with this musicmakers’ software bundle! This powerhouse pack features a mix of presets, plugins, loops, sample packs, and more to help audio producers and DJs achieve the sound you’re going for. You’ll also get a coupon to save 20% off FL Studio Fruity Edition for a limited time. Get the software and sounds you need, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/09111143b686578f5fc53fb32b8a615419fd873f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=49029a96c9990a7f957f25a4fb7aa083" length="99116" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Game Development Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-game-development-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Build worlds beyond imagination</description>
      <content:encoded>Open the door to a dizzying universe of game development possibilities with this bundle of Unreal Engine and Unity assets. You’ll get a vast trove of ready-to-use game assets for the two most popular game engines in the world—everything from gritty cyberpunk sets and serene seaside vistas, to weapons from across history, high quality icons for your UI, and stunning special effects. Also included in the bundle are a host of tutorials to broaden your skillset, as well as handy plugins that you can quickly add to your workflow. Pay what you want for this vast toolbox of assets valued at over $3,000 and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f08c08afe9f9e692f1b21e6be2e9236f03e88a51.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=35f701299779a72b4587e23096b097d1" length="164247" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo editing: Cinematic bundle with Luminar Neo Lite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/photo-editing-cinematic-bundle-with-luminar-neo-lite-software</link>
      <description>Photo editing kits, LUTs, overlays, and more</description>
      <content:encoded>Elevate your photography with &lt;em&gt;Luminar Neo Lite&lt;/em&gt;, Skylum’s easy-to-use photo editing software! This bundle features a library of tools to help give your projects cinematic flair, including Editing Kits for a variety of genres and styles, LUTs to apply the colors and tones you’re looking for, and overlays to add eye-catching effects. Get everything you need to create head-turning images, and help support Razom for Ukraine with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/607e2d0bfeab57b84b0f3c141216644cf0e8c786.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8167341353fa98e5137770c14b8f2f12" length="78526" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Create Game Art in Blender Bundle 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-create-game-art-in-blender-bundle-2023-software</link>
      <description>Your complete Blender learning kit</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn Blender with the help of the creators at GameDev.tv! This comprehensive bundle features everything you need to get started or level up your skills with the free, open-source 3D art software. Learn about animation, rigging, modeling, environmental art, and more with GameDev.tv’s courses. Pick up Alpha Brush Packs and materials to help carve out details in your creations. Get a complete kit for your Blender learning journey, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/319a678a5223667ae6d688f6e15162fffb86f694.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c3ae73b85a5fc9090c139f579065c219" length="70955" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cartographer's Vault: A Treasury of Expertly Crafted Maps</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cartographers-vault-treasury-expertly-crafted-maps-software</link>
      <description>Bring your RPG worlds to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Calling all Game Masters…Elevate your RPGs with this bundle from ProFantasy Software! This collection includes ProFantasy’s revered flagship map-making program &lt;em&gt;Campaign Cartographer 3&lt;/em&gt;, which will equip you with the powerful tools to create maps like those you’d find in a deluxe RPG boxed set. You’ll also get more than 450 maps meticulously crafted by expert cartographers, suitable for printing or for virtual tabletop adventures. Explore distant realms, navigate perilous dungeons, and journey through cosmic landscapes. Unlock a treasury that will take your tabletop games to the next level, and help support charity: water with your purchase</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ad6cfa106f256352e27a42445fa68305add422eb.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1f3e32820e2cc3964ca6ae43664cf946" length="209864" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday Python Generative AI Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/black-friday-python-generative-ai-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Stay ahead on AI tech</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re a fledgling coder or a seasoned Python pro, this bundle of courses from Zenva will give you the skills you need to leverage the exponential growth of AI tech. A strong grasp of Python is critical in this thriving domain, and this bundle includes comprehensive courses on a variety of topics to get you ready to dive in. You’ll get instruction ranging from the very basics of Python programming, to cutting edge material like neural networks, large language models, numerous topics across data science, and much more. Pay what you want for this bundle of essential learning valued at almost $1,500, and help support NPower with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9e0701e7cf536c841500cca30049f39dbc40adc5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8ce2e7804d290f8d7f6b5c71e0c6f801" length="50512" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Graphics Bundle Ever 2 - Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/biggest-graphics-bundle-ever-2-remix-software</link>
      <description>A hyper-handy toolkit for designers</description>
      <content:encoded>Expand your graphics palette with this mega-sized bundle of brushes, actions, effects, and other digital artists’ tools from Eldamar Studio! Take your photos to the next level with thousands of professional LUTs and overlays. Get specialized graphic design bundles for everything from comics to Christmastime. Get tools to create images that turn heads, and support Child's Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a22575e746be012e55066267b724ef1486976cd5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8b00090841555879b20691d457ca0ade" length="98476" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Engine Asset Bonanza</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-engine-asset-bonanza-software</link>
      <description>A sandbox of open world assets</description>
      <content:encoded>Get your open world game project up and running at record pace with this comprehensive bundle of assets for Unreal Engine! Regardless of where your project is in development, you’ll get the building blocks you need to make your vision real, including 3D models for characters, environments, props, and vehicles, high quality mocap animation sets, royalty-free music collections, and more! Pay what you want for this massive collection of assets that span the genres, valued at over $2,500, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/796be10b879bf471b61fffbed144fbcc014a53ca.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=11eca12df270dcc686b1286256a288d6" length="86332" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create &amp; Elevate: Amazing Art Tools from Corel</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/create-and-elevate-amazing-art-tools-from-corel-software</link>
      <description>Bring your vision to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Get inspired and get creative with this bundle of amazing visual art software from Corel! Sketch, paint, and illustrate with the renowned Corel Painter 2023, plus a kit full of brush packs to help you create your signature style. Make every shot your best shot with the advanced photo editing of PaintShop Pro, and harness the time-saving power of AfterShot Pro. Become a master of the digital canvas with the help of Corel, and support Children’s Hospital of Eastern Ontario (CHEO) with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/34f47c6f1e0bf90235bb454bd57244daad77ad64.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=00170190a56dc500daffd932260da400" length="94451" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
