<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:44:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 02:44:59 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spectacular Sounds &amp; Marvellous Music Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/spectacular-sounds-marvellous-music-collection-software</link>
      <description>A universe of sound at your fingertips</description>
      <content:encoded>Looking to add some pro-level audio to your game, app, or video project? This bundle of expertly crafted audio assets has the sound effects, voices, ambient sounds, and background music you’ll need to bring a layer of aural polish to your creation. You’ll get the hum and whizz of arcane energy, the crisp flutter of a stack of bills, and weapons fire and melee clanks galore. Get 10,000+ SFX files and 20+ hours of music to cover every genre—even background tracks for your UI—valued at over $900, and support the work of SpecialEffect with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Dev's Guide to Fantasy Character Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/game-devs-guide-to-fantasy-character-assets-software</link>
      <description>A game creator’s bestiary</description>
      <content:encoded>Populate your fantasy worlds with fantastic characters &amp; creatures using this bundle of assets curated for Unity game developers! Featuring fully animated customizable models, meshes, music, and sound effects for devious demons, serpent warriors, behemoth worms, and more, this bundle is packed with everything game devs need to craft thrilling encounters for your RPGs and fantasy epics. Get a monstrous menagerie, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Blender 3D Modeling Online Course MegaBundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-blender-3d-modeling-online-course-megabundle-software</link>
      <description>Boost your 3D modeling skills</description>
      <content:encoded>Get access to comprehensive tutorials that’ll help you bring your dreams to life with this mega bundle of  Blender 3D modeling courses from Mammoth Interactive! Featuring over 68 hours of online tutorials being made available first exclusively through Humble Bundle, this comprehensive series includes foolproof, step-by-step, cookbook-style instructions to build a variety of characters, environments, and more. Whether you're a complete beginner or looking to take your 3D modeling skills to the next level, this bundle has it all. Help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>English Language Travel with Lonely Planet and Utalk</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/english-language-travel-with-lonely-planet-and-utalk-software</link>
      <description>Explore &amp; learn in English-speaking regions of the world</description>
      <content:encoded>Get ready to explore the United States, the U.K., Australia, and more English-speaking regions of the world with this bundle of Lonely Planet travel guides and software from uTalk, the easy-to-use language-learning app! Find out what to see, what to skip, and what hidden discoveries await in New York and New Zealand. Learn to speak and understand multiple regional dialects of English, along with Welsh, Irish, and more. Get a traveler’s kit full of ebooks and software, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders &amp; Ghouls - Sci-fi Modern &amp; Wasteland 3D Printable Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/raiders-ghouls-scifi-modern-wasteland-3d-printable-bundle-software</link>
      <description>3D print your sci-fi wasteland</description>
      <content:encoded>Set the stage for your sci-fi or post-apocalyptic tabletop adventures with this super-sized stockpile of 3D printable terrain, props, characters, and more! Among these 100+ themed sets, you’ll find the bits necessary to build everything from ruined mini marts and gas stations to futuristic police stations and extraterrestrial medical facilities. People your scenes with the veritable army of characters on offer—ranging from modern SWAT operatives to plasma rifle-wielding sci-fi soldiers—and bring your sci-fi wasteland tableau to life! Pay what you want, and support the mission of Direct Relief with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Engine Mega Pack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-engine-mega-pack-software</link>
      <description>Massive maps, modular environments, and more</description>
      <content:encoded>Viking villages, pirate islands, medieval towns, and more… build the game world you’re envisioning with this bundle of assets curated for Unreal Engine developers! This mega pack features fully modular environments to build your play spaces, VFX libraries, packs of Nanite meshes for props, massive ready-to-go maps, and more from the creators at Hivemind. Plus, your purchase helps support World Wildlife Fund!</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberSecurity: Zero to Hero</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cybersecurity-zero-to-hero-software</link>
      <description>Become a cybersecurity champion</description>
      <content:encoded>Want to train up to take on today’s biggest cybersecurity challenges? Go from zero to hero with this comprehensive bundle of courses from Packt. Focus on the fundamentals, and build up advanced skills through hands-on training. Learn how to write secure code, test your systems’ defenses, how to be an ethical hacker, and more—and help support World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiverse of Music: An Ovani Music Sampler</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/multiverse-music-an-ovani-music-sampler-software</link>
      <description>Realms of royalty-free music!</description>
      <content:encoded>Embark on an unforgettable audio adventure with our thrilling new bundle in partnership with Ovani Sound! Experience a variety of genres, from the thunderous Metal Music Pack and mesmerizing Electronic Music Pack to the enchanting Fantasy Music Pack, spine-chilling Horror Music Pack, nostalgic Chiptune Music Pack, and more—over 500 music files total. Score your game, film, or other creative project, and help support the Navy-Marine Corps Relief Society, amplifying the power of music and compassion.</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
