<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 08:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 09:09:14 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Create Game Art in Blender Bundle 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-create-game-art-in-blender-bundle-2023-software</link>
      <description>Your complete Blender learning kit</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn Blender with the help of the creators at GameDev.tv! This comprehensive bundle features everything you need to get started or level up your skills with the free, open-source 3D art software. Learn about animation, rigging, modeling, environmental art, and more with GameDev.tv’s courses. Pick up Alpha Brush Packs and materials to help carve out details in your creations. Get a complete kit for your Blender learning journey, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/319a678a5223667ae6d688f6e15162fffb86f694.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c3ae73b85a5fc9090c139f579065c219" length="70955" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cartographer's Vault: A Treasury of Expertly Crafted Maps</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cartographers-vault-treasury-expertly-crafted-maps-software</link>
      <description>Bring your RPG worlds to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Calling all Game Masters…Elevate your RPGs with this bundle from ProFantasy Software! This collection includes ProFantasy’s revered flagship map-making program &lt;em&gt;Campaign Cartographer 3&lt;/em&gt;, which will equip you with the powerful tools to create maps like those you’d find in a deluxe RPG boxed set. You’ll also get more than 450 maps meticulously crafted by expert cartographers, suitable for printing or for virtual tabletop adventures. Explore distant realms, navigate perilous dungeons, and journey through cosmic landscapes. Unlock a treasury that will take your tabletop games to the next level, and help support charity: water with your purchase</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/ad6cfa106f256352e27a42445fa68305add422eb.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1f3e32820e2cc3964ca6ae43664cf946" length="209864" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday Python Generative AI Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/black-friday-python-generative-ai-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Stay ahead on AI tech</description>
      <content:encoded>Whether you’re a fledgling coder or a seasoned Python pro, this bundle of courses from Zenva will give you the skills you need to leverage the exponential growth of AI tech. A strong grasp of Python is critical in this thriving domain, and this bundle includes comprehensive courses on a variety of topics to get you ready to dive in. You’ll get instruction ranging from the very basics of Python programming, to cutting edge material like neural networks, large language models, numerous topics across data science, and much more. Pay what you want for this bundle of essential learning valued at almost $1,500, and help support NPower with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9e0701e7cf536c841500cca30049f39dbc40adc5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8ce2e7804d290f8d7f6b5c71e0c6f801" length="50512" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Graphics Bundle Ever 2 - Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/biggest-graphics-bundle-ever-2-remix-software</link>
      <description>A hyper-handy toolkit for designers</description>
      <content:encoded>Expand your graphics palette with this mega-sized bundle of brushes, actions, effects, and other digital artists’ tools from Eldamar Studio! Take your photos to the next level with thousands of professional LUTs and overlays. Get specialized graphic design bundles for everything from comics to Christmastime. Get tools to create images that turn heads, and support Child's Play with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a22575e746be012e55066267b724ef1486976cd5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8b00090841555879b20691d457ca0ade" length="98476" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architect - Home &amp; Landscape Design</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/architect-home-landscape-design-software</link>
      <description>Bring your home design ideas to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Design your home with the help of &lt;em&gt;Personal Architect&lt;/em&gt;! This bundle of software contains everything you need to visualize the residence of your dreams, including interiors, landscapes, kitchens, baths, and more. Get 3D home design software that everyone can use, and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/0de81e6d0bf20e802a8ab525025eea7adc4081d4.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=6f8909640e3a6ba76babf6cb47e2c440" length="138613" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Engine Asset Bonanza</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-engine-asset-bonanza-software</link>
      <description>A sandbox of open world assets</description>
      <content:encoded>Get your open world game project up and running at record pace with this comprehensive bundle of assets for Unreal Engine! Regardless of where your project is in development, you’ll get the building blocks you need to make your vision real, including 3D models for characters, environments, props, and vehicles, high quality mocap animation sets, royalty-free music collections, and more! Pay what you want for this massive collection of assets that span the genres, valued at over $2,500, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/796be10b879bf471b61fffbed144fbcc014a53ca.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=11eca12df270dcc686b1286256a288d6" length="86332" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmonic Hauntings: A Horrific Sound and Music Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/harmonic-hauntings-horrific-sound-and-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Craft an unsettling horror score</description>
      <content:encoded>Create a sinister soundscape for your game, film, or audio project with this bundle of spooky samples, macabre melodies, and more royalty-free horror music and sound effects. Craft a chilling auditory experience with the unnerving chords and experimental sounds of Ovani’s Apprehension Engine sample packs. Unnerve your audience with royalty-free horror and sci-fi music. Get 150 music files and 1,200+ sounds, and help support American Cancer Society with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f8ed075c3fdf5bf5ade9eeb7d18563750b154784.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=44d7f1915e80267f7c383efd6e1c6382" length="116527" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create &amp; Elevate: Amazing Art Tools from Corel</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/create-and-elevate-amazing-art-tools-from-corel-software</link>
      <description>Bring your vision to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Get inspired and get creative with this bundle of amazing visual art software from Corel! Sketch, paint, and illustrate with the renowned Corel Painter 2023, plus a kit full of brush packs to help you create your signature style. Make every shot your best shot with the advanced photo editing of PaintShop Pro, and harness the time-saving power of AfterShot Pro. Become a master of the digital canvas with the help of Corel, and support Children’s Hospital of Eastern Ontario (CHEO) with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/34f47c6f1e0bf90235bb454bd57244daad77ad64.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=00170190a56dc500daffd932260da400" length="94451" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon &amp; Monsters 3 - 3D Printable Tabletop Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/dungeon-monsters-3-3d-printable-tabletop-bundle-software</link>
      <description>3D printable monsters, heroes, and more</description>
      <content:encoded>Warm up your 3D printer and make sure you’re stocked on resin because a veritable horde of 3D printable fantasy minis is heading your way! This expansive bundle contains over 150 items &amp; sets ready to print off, including all the monsters, heroes, terrain, and scenery bits you need to bring the vivid fantasy world of your imagination to life. And if you’re looking for an excuse to field the mighty armies you’ll build, look no further than the included &lt;em&gt;Pirates of the Dread Sea&lt;/em&gt; rulebook, a skirmish game that pits crews of scalawags against each other in fast-paced scenarios. Pay what you want for this massive collection of 3D printable minis and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/68009e3a4ace3f6bfe4616de887dd8e379130a89.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2458fd3088de63ab248d289c0a4d13d2" length="104979" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up Remix</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/level-up-remix-software</link>
      <description>Take your sound to the next level</description>
      <content:encoded>Get an instant, complete music production suite with this value-packed bundle—featuring a pro-level DAW (digital audio workstation), virtual synths &amp; instruments, SFX, and an epic library of thousands of loops and samples! &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Record and mix tracks with the powerful, easy-to-use &lt;em&gt;Mixcraft 9 Recording Studio&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Recreate sounds of legendary instruments with &lt;em&gt;Mercury-4&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Eight Voice Synthesizer&lt;/em&gt;, and more.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tap into loops, vocals, one-shots, and MIDI for a huge variety of styles and genres.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Whether you’re a beginner or a professional already deep into production, this bundle’s got everything you need. Plus, your purchase helps support Music Will!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/989057a30e10e0bb94b3ccf3f4765725a0bf6e8d.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=872a7ecaea73989f65f66ccc56f2cdeb" length="160700" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
