<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 08:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 10:10:17 +0200</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dream it, design it, build it! Professional home construction + Extensions</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/dream-it-design-it-build-it-software</link>
      <description>Design your build-ready dream home</description>
      <content:encoded>Are you a pro in the building, landscaping, or interior design trades? Or a DIYer looking to take the reins on your home remodel or landscaping project? This bundle of 3D CAD software from Ashampoo will help you bring your ideas to life! Including pro-grade software like &lt;em&gt;3D CAD Professional 10&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Home Design 8&lt;/em&gt;, and a suite of specialized extensions for kitchens and offices, these tools will help you visualize your ideas beautifully and accurately. Get the tools you need to make your vision build-ready, and support Cancer Research UK and American Cancer Society with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/cf8eee34b8f44d7554dd56b0df847544b456cfdf.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1774884eea4424e1e9ea3ac33dccb9b5" length="63304" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Production Powerhouse Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/production-powerhouse-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Video, movie, and audio software from Magix</description>
      <content:encoded>Become a production powerhouse with this suite of software from MAGIX! This bundle features a mix of potent video and audio tools, including: &lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Video Pro X14&lt;/em&gt;, featuring intuitive video editing and professional tools.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;ACID Pro 10&lt;/em&gt;, the creative DAW for loop- and sample-based work.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Movie Studio 2023&lt;/em&gt;, your entry into the world of video editing.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Plus, a library of Soundpools filled with thousands of loops.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Create movies and music like a pro, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/81f42780ecabe8fc697ecabcdde6a72b9cf7e708.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2f748680722dbcb28b9aa5f4609fdb4e" length="53615" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WW2 Military Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ww2-military-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A stockpile of WW2 assets for Unreal</description>
      <content:encoded>Introduce a level of jaw-dropping authenticity to your Unreal Engine game project with this bundle of World War II–themed assets! Included in this package are game-ready models and blueprints for an assortment of weapons and vehicles, a variety of photorealistic environment packages, and more. You’ll get access to 18 jam-packed asset collections that you can implement immediately into your project, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/906592442ae690d871c16362e99d2f6f309de23e.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=8e269ff000d78e7f4b1d1c368e493a42" length="93443" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stardock Desktop Essentials</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/stardock-desktop-essentials-software</link>
      <description>Powerful PC desktop utilities</description>
      <content:encoded>Organize, customize, and clean up your PC desktop with this bundle of utilities from Stardock! Arrange your icons into resizable shaded areas with &lt;em&gt;Fences 4&lt;/em&gt;. Simplify working across multiple computers with &lt;em&gt;Multiplicity KM&lt;/em&gt;. Create stunning animated mouse cursors with &lt;em&gt;CursorFX 4&lt;/em&gt;. Complete your Stardock toolkit with &lt;em&gt;Start11&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;SpaceMonger&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;IconPackager&lt;/em&gt;, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Licenses are perpetual.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/3a4ae8eb34b3ab8cb2416821253f925b51b20956.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=64a56619ccd852f6103145184d1b090b" length="65380" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Streets by KitBash3D Flash Sale</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cyber-streets-kitbash3d-flash-sale-software</link>
      <description>Assets for your sci-fi dystopia</description>
      <content:encoded>Populate the streets of your cyberpunk worlds with this bundle from KitBash3D! This Kit features kiosks, store fronts, food joints, interiors, machinery, street clutter, and more to craft your gritty futuristic environments—114 assets, 401 meshes, 35 PBR materials, and 375 textures all told. The Kit’s larger pieces also have detailed interiors suited for your sci-fi or dystopian worlds. Make the cyberpunk streets of your electric dreams, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt;Cyber Streets code must be redeemed by September 31, 2023 at 11:59pm PT.&lt;/em&gt;</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f8528258b2a22109d9c910ca6f24ef0085ebd67a.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=968d940e607018444cf0a92585d9664d" length="69687" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAME DEV ROYALTY FREE MEGA MUSIC BUNDLE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/game-dev-royalty-free-mega-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Score your game project!</description>
      <content:encoded>Craft the soundtrack to your quests, the beats to your battles, and the perfect audio backdrop for your game world with this epic bundle of royalty-free music! This massive bundle features 50 music packs suited for a wide variety of game genres and styles, whether you’re creating an epic fantasy RPG, high-seas pirate adventure, hi-octane action game, or dark horror tale. Get hundreds of royalty-free tracks, and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d8906bfff3890ba1a68382f30e7a464ed8274bf8.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=2fccb198b9408770258234f76a0d9c71" length="61822" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bedroom to Billboards - Your Complete Music Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/bedroom-to-billboards-your-complete-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Royalty-free loops and more!</description>
      <content:encoded>Make masterful modern music with this massive collection from Function Loops! This essential producer’s kit features 65 packs of 100% royalty-free samples, loops, one-shots, presets, vocals, MIDI files, and more from a wide range of today’s hottest genres. Pick up &lt;em&gt;Vocal Secrets&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Jazzy Hip Hop Cutz&lt;/em&gt;, and more to equip your home studio with thousands of versatile sound files that’ll help you reach new heights—and help support Music Will with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/e8a79217ad1985b9c9c7a9482b38238dd5a80c06.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=db795376c417d2692d69ef5ae9282c6f" length="111092" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy and Sci Fi essentials for Unity</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/fantasy-and-sci-fi-essentials-for-unity-software</link>
      <description>Amazing sci-fi &amp; fantasy assets for Unity</description>
      <content:encoded>Propel your Unity game project to new heights of visual fidelity with this massive sci-fi and fantasy asset bundle, crafted by some of the dev scene’s most esteemed content creation studios! You’ll get all the building blocks needed to craft impressive and immersive game worlds, including a vast catalog of sci-fi and fantasy creatures, high-end animation sets for all manner of entities monstrous to mundane, stunning environment packs, and much more. As a bonus, you’ll also get a voucher for the Unity Asset Store good for 10% off your next purchase! Pay what you want for this enormous asset bundle valued at over $2,500, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/db01c5f225bb0ce3fcd88756f95dd13522569ff9.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=4f301a9df47ab5086076f7759cde234a" length="138754" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Managers Toolkit - Become a Productivity Powerhouse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/project-managers-toolkit-become-productivity-powerhouse-software</link>
      <description>The keys to PM success</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn the essentials project management professionals need to succeed with this bundle of courses from Packt! Discover best practices to plan, track, release, and support projects using tools like Trello and JIRA. Explore the benefits and drawbacks of PM methodologies like Agile and Scrum. Level up the skills that help your company and team succeed, and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/290768e2ee46664b781eaba31cdbe9569afec03c.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=7724540cdea8a311a92284ffb1e99e64" length="75228" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Blender 3D Modeling Online Course MegaBundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-blender-3d-modeling-online-course-megabundle-software</link>
      <description>Boost your 3D modeling skills</description>
      <content:encoded>Get access to comprehensive tutorials that’ll help you bring your dreams to life with this mega bundle of  Blender 3D modeling courses from Mammoth Interactive! Featuring over 68 hours of online tutorials being made available first exclusively through Humble Bundle, this comprehensive series includes foolproof, step-by-step, cookbook-style instructions to build a variety of characters, environments, and more. Whether you're a complete beginner or looking to take your 3D modeling skills to the next level, this bundle has it all. Help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/8a83c4ebf1e45212f36c0ece9c728d26ff6509f2.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=d7675638a4196924778fef041288dfaf" length="87010" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
