<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 08:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 09:09:19 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Mini DragonSan Flash Sale</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/mini-dragonsan-flash-sale-software</link>
      <description>MMO asset flash sale happening now</description>
      <content:encoded>Hard at work on your upcoming MMO masterpiece? Don’t miss out on your chance to snag this bundle of expertly crafted assets by the MMO specialists at DragonSan, available for &lt;em&gt;one week starting now!&lt;/em&gt;. You’ll get three separate packs that include two distinct character models each for dwarves, elves, and humans, as well as multiple awesome armor sets, all usable on the Unity game engine. Also included slick icon packs for loot and herbs, ready to add a layer of polish to your inventory system. Act now and claim this awesome value before it’s gone and help support charity with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/a685613e320717881f77c617740ea0ad18f92d05.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=76e5f44a9b1c98c598af1e7f51cf50eb" length="94691" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Engine Space &amp; Sci-Fi Mastery Kit: Assets, Tutorials &amp; More!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-engine-space-and-sci-fi-mastery-kit-software</link>
      <description>Unreal assets on a cosmic scale</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring the majesty of the cosmos to your Unreal Engine project with Arghanion’s Puzzle Box! This bundle of stunning assets will help you implement all manner of awe-inspiring outer space phenomena into your project. At your disposal are the tools to craft rich asteroid fields and mesmerizing nebulas, generate space stations, planets, and colossal Dyson spheres, and even ready-to-use Unreal Engine blueprints to build functioning space ships. Pay what you want for this galactic treasure trove and help support Code.org with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/1ca66ac12f247206e06f108f845d7d6cbebb8308.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=0756f247bf4f6f24ff95b2691410aaaa" length="97934" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CZEPEKU's Multiversal Maps &amp; Scenes for Alchemy VTT</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/czepekus-multiversal-maps-scenes-for-alchemy-vtt-software</link>
      <description>Set the mood with awesome maps</description>
      <content:encoded>Stock up on high-quality virtual tabletop assets for your RPG campaign with this bundle from beloved map creators CZEPEKU! From lush mangrove wilds teeming with life and danger, to thrumming city marketplaces, this collection of over 20 maps will help you set the stage for countless memorable adventures. Alongside the maps, you’ll also get Scenes, which are cinematic vignettes handcrafted by CZEPEKU to help you set the stage for your adventures. Pay what you want for this bundle of gorgeous game aids and help support One Tree Planted!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/56bc6d71002d5a3db62d03cf1c9dc478549c9a06.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ec9a8ad3b5396664ee9cebe601865f09" length="144630" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Testing Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-testing-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Hack-proof skills in testing &amp; security</description>
      <content:encoded>Level-up your understanding of cybersecurity and software testing with this bundle of video courses, covering a spectrum of critical skills in today’s IT landscape. Learn to test the security of websites and web applications using the same tools and techniques as the black hat hackers you’re trying to ward off. Achieve mastery of Selenium, the powerful open source set of tools and libraries that lets you automate critical browser tasks for testing web apps and enhancing efficiency and accuracy in your dev process. Get up to speed with testing WiFi security, REST APIs, Ruby, and much more! Pay what you want for this bundle of cutting edge instruction, and help support charity with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/8d0a9084fb75cb819ab5ffce54999849ae772790.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a07423c27e8992a9c09cfcb0a9094243" length="61937" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity RPG Beginners Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unity-rpg-beginners-collection-software</link>
      <description>Craft your dream RPG with Unity</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring your RPG vision to life with this bundle of video courses from Zenva, conceived from the ground up for Unity beginners! Offering hours of instruction in addition to source code that you can adapt, you’ll learn critical skills via hands-on practice that’ll enable you to create 2D action RPGs, 3D turn-based RPGs, mouse-only micro-RPGs, and much more. Also included are courses covering topics invaluable to RPG development, like procedural terrain generation and Unity debugging fundamentals. There’s even a course on how to harness Dall-E to create NPC portraits for your game! Get started on your dream project today, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/6f6b4515dffd89278c175614c3d5ec2bd2ca1b35.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=5e1a490ace34b08262a9153c8e021206" length="97376" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity Power Tools Dev Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unity-power-tools-dev-assets-software</link>
      <description>Supercharge your game development</description>
      <content:encoded>Make your game dev life easier with this power pack from the Unity Asset Store, featuring dozens of plug-ins, FX, and tools from a variety of developers to help you… &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Manage character movement and create animation more easily&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Add systems for dialogue, physics, or survival game mechanics&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Implement lens flare, lightning, projectiles, and other visual effects&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Build landscapes, manage assets, and a whole lot more!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Streamline your game dev processes, and help support Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/67ef5cbfdbd73239c506619bb61d2fcad19545e9.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=fd5bc30ec6d245261ac87f9fbbe5e9a5" length="85637" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Video Bundle by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/devops-video-bundle-pearson-software</link>
      <description>Mission-critical DevOps skills await</description>
      <content:encoded>Upgrade your proficiency with today’s most relevant DevOps tools and technologies with this all-encompassing bundle of video courses from Pearson. Delve into AWS services for defining encryption, compliance, and other critical processes. Get a handle on Kubernetes by diving into server-oriented infrastructure and container deployment. Get up to speed on current best practices of continuous delivery, integrating principles and practices for efficient software delivery. Taught by experts in each respective field, this bundle will help you upgrade your skills in cloud computing, security, containerization, deployment strategies, and more. Plus, your purchase supports Girls Who Code!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/36914aaf0eb90d3f5e373889a46d33921436f282.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=3f9fd855248a7e4449ab2e599a7c50a0" length="79727" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS Pro Creative Frontier Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vegas-pro-creative-frontier-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Total content creator’s package</description>
      <content:encoded>Upgrade your video and audio creation capabilities with this comprehensive content creator’s toolkit, packed with world-class software and assets to make your output soar. VEGAS Pro 19 Edit is a comprehensive video editing software package that’s easy to learn, and includes sophisticated compositing features as well as integrated audio and effects. You’ll also get Sound Forge Pro 15, a powerhouse audio editing suite with extensive plugin support, designed to deliver flawless masters. You’ll also get the easy-to-use Magix Music Maker 2022 as well as a boatload of loops, instruments, effects, and more! Pay what you want for this content creator’s treasure trove and help support Save the Children!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/260d2ceca663f65d3f5cbb0c8accfe46befd26be.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=464516e10f7ae505051c9f1af50c7bf7" length="96372" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2D Game Creation Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2d-game-creation-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Full game asset kits for your 2D game</description>
      <content:encoded>Game developers, build your 2D game with this massive bundle of art and sound assets from GameDev Market! This varied and versatile collection features characters, creatures, UI elements, environments, music, and SFX for a variety of 2D game genres. Create your outer space epic, zombie apocalypse, or whatever game you’re imagining—and help support Save the Children with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/aa9300db3ea68f89c1ba74bef0b5c67e4e63b63e.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=1f5806ab6556c17bf0cc5560b242ab51" length="99699" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Studio, UVI &amp; Friends - Hitmaking Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/fl-studio-uvi-friends-hitmaking-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Bring the music in your head to life</description>
      <content:encoded>Turn the songs in your soul into certified hits with this musicmakers’ software bundle! This powerhouse pack features a mix of presets, plugins, loops, sample packs, and more to help audio producers and DJs achieve the sound you’re going for. You’ll also get a coupon to save 20% off FL Studio Fruity Edition for a limited time. Get the software and sounds you need, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/09111143b686578f5fc53fb32b8a615419fd873f.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=49029a96c9990a7f957f25a4fb7aa083" length="99658" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Game Development Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-game-development-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Build worlds beyond imagination</description>
      <content:encoded>Open the door to a dizzying universe of game development possibilities with this bundle of Unreal Engine and Unity assets. You’ll get a vast trove of ready-to-use game assets for the two most popular game engines in the world—everything from gritty cyberpunk sets and serene seaside vistas, to weapons from across history, high quality icons for your UI, and stunning special effects. Also included in the bundle are a host of tutorials to broaden your skillset, as well as handy plugins that you can quickly add to your workflow. Pay what you want for this vast toolbox of assets valued at over $3,000 and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/f08c08afe9f9e692f1b21e6be2e9236f03e88a51.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=35f701299779a72b4587e23096b097d1" length="164247" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Create Game Art in Blender Bundle 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-create-game-art-in-blender-bundle-2023-software</link>
      <description>Your complete Blender learning kit</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn Blender with the help of the creators at GameDev.tv! This comprehensive bundle features everything you need to get started or level up your skills with the free, open-source 3D art software. Learn about animation, rigging, modeling, environmental art, and more with GameDev.tv’s courses. Pick up Alpha Brush Packs and materials to help carve out details in your creations. Get a complete kit for your Blender learning journey, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/319a678a5223667ae6d688f6e15162fffb86f694.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c3ae73b85a5fc9090c139f579065c219" length="70955" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
