<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Py Humble Software</title>
    <link>https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle Software bundles!</description>
    <atom:link href="https://shimst3r.xyz/py-humble/software" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 08:08:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 09:08:55 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Environment Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/unreal-environment-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The ultimate Unreal worldbuilder’s toolkit</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ousRgF0CFHg?si=c96-ddsCav-9KENN" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt; Unreal developers, this bundle will give you everything you need to craft game environments that’ll enthrall and immerse your players! Included are 15 packs of full models, meshes, visual effects, and more, modular and ready to drop into your Unreal Engine project. You’ll get assets suitable for all kinds of genres, enabling you to create stunning fantasy worlds, blighted post apocalyptic settings, lush natural environments, and much more. Pay what you want for over $1100 worth of assets and help support Trees, Water &amp; People with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/dbdf5504836825337e94021e8cdb202cbe08a69d.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=31fef2090b04255cd2267997af9e8f38" length="99094" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic Game Worlds in Unity Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/epic-game-worlds-in-unity-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Amazing assets, audio &amp; more for Unity</description>
      <content:encoded>Bolster your game-maker’s toolkit with this Unity bundle, full of visual assets, plugins, audio, and more! You’ll get the &lt;em&gt;Nature Renderer&lt;/em&gt; plugin to level up your game’s scenery with advanced features  and custom shader support. The &lt;em&gt;Big Fantasy RPG Music Bundle&lt;/em&gt; is packed with over 443 tracks of orchestral tunes to score all aspects of your epic adventure. If you’re going for retro vibes, the &lt;em&gt;Low Poly Nature Pack&lt;/em&gt; puts 800 high-quality game-ready 3D nature assets at reach, crafted with botanical accuracy and low poly charm. Pay what you want for all this and more, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/85a25f8282445c9b1175b58e95edd4e4455314c6.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=009ed7d2c99b5f24bd806acae951dda1" length="187199" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering 101</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/packt-data-engineering-software</link>
      <description>Get started with data engineering</description>
      <content:encoded>Learn the skills you need to secure a career in the growing, in-demand field of data engineering with this bundle of online video courses from Packt! It’ll bring you up to speed on a number of today’s most relevant technologies, including Apache Spark &amp; Kafka, Amazon Web Services, SQL &amp; MySQL, Elasticsearch, and many more. You’ll learn to build the infrastructure to enable everything from large-scale data analytics and robust real-time data pipelines to cutting edge machine learning models and big data warehousing. Pay what you want for this bundle, valued at more than $1,700, and help support Girls Who Code.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/8b81d946864e6d4f9a42f94438b41c69f17f1dc1.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=c00ceb2a5ca1e545e4d0746cfe929247" length="98890" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your fantasy world with KitBash3D's Enchanted Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/build-your-fantasy-world-with-kitbash3ds-enchanted-collection-software</link>
      <description>Craft your own enchanted land</description>
      <content:encoded>Bring your dream fantasy world to life with this bundle of stunning premium 3D assets from KitBash3D! This bundle consists of KitBash3D’s &lt;em&gt;Enchanted&lt;/em&gt; asset kit, which is perfect for any fantasy setting. You’ll get all the buildings you need to craft any number of convincing and authentic medieval fantasy environments—from bustling inns and pubs, to majestic keeps and secluded wizards’ towers. You’ll get a vast toolbox full of props to help make your fantasy world feel cozy and lived-in. Take advantage of this unbelievable value and help support Girls Who Code!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9aaa8750001ff5b918377684c0281559ddc78985.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a985a2e868d2beb5deeb2967e0cac6be" length="109908" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beat Builders: Crafting Captivating Tunes</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/beat-builders-crafting-captivating-tunes-software</link>
      <description>A trove of royalty free audio</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O96K2tJzSAY?si=Q4CkpCc42X80EVgL" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt; Whether you’re a game developer, musician, or creative of any stripe, you’ll want to get your hands on this bundle of royalty free audio goods from Function Loops. Included are 20 soundtrack packs spanning the genres, ready to drop into your workflow. You’ll also get a number of jam-packed sound collections loaded with FX like impacts, melodies, and atmospheres, plus an array of multi-genre music packs filled with stems, loops, one-shots, and MIDI. As a bonus, you’ll get both Function’s Vocal Music Production Course and their Tech House Drums VST plugin. Pay what you want for over $1,200 worth of royalty free audio and help support Music Will with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/9ac73e8e6e23173e3ce8471871b035b4eaa27115.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=b6e3fc86ee026e3bf54d7c6af7fd8163" length="109268" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melodic Mayhem: A Comprehensive Audio and Music Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/melodic-mayhem-comprehensive-audio-and-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Your audio needs are met</description>
      <content:encoded>Upgrade your next project with pro-level audio with this mind-bogglingly huge bundle, packed with all the music, sound effects, and engine-specific plugins you’ll ever need. You’ll get royalty-free tracks that span the genres, both musical and thematic—from atmospheric synthpop and hard-driving industrial, to tunes perfect for fantasy, sci-fi, and more. Also included is a vast library of sound effects suitable for all manner of genres and settings, as well as jingles and UI sounds, plus essential sound plugins for Unreal, Unity, and Godot. Pay what you want for a library that will cover your audio needs forever and help support the Children's Miracle Network with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/d20dd9975e578125b632be5beefff8ae3cc260f5.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=9becd60290e58206e4a5020e444a6b89" length="100517" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACI Network Mastery</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/aci-network-mastery-software</link>
      <description>Career-boosting IT certifications await</description>
      <content:encoded>Looking to upskill into the IT world? Or want to make your qualifications bulletproof to potential employers? This bundle of video courses from Packt is designed to get you ready for a wide range of IT certifications! You’ll get access to a host of expert-led courses covering essential certification tests from CompTIA, Cisco, Google, Palo Alto Networks, and more, covering everything from networking basics and cloud platforms, to specialized topics like cybersecurity and IoT. Pay what you want for hours of instructions valued at over $4,000 and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/61e95b1b4a3e9ce34c74bb09d8606fc95ee76cfa.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=27dfdcb76d21212cdb230f47020cf1c0" length="136618" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create &amp; Elevate: Amazing Art Tools from Corel Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/create-and-elevate-amazing-art-tools-from-corel-encore-software</link>
      <description>Corel’s artist’s arsenal is back!</description>
      <content:encoded>Back by popular demand, this bundle of digital art and editing tools from Corel will help you make your artistic vision real! Sketch, paint, and illustrate with the renowned Corel Painter 2023, including a kit full of brush packs to help you create your signature style. Make every shot your best with the advanced photo editing capabilities of PaintShop Pro, and harness the time-saving power of AfterShot Pro. Become a master of the digital canvas with the help of Corel, and help support Children’s Hospital of Eastern Ontario (CHEO) with your purchase!</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/6265c92943d246deedd9c67726ac8f4ce6092cf5.jpg?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=ad6dd9a746e92b4893dcb0b1e901c6d0" length="94421" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Chinese: From Zero To Chinese Hero</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/skillet-learn-chinese-software</link>
      <description>Immerse in Chinese language and culture</description>
      <content:encoded>Take your first step on the road to mastering Mandarin and deepen your knowledge of Chinese culture with this bundle of online courses! You’ll get &lt;em&gt;From Zero to Chinese Hero&lt;/em&gt;, an immersive six-part online course that’ll take you from a beginner into a confident speaker of Mandarin with engaging lessons, cultural insights, and interactive practice sessions. You’ll also get specialized comprehensive courses that dive deep into various aspects of Chinese culture, including its cuisine, history, economy, and much more. Pay what you want for 17 courses in all—a value of over $1,000—and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/53964b3dc1484bb4c1d3e57a0d75610b2b7b48d0.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=a98342a38098701d76488675be69ef87" length="133847" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Apocalypse Essentials Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-apocalypse-essentials-reloaded-software</link>
      <description>A wonderland of Unreal Engine assets</description>
      <content:encoded>Game makers, give your Unreal Engine project a facelift with this bundle of assets covering all spectrums of the development process! Included are loads of high-quality character models, environments, music, animations, and more! Whether you’re creating a shattered post-apocalyptic dystopia, a soaring heroic fantasy, or anything in between, you’ll get a vast repository of ready-to-use assets to make your prototype ready for primetime. Pay what you want for over $1,200 worth of assets and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase.</content:encoded>
      <enclosure url="https://hb.imgix.net/51e5577e3d7b6b55b8a1c44895732db222de2a7d.png?auto=compress,format&amp;fit=crop&amp;h=600&amp;w=1200&amp;s=bbfd0b30a68e259461eeda3d6725a193" length="119622" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
